The two masters who dominate the Korean art world.
الأساتذة اللذين يهيمنان على عالم الفن الكوري.
(Title: At the Shoot, Title: TV Rating Notice)
(العنوان: في التصوير ، العنوان: إشعار تصنيف التلفزيون)
(The detailed expression and artistry are remarkable.)
(التعبير التفصيلي والفن رائعان.)
I just did it,
لقد فعلت ذلك للتو ،
- and I found it fun. - Born with artistic blood,
- ووجدته ممتعًا. - ولد بدم فني ،
- the elite artists, the Kim Family. - I should draw.
- الفنانين النخبة ، عائلة كيم. - يجب أن أرسم.
Though he may not look like it,
على الرغم من أنه قد لا يبدو هكذا ،
(The avant-garde art that breaks form and framework)
(فن الطليعة الذي يكسر الشكل والإطار)
He was not cut out for comedy, so he gave up being a comedian...
لم يكن مقطوعًا للكوميديا ، لذلك تخلى عن كونه كوميديًا ...
and pursued the path of an artist. The Yu Family.
ومتابعة مسار الفنان. عائلة يو.
This is Son Heung Min.
هذا هو الابن هيونغ مين.
- Son Heung Min? - What?
- الابن هيونغ مين؟ - ماذا؟
How is this a soccer ball?
كيف هذه كرة كرة قدم؟
The drawing looks the same!
الرسم يبدو نفسه!
What is this?
ما هذا؟
(Title: Deer)
(العنوان: الغزلان)
(Isn't this a carrot?)
(أليس هذا الجزرة؟)
The two families, disrespectful of each other's talent,
العائلتان ، لا تحترم موهبة بعضهما البعض ،
are having a showdown to determine the winner today.
لديهم مواجهة لتحديد الفائز اليوم.
It's been a really long time since I picked up a brush.
لقد مضى وقت طويل منذ أن التقطت فرشاة.
I should try drawing this guy.
يجب أن أحاول رسم هذا الرجل.
His face is a little...
وجهه قليلا ...
(Painter Kim is drawing someone's portrait.)
(الرسام كيم يرسم صورة لشخص ما.)
The teeth.
الأسنان.
It totally looks like a locust.
يبدو تماما مثل الجراد.
Seriously, this looks just like Yu Jae Seok.
على محمل الجد ، هذا يبدو مثل يو جاي سوك.
All right. I should do some art...
حسنًا. يجب أن أفعل بعض الفن ...
after a long time.
بعد وقت طويل.
(Painter Yu works on a drawing after a long time.)
(الرسام يو يعمل على رسم بعد فترة طويلة.)
Would you like me to draw your face?
هل تريد مني أن أرسم وجهك؟
- Me? - Yes.
- أنا؟ - نعم.
Yes. Don't worry and trust me.
نعم. لا تقلق وأثق بي.
My family has been painting for generations.
كانت عائلتي ترسم للأجيال.
My family is also known for being quick drawers.
تشتهر عائلتي أيضًا بأنها أدراج سريعة.
(Messy)
(فوضوي)
It will be quick.
سيكون سريعا.
(A bold touch to replace hands with tree branches)
(لمسة جريئة لاستبدال اليدين بفروع الأشجار)
(Drawing without hesitation)
(الرسم دون تردد)
It's done.
لقد تم.
- Is it over already? - Sure.
- هل انتهى بالفعل؟ - بالتأكيد.
This is my drawing.
هذا هو الرسم الخاص بي.
I'll give this to you. This will go up in price later.
سأعطي هذا لك. هذا سوف يرتفع السعر في وقت لاحق.
It will bring you good money.
سوف يجلب لك المال الجيد.
My hands look like chicken feet.
يدي تبدو مثل أقدام الدجاج.
That's a characteristic of my painting style.
هذه سمة من سمات أسلوب الرسم الخاص بي.
It needs things like this to be recognized for its value later.
يحتاج إلى أشياء مثل هذا ليتم الاعتراف بها لقيمته لاحقًا.
I notice you have long hair.
لاحظت أن لديك شعر طويل.
(Adding details)
(إضافة تفاصيل)
(Chuckling)
(ضحكة مكتومة)
All right. I drew the hair.
حسنًا. وجهت الشعر.
(A unique art style that ordinary people can't appreciate)
(أسلوب فني فريد لا يمكن أن يقدره الناس العاديون)
Who is that? Hey.
من ذاك؟ يا.
- Hello, Father. - Dad.
- مرحبا أبي. - أب.
Hey, you guys are here.
مهلا ، يا رفاق هنا.
- Hello. - Father.
- مرحبًا. - أب.
The comedian-turned-painter family.
الكوميدي الذي تحول إلى عائلة painter.
(As expected from former comedians, they show up while making a fuss.)
(كما هو متوقع من الكوميديين السابقين ، يظهرون أثناء إثارة ضجة.)
Are you a couple?
هل انت زوجين؟
- No. - No, she's my younger sister.
- لا. - لا ، إنها أختي الصغرى.
Why do you keep saying that we're a couple?
لماذا لا تزال تقول أننا زوجين؟
- You two... - I'm the third child.
- أنتما ... - أنا الطفل الثالث.
- You are wearing similar clothes. - I see.
- أنت ترتدي ملابس مماثلة. - أرى.
- My younger sister. - He's dressed like a nerd.
- أختي الصغرى. - إنه يرتدي مثل الطالب الذي يذاكر كثيرا.
- What? - I'm dressed like a moron.
- ماذا؟ - أنا أرتدي مثل المعتوه.
A moron or a nerd.
معتوه أو الطالب الذي يذاكر كثيرا.
Please draw something for me.
من فضلك ارسم شيئًا لي.
- You want one? - Yes.
- تريد واحد؟ - نعم.
Hang on. Actually, I was...
انتظر. في الواقع ، كنت ...
(They take a look at what he drew in advance first.)
(يلقون نظرة على ما رسمه مقدمًا أولاً.)
- I drew one person. - What?
- رسمت شخص واحد. - ماذا؟
- Is it one of the people here? - Yes.
- هل هو أحد الناس هنا؟ - نعم.
- It's Wan Su. - I see.
- إنه wan su. - أرى.
I recognize it. You know that.
أنا أدرك ذلك. أنت تعرف ذلك.
- I didn't know. - It's Wan Su.
- لم أكن أعرف. - إنه wan su.
- It looks like her, right? - Yes.
- يبدو مثلها ، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
He recognizes Su Wan right away.
انه يعترف سو وان على الفور.
- It's Su Wan. - He recognizes her right away.
- إنه سو وان. - يتعرف عليها على الفور.
- Try drawing Ye Eun. - Ye Eun?
- حاول رسم أيها. - أيها يون؟
- Okay. I'll draw Ye Eun. - Stand in front of him.
- تمام. سأرسم أيها ايون. - قف أمامه.
- Draw your youngest daughter. - Okay.
- ارسم ابنتك الصغرى. - تمام.
I'll draw my youngest daughter.
سأرسم ابنتي الصغرى.
In the past, all I needed was a double chin to draw Ye Eun's face.
في الماضي ، كان كل ما احتاجه هو الذقن المزدوجة لرسم وجه eun.
But now...
لكن الآن ...
Your face has become a lot slimmer.
أصبح وجهك أنحف كثيرًا.
Gosh, it's really slim.
يا إلهي ، إنه نحيف حقًا.
- I know, right? - Yes.
- أنا أوافق؟ - نعم.
- My drawing has the vibe, right?
- الرسم الخاص بي لديه فيبي ، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
You know that my trademark is the dimples, right?
أنت تعلم أن علامتي التجارية هي الدمامل ، أليس كذلك؟
Don't worry. I'll draw them.
لا تقلق. سأرسمهم.
Why?
لماذا؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
(Wrinkles disguised as dimples)
(التجاعيد متنكرا كدمامل)
- It looks the same, right? - Yes.
- يبدو نفسه ، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
Seriously...
بجد...
Why?
لماذا؟
- All right. - It looks great.
- حسنًا. - يبدو رائعا.
- This is my youngest daughter. - Here.
- هذه هي ابنتي الأصغر. - هنا.
- Her expression looks the same. - Okay.
- تعبيرها يبدو نفسه. - تمام.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
This is you. These are your dimples.
هذا أنت. هذه هي الدمامل الخاصة بك.
I described the look on your face perfectly.
وصفت المظهر على وجهك تماما.
- My gosh. - But this is too ugly.
- يا إلهي. - لكن هذا قبيح للغاية.
Seriously, it looks the same.
على محمل الجد ، يبدو نفس الشيء.
- This is hyperrealism. - This is just you.
- هذا هو واقعية مفرطة. - هذا فقط أنت.
- Take this. - Who do you think will notice it?
- خذ هذا. - من برأيك سيلاحظ ذلك؟
- Father. - They're here.
- أب. - هم هنا.
- My gosh. - Hey.
- يا إلهي. - يا.
(The next family members of the Yu Family appear.)
(يظهر أفراد عائلة عائلة Yu القادم.)
(The first child of the Yu Family, Seok Sam)
(أول طفل لعائلة يو ، سوك سام)
- Father. - Are you a trot singer?
- أب. - هل أنت مغني هروب؟
A "Show Me the Money" contestant? What are you?
متسابق "أرني المال"؟ ماذا انت
Goodness, Father.
الخير يا أبي.
- Goodness, my daughter-in-law. - Goodness, Father.
-الخير ، ابنتي. - الخير ، الأب.
- Father.
- أب. - أب.
She's the one...
هي واحدة ...
- She's the one I told you about. - Father.
- إنها التي أخبرتك عنها. - أب.
- She's my babe. - Is this a hairdryer?
- إنها طفلتي. - هل هذا مجفف شعر؟
- It's just too hot in here.
- الجو حار جدًا هنا. - هل هذا مجفف شعر؟
- It's too hot. - My darling.
- الجو حار جدا. - يا عزيزى.
I told you I would bring a fantastic bride for me.
قلت لك إنني سأحضر عروسًا رائعة لي.
- No, you two are already married. - We are already married.
- لا ، أنتما متزوجان بالفعل. - نحن متزوجون بالفعل.
- We are married? - You are.
- نحن متزوجون؟ - أنت.
- So we're already married. - She's my first daughter-in-law.
- لذلك نحن متزوجون بالفعل. -إنها ابنتي الأولى.
She's my daughter-in-law.
إنها ابنتي.
- You have 3 children. - He's got 3 children.
- لديك 3 أطفال. - لديه 3 أطفال.
- First, second, and third.
- الأول والثاني والثالث. - الأول والثاني والثالث.
- And you're the father. - Right.
- وأنت الأب. - يمين.
And you are my daughter-in-law.
وأنت ابنتي.
- And I'm the biggest. - Right.
- وأنا الأكبر. - يمين.
Are you a trot singer? "Show Me the Money" contestant?
هل أنت مغني تروت؟ "أرني المال" المتسابق؟
- What are you? - Seok Sam.
- ماذا أنت؟ - سوك سام.
- Yes? - What are you?
- نعم؟ - ماذا أنت؟
- Isn't he a painter... - I...
- أليس رسامًا ... - أنا ...
Before you knew it,
قبل أن تعرف ذلك ،
I made it big.
لقد جعلتها كبيرة.
I made it big by discovering a gold mine.
لقد جعلتها كبيرة من خلال اكتشاف منجم ذهبي.
- It's complicated. - Yes.
- إنه معقد. - نعم.
- I didn't tell you, did I? - You didn't.
- لم أخبرك ، أليس كذلك؟ - لم تفعل.
- But look, Seok Sam. - What is it?
- لكن انظر ، سوك سام. - ما هذا؟
You are the son, yet you said, "I didn't tell you, did I?"
أنت الابن ، ومع ذلك قلت ، "لم أخبرك ، أليس كذلك؟"
Where are your manners?
أين آدابك؟
- And you even pointed at him. - Mind your manners.
- حتى أشارت إليه. - مانع من آدابك.
That's too rude.
هذا وقح للغاية.
How dare you act so rudely to your father?
كيف تجرؤ على التصرف بوقاحة لأبيك؟
- You are a rude boy. - Dad.
- أنت فتى وقح. - أب.
You didn't raise me that way.
أنت لم ترفعني بهذه الطريقة.
Did you just touch Dad's cheek?
هل لم تلمس خد أبي فقط؟
When I was little... Honey.
عندما كنت صغيرا ... عزيزتي.
- When I was little... - You are treating me...
- عندما كنت صغيرًا ... - أنت تعاملني ...
- "Honey!" - he was like a friend.
- "عسل!" - كان مثل صديق.
- Come here. - Father, I'm a guest, you know.
- تعال الى هنا. - الأب ، أنا ضيف ، كما تعلم.
- Hey! - How can you be...
- يا! - كيف يمكنك أن تكون ...
What?
ماذا؟
(What did you just do to my husband?)
(ماذا فعلت للتو لزوجي؟)
- How dare you treat your father... - What's going on?
- كيف تجرؤ على التعامل مع والدك ... - ماذا يحدث؟
- Hey! What's the problem, Father? - I...
- يا! ما هي المشكلة يا أبي؟ - أنا...
- I just... - What's the matter?
- أنا فقط ... - ما الأمر؟
(A wife fiercely guarding her husband)
(زوجة تحرس زوجها بشدة)
- What are you doing to my husband? - I...
- ماذا تفعل لزوجي؟ - أنا...
I...
أنا...
Wait.
انتظر.
- Don't do that to my husband. - Are you a gangster or what?
- لا تفعل ذلك لزوجي. - هل أنت رجل عصابات أم ماذا؟
- Honey. - I'm the daughter-in-law.
- عسل. -أنا ابنة زوجها.
- Honey, he hit me. - Darling daughter-in-law.
- عزيزتي ، ضربني. -ابنة حبيبي.
- Honey, what's going on? - Wait.
- عزيزتي ، ماذا يحدث؟ - انتظر.
- Honey. - What's going on?
- عسل. - ماذا يحدث هنا؟
- Where's my welcome watermelon? - And look.
- أين هو البطيخ الترحيبي؟ - وانظر.
"Where's your welcome watermelon?"
"أين هو البطيخ مرحب به؟"
Darling daughter-in-law.
ابنة حبيبي.
By the way, the carpet is getting flattened.
بالمناسبة ، يتم تسوية السجادة.
Her shoe imprints are pretty deep.
بصمات حذاءها عميقة جدا.
I apologize.
أنا أعتذر.
Those high heels!
تلك الكعب العالي!
- My feet really hurt. - Are your feet all right?
- قدمي تؤلمني حقًا. - هل قدميك كل الحق؟
- I'm okay. - The heels might break.
- أنا بخير. - قد ينكسر الكعب.
Honey, this is my family.
عزيزتي ، هذه هي عائلتي.
- What's up with this family? - We are a family of artists.
- ما الأمر مع هذه العائلة؟ - نحن عائلة من الفنانين.
- You are in the arts. - He draws and paints.
- أنت في الفنون. - يرسم ويرسم.
- I told you about him. - I draw.
- أخبرتك عنه. - أرسم.
Should I draw you?
هل يجب أن أرسمك؟
- Draw my sister-in-law. - Come, honey.
-ارسم أختي. - تعال يا عزيزتي.
- To celebrate her first visit, - My sister-in-law.
- للاحتفال بزيارتها الأولى ،- أختي.
- I should draw her. - Wait.
- يجب أن أرسمها. - انتظر.
- Darling. - Yes.
- محبوب. - نعم.
I draw what I see.
أرسم ما أراه.
- I am a hyperrealist artist. - Father is...
- أنا فنان واقعية. - الأب ...
- Father is a famous artist. - Father.
- الأب هو فنان مشهور. - أب.
- Isn't she too big? - He's...
- أليس كذلك؟ - هو ...
(Huge)
(ضخم)
She's too big.
إنها كبيرة جدًا.
- You swung your arm like this. - No.
- قمت بتأجيل ذراعك مثل هذا. - لا.
- My goodness. - It's hyperrealistic.
- يا إلهي. - إنه مفرط الواقعية.
(Fearless strokes)
(السكتات الدماغية بلا خوف)
Dad, you are...
أبي ، أنت ...
brave.
شجاع.
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
Dad, you are...
أبي ، أنت ...
His art doesn't take long.
فنه لا يستغرق وقتًا طويلاً.
- Can I see? - I'm a hyperrealistic artist.
- هل بإمكاني رؤية ذلك؟ - أنا فنان واقعية.
Here.
هنا.
Hey, mister.
مهلا ، سيد.
(In disbelief.)
(في الكفر.)
She called him "mister."
دعته "سيد".
- Her mouth is so small. - It's...
- فمها صغير جدا. - إنه...
She looks just like this.
انها تبدو مثل هذا تماما.
- She looks just like this. - Wait.
- تبدو هكذا تماما. - انتظر.
But there is no mouth. How can I eat?
ولكن لا يوجد فم. كيف يمكنني أن آكل؟
- Dad. - She looks like this.
- أب. - تبدو هكذا.
She looks too old.
تبدو قديمة جدا.
- She looks just like this. - My honey is cute.
- تبدو هكذا تماما. - عسلي لطيف.
- I'm not your daughter-in-law. - What?
-أنا لست ابنتك. - ماذا؟
- My feet hurt too much. - Honey, are you all right?
- قدمي تؤلمني كثيرا. - عزيزتي ، هل أنت بخير؟
I'm not used to wearing high heels.
أنا لست معتادًا على ارتداء الكعب العالي.
Honey, are you okay?
عزيزتي ، هل أنت بخير؟
- Honey. - How...
- عسل. - كيف...
- Her feet can't breathe. - By the way,
- قدميها لا يمكن أن تتنفس. - بالمناسبة،
her shoes are crying.
حذائها تبكي.
- It's crying for help. - Her shoes are crying.
- إنه يبكي طلبًا للمساعدة. - حذائها تبكي.
- Honey, your feet are bigger. - Honey.
- عسل ، قدميك أكبر. - عسل.
You're not supposed to say that, honey.
ليس من المفترض أن تقول ذلك يا عزيزتي.
Honey.
عسل.
(Desperate to make people laugh, he puts on his wife's shoes.)
(يائسة لجعل الناس يضحكون ، يضع أحذية زوجته.)
You humiliated me.
أنت مهينة لي.
- What happened? - Why did you do it?
- ماذا حدث؟ - لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
It's too big, honey.
إنه كبير جدًا يا عزيزتي.
What's your shoe size?
ما هو حجم حذائك؟
- I wear a size 10.5. - Really?
- أرتدي حجم 10.5. - حقًا؟
- I wear a size 9. - Her feet are bigger than mine.
- أرتدي حجم 9. - قدميها أكبر من لي.
- I sometimes wear a size 12. - Right.
- أحيانًا أرتدي حجمًا 12. - صحيح.
Honey, it's okay. You can stay down.
عزيزتي ، لا بأس. يمكنك البقاء أسفل.
- Okay. I'm okay, honey. - I will help you.
- تمام. أنا بخير يا عزيزتي. - سوف أساعدك.
(The Kims are looking at the drawing.)
(كيمز ينظرون إلى الرسم.)
- I know him.
- أنا أعرفه. - أنا أعرفه.
I know him.
أنا أعرفه.
(He drew Grasshopper.)
(وجه جراد.)
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Father draws really well.
الأب يرسم جيدًا حقًا.
- Of course. - He draws really well.
- بالطبع. - انه يرسم جيدا حقا.
Stop drawing, Father.
توقف عن الرسم ، أيها الأب.
No, Father. You're great.
لا ، الأب. أنت عظيم.
Father.
أب.
- You're here.
- أنت هنا. - أنت هنا.
- It's nice to meet you, Father. - Ji Hyo.
- من الجيد مقابلتك يا أبي. - جي هيو.
What?
ماذا؟
(He bows down right away.)
(ينحني على الفور.)
- Father. - Who is he?
- أب. - من هو؟
He's my fiancé.
إنه خطيبتي.
- What? - Gosh.
- ماذا؟ - يا إلهي.
I am Ji Hyo's boyfriend, Shindong.
أنا صديق جي هيو ، شيندونغ.
You should say you're my fiancé now.
يجب أن تقول أنك خطيبتي الآن.
- Wait. - Right.
- انتظر. - يمين.
I am her fiancé.
أنا خطيبها.
- You're really getting married? - Yes.
- هل تتزوج حقًا؟ - نعم.
- Wait. - We're engaged.
- انتظر. - نحن متورطون.
- Finally, we are tying the knot. - Darling.
- أخيرًا ، نحن نربط العقدة. - محبوب.
What?
ماذا؟
You're really getting married?
هل تتزوج حقًا؟
- Wait. - We're engaged.
- انتظر. - نحن متورطون.
Finally, we are tying the knot.
أخيرًا ، نحن نربط العقدة.
- You! - She's older.
- أنت! - إنها أكبر سنا.
- Are you older? - What?
- هل أنت أكبر سنا؟ - ماذا؟
I only go for older ladies.
أنا فقط أذهب للسيدات الأكبر سنا.
- Shindong. - Yes.
- شيندونغ. - نعم.
- You... - Ji Hyo's not divorced yet.
- أنت ... - جي هيو لم يطلق بعد.
(Ji Hyo's not divorced yet.)
(جي هيو لم يطلق بعد.)
What?
ماذا؟
You. - Why didn't you... - Are you going to be okay?
أنت. - لماذا لم تكن ... - هل ستكون بخير؟
tell me such a secret?
قل لي هذا السر؟
Why didn't you tell him about your past?
لماذا لم تخبره عن ماضيك؟
- It's all right, Father. - How can you...
- كل شيء على ما يرام يا أبي. - كيف يمكنك ...
- reveal your daughter's past? - It's all right...
- تكشف ماضي ابنتك؟ - كل شيء على ما يرام...
- because I have a past too. - Really?
- لأن لدي ماضي أيضًا. - حقًا؟
What did you do?
ماذا فعلت؟
- Hey! - I've been divorced too.
- يا! - لقد طلقت أيضًا.
- Right.
- يمين. - يمين.
So it's okay.
لذلك لا بأس.
Weren't you supposed to get married?
ألم يكن من المفترض أن تتزوج؟
- I failed. - It's all right.
- فشلت. - كل شيء على ما يرام.
We both have been hurt, so we decided to embrace each other.
كلانا أصيبنا ، لذلك قررنا احتضان بعضنا البعض.
- Right. - Right. We wish you good luck.
- يمين. - يمين. نتمنى لكم حظا سعيدا.
- Good luck. - Please give us your blessing.
- حظ سعيد. - من فضلك أعطنا نعمة.
- But to join my family, - Yes?
- ولكن للانضمام إلى عائلتي ، - نعم؟
you need to be athletic.
يجب أن تكون رياضيًا.
- You can't be like that. - Athletic?
- لا يمكنك أن تكون هكذا. - رياضي؟
- I am athletic. - You are?
- أنا رياضي. - أنت؟
- I can do a breakfall. - Nice.
- يمكنني القيام بتقسيم. - لطيف - جيد.
- A breakfall?
- استراحة؟ - استراحة؟
Here?
هنا؟
Stop it.
أوقفه.
Do you want to see a breakfall?
هل تريد أن ترى فاصلًا؟
- Nice. - A breakfall?
- لطيف - جيد. - استراحة؟
- Here. - Don't do it.
- هنا. - لا تفعل ذلك.
He's good.
إنه جيد.
(He's heavy but agile!)
(إنه ثقيل ولكنه رشيق!)
- That was smooth. - Smooth.
- كان ذلك سلسًا. - سلس.
- So smooth. - Don't do it.
- سلس جدا. - لا تفعل ذلك.
- Look.
- لا تفعل ذلك. - ينظر.
(Landing lightly)
(الهبوط برفق)
So smooth.
سلس جدا.
- So smooth. - When I was little...
- سلس جدا. - عندما كنت صغيرا ...
- You could do this? - My goodness, Shindong.
- هل يمكن أن تفعل هذا؟ - يا إلهي ، شيندونغ.
- He's so good - I used to do judo.
- إنه جيد جدًا - اعتدت أن أفعل الجودو.
- You could do this? - Yes.
- هل يمكن أن تفعل هذا؟ - نعم.
- When you were doing this, - You are amazing.
- عندما كنت تفعل هذا ، - أنت مدهش.
- you were very bouncy. - Very smooth.
- كنت نطاط جدا. - سلس جدا.
I am very smooth.
أنا ناعم جدا.
- So sexy! - He can move.
- مثير جدا! - يمكنه التحرك.
Father!
أب!
My youngest is...
أصغرهم ...
- Goodness.
- الخير. - الخير.
- Father. - Our cutie pie is here.
- أب. - فطيرة كتي لدينا هنا.
- Youngest. - Pumpkin.
- أصغر. - اليقطين.
(The youngest Kim, Jang Hoon)
(أصغر كيم ، جانغ هون)
The youngest is...
الأصغر سنا ...
Why do we always gather outside under the hot sun?
لماذا نتجمع دائمًا في الخارج تحت أشعة الشمس الحارة؟
- He's the youngest? - We could...
- إنه الأصغر؟ - يمكننا ...
- Jang Hoon. - stay inside where it's cool.
- جانج هون. - ابق في الداخل حيث يكون الجو باردا.
- He's the youngest? - Wait.
- إنه الأصغر؟ - انتظر.
We could stay inside where it's cool.
يمكن أن نبقى في الداخل حيث يكون الأمر رائعًا.
You should say hi to your father first.
يجب أن تقول مرحبًا لأبيك أولاً.
We met earlier, Father.
التقينا في وقت سابق ، الأب.
You should still say hi, boy.
لا يزال يتعين عليك أن تقول مرحبا يا فتى.
I haven't seen this pumpkin in a while.
لم أر هذا اليقطين منذ فترة.
(Big brother steps in to keep the youngest in line.)
(يخطو الأخ الأكبر للحفاظ على أصغرهم في الخط.)
- Boys. - You cutie pie!
- الأولاد. - أنت كتي فطيرة!
I've missed you.
لقد اشتقت لك.
Hey!
يا!
(Groaning)
(يئن)
(The younger brother, 1.5x bigger than his brother, rebels)
(الأخ الأصغر ، 1.5x أكبر من شقيقه ، المتمردين)
How dare you do that to your big brother?
كيف تجرؤ على فعل ذلك لأخيك الكبير؟
What are you doing to our big brother?
ماذا تفعل لأخينا الكبير؟
- You had a giant younger brother? - I haven't been on TV...
- كان لديك شقيق أصغر عملاق؟ - لم أكن على شاشة التلفزيون ...
with my brothers in a while.
مع إخواني منذ فترة.
(The Kim family is cursed to grow with every birth.)
(عائلة كيم لعن لتنمو مع كل ولادة.)
It's hot today.
الجو حار اليوم.
Should we not get on each other's nerves?
ألا يجب أن نتعرف على أعصاب بعضنا البعض؟
Let's keep a distance since it's hot.
دعونا نبقى مسافة لأن الجو حار.
(Let's keep a distance since it's hot.)
(دعونا نبقى مسافة لأنه ساخن.)
You're acting like a star.
أنت تتصرف مثل النجم.
- Jang Hoon. - Jang Hoon is...
- جانج هون. - جانج هون ...
Look at our youngest.
انظر إلى أصغرنا.
- Adore him. - Don't annoy him.
- أعشقه. - لا تزعجه.
Jang Hoon, why are you standing so far away?
جانغ هون ، لماذا تقف بعيدًا جدًا؟
- He's moving into the shade. - It's hot to be close to us.
- انه ينتقل إلى الظل. - الجو حار أن نكون قريبًا منا.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
- Come near. - Go to the center.
- تقترب. - اذهب إلى المركز.
It's just that it's surprisingly hot.
إنه أمر ساخن بشكل مدهش.
- He got even taller. - Why did you...
- حصل على أطول. - لماذا فعلت ...
- put on a sweater then? - Why won't you listen to us?
- وضعت على سترة بعد ذلك؟ - لماذا لا تستمع إلينا؟
I thought we were going to be inside.
اعتقدت أننا سنكون في الداخل.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
- I will... - Father drew...
- سأفعل ... - الأب درو ...
- He's really good. - It's been a while.
- إنه جيد حقًا. - لقد مرت فترة.
I drew a little something.
لقد رسمت شيئًا صغيرًا.
- He looks familiar. - He...
- يبدو مألوفا. - هو...
I am an artist, you know.
أنا فنان ، كما تعلم.
And you all have my artistic talent.
وللكم جميعًا موهبتي الفنية.
I actually did well that time.
لقد فعلت ذلك بشكل جيد في ذلك الوقت.
Jang Hoon, why did you bother to bring an umbrella?
جانغ هون ، لماذا عناء إدخال مظلة؟
I know it's hot, but still.
أعلم أنه ساخن ، لكن لا يزال.
Why would you bring an umbrella of your own?
لماذا تحضر مظلة خاصة بك؟
(The huge parasol looks like an umbrella in his hand.)
(يبدو المظلة الضخمة مظلة في يده.)
It's nice to see someone really tall.
من الجيد أن ترى شخصًا طويلًا حقًا.
- It's hot. - Yes.
- الطقس حار. - نعم.
The sun is strong.
الشمس قوية.
- Where? - I saw a really tall boy earlier.
- أين؟ - رأيت فتى طويل القامة حقا في وقت سابق.
The really tall boy...
الفتى طويل القامة ...
- is looking very upset. - Right.
- يبدو مستاء جدا. - يمين.
He's wiping sweat.
إنه يمسح العرق.
- Tell him to come here. - He's there?
- أخبره أن يأتي إلى هنا. - هو هناك؟
- Is he outside? - I guess our family is better.
- هل هو في الخارج؟ - أعتقد أن عائلتنا أفضل.
- At least we're inside. - I know.
- على الأقل نحن في الداخل. - أنا أعرف.
They are our rivals.
هم منافسينا.
They are just one rude family.
هم مجرد عائلة وقحة.
A family with no class.
عائلة بدون فصل.
- Okay! - What? They are here.
- تمام! - ماذا؟ هم هنا.
- What?
- ماذا؟ - ماذا؟
- It's hot. - Why did you put us outside?
- الطقس حار. - لماذا وضعتنا في الخارج؟
- Look.
- ينظر. - ينظر.
- You rude... - You nobodies.
- أنت وقح ... - أيها النوب.
- You rude family. - Gosh.
- أنت عائلة وقحة. - يا إلهي.
You nobodies.
أيها النبلاء.
- Rude? - Your family is...
- غير مهذب؟ - عائلتك ...
- How dare you? - the uneducated and cheap one.
- كيف تجرؤ عليك؟ - غير متعلم ورخيص.
- You are the rude ones. - How dare you?
- أنت وقح. - كيف تجرؤ عليك؟
- You have no class. - Gosh.
- ليس لديك فصل. - يا إلهي.
- Goodness. - You are the family with no class.
- الخير. - أنت الأسرة التي لا تحتوي على فصل.
You're wearing that cliché apron just because you're an artist.
أنت ترتدي هذا المئزر كليشيهات لمجرد أنك فنان.
- Cliché?
- صورة؟ - صورة؟
Is he a Boy Scout or what?
هل هو صبي الكشافة أم ماذا؟
- Gosh, you. - Look at that sweat.
- يا إلهي ، أنت. - انظر إلى هذا العرق.
- Goodness. - Look at him sweating.
- الخير. - انظر إليه بالتعرق.
He's sweating so much.
انه يتعرق كثيرا.
It's...
إنه...
- He's so tall. - I'm already sweating too.
- إنه طويل جدًا. - أنا بالفعل أتعرق أيضًا.
Why are you sweating so much?
لماذا تعرق كثيرا؟
I've seen them a lot recently.
لقد رأيتهم كثيرًا مؤخرًا.
In the recent episodes,
في الحلقات الأخيرة ،
- they didn't do this. Why... - A role play?
- لم يفعلوا هذا. لماذا ... - لعب الأدوار؟
- We sometimes do this. - What's up with the role play?
- نحن في بعض الأحيان نفعل هذا. - ما الأمر مع لعب الأدوار؟
We do a mix of things.
نحن نفعل مزيج من الأشياء.
- A mix of things. - Hey, Youngest!
- مزيج من الأشياء. - مهلا ، أصغر!
(At Yu's, his whining won't work.)
(في يو ، لن يعمل أنينه.)
- Hey, Youngest! - Yes.
- مهلا ، أصغر! - نعم.
You standing in the middle makes it look like we're swearing.
أنت تقف في الوسط تجعل الأمر يبدو وكأننا نقسم.
(Standing tall)
(يقف طويل القامة)
You're sticking out alone.
أنت تخرج بمفردك.
Go to the side!
اذهب إلى الجانب!
Father, I haven't been on this show in a while.
أيها الأب ، لم أكن في هذا العرض منذ فترة.
He's your son?
هو ابنك؟
- He's his son?
- هو ابنه؟ - هو ابنه؟
- He's the youngest. - He's our little brother.
- إنه الأصغر. - إنه شقيقنا الصغير.
He's our little brother.
إنه شقيقنا الصغير.
(He finds something.)
(يجد شيئًا.)
She's born to be the center figure.
ولدت لتكون شخصية المركز.
No matter where she is, she stands in the center.
بغض النظر عن مكانها ، فإنها تقف في الوسط.
She's the one who brings in the viewer rating.
إنها الشخص الذي يجلب تصنيف المشاهد.
- I am the one. - She makes people see it.
- أنا واحد. - تجعل الناس يرون ذلك.
- She does. - Do you know why...
- هي تفعل. - هل تعرف لماذا ...
- she's next to my little brother? - Why?
- هي بجانب أخي الصغير؟ - لماذا؟
To look pretty.
لتبدو جميلة.
- To look petite and precious. - She's good at positioning.
- لتبدو صغيرة وثمن. - إنها جيدة في المواقع.
I'm going to stick to you.
سألتزم بك.
- She's petite and precious. - Is that why you're here?
- إنها صغيرة وثمينة. - هل هذا لماذا أنت هنا؟
You usually stand there.
عادة ما تقف هناك.
- You're making her look pretty. - She's the pocket girl.
- أنت تجعلها تبدو جميلة. - إنها فتاة الجيب.
(She can be the pocket girl only today.)
(يمكن أن تكون فتاة الجيب فقط اليوم.)
Who's the man there?
من هو الرجل هناك؟
- Me? - Who?
- أنا؟ - من؟
- I'm a rich man. - Going on "Show Me the Money?"
- أنا رجل ثري. - الذهاب "أرني المال؟"
- But look.
- أنا رجل ثري. - لكن انظر.
You look too cheap...
تبدين رخيصة جدا ...
- to be a rich man. - Hey!
- أن تكون رجل ثري. - يا!
(He looks too cheap to be a rich man.)
(يبدو رخيصًا جدًا ليكون رجلاً ثريًا.)
I don't look as cheap as you do.
لا أبدو رخيصة كما تفعل.
- Youngest. - You little man.
- أصغر. - يا رجل صغير.
Fake jewelry will make your allergies explode.
المجوهرات المزيفة ستجعل الحساسية الخاصة بك تنفجر.
- How dare you? - Aren't you the son?
- كيف تجرؤ عليك؟ - ألست الابن؟
(The two families fight.)
(تقاتل العائلتان.)
How dare you fight my father?
كيف تجرؤ على محاربة والدي؟
- What are you doing? - He's the father?
- ماذا تفعل؟ - هو الأب؟
- I'm the father. - He's the father.
- أنا الأب. - إنه الأب.
- He is? - What kind of a family is this?
- هو؟ - أي نوع من الأسرة هذا؟
I'm the daughter-in-law.
أنا ابنة زوجها.
(The daughter-in-law joins in.)
(تنضم ابنة زوجها.)
(Flinching)
(متهور)
- That was intimidating. - Baby brother!
- كان ذلك مخيفًا. - أخي طفل!
- Thank you, honey. - No way.
- شكرا لك عزيزي. - مستحيل.
- Honey, let me handle this. - Baby brother.
- عزيزتي ، دعني أتعامل مع هذا. - أخي طفل.
Jang Hoon, as the youngest, you should defend the family.
جانغ هون ، باعتباره الأصغر سنا ، يجب عليك الدفاع عن الأسرة.
- What a bunch of jerks! - Are you kidding me?
- يا لها من حفنة من الهزات! - هل تمزح معي؟
- How dare you? - You wait and see.
- كيف تجرؤ عليك؟ - أنت تنتظر وترى.
- Shindong, Jang Hoon, - Unbelievable.
- Shindong ، Jang Hoon ، - لا تصدق.
and Gi Ru are here...
و GI RU هنا ...
as our guests today.
كضيوفنا اليوم.
- What's this? - No way.
- ما هذا؟ - مستحيل.
"Baebully Hills" airing on Disney?
"بايبللي هيلز" تبث على ديزني؟
- What's this? - "Baebully Hills."
- ما هذا؟ - "تلال بيبلي".
- "Baebully Hills?" - On August 24.
- "بايبللي هيلز؟" - في 24 أغسطس.
It's the second season of "Meokjjippa."
إنه الموسم الثاني من "Meokjjippa".
- You all know "Meokjjippa." - Of course.
- تعرفون جميعا "meokjjippa". - بالطبع.
- It's a remake of that show. - I see.
- إنه طبعة جديدة من هذا العرض. - أرى.
We're aliens from space called Baebullians.
نحن الأجانب من الفضاء يسمى baebullians.
(Embarrassed)
(مُحرَج)
We're aliens.
نحن الأجانب.
- We're Baebullians... - Aliens?
- نحن baebullians ... - الأجانب؟
who have come to attack Earth.
الذين جاءوا لمهاجمة الأرض.
- Are you aliens? - That's right.
- هل أنت أجانب؟ - هذا صحيح.
(They have to consume plenty of calories...)
(عليهم أن يستهلكوا الكثير من السعرات الحرارية ...)
(to make it back to their home star.)
(للعودة إلى نجمهم المحلي.)
(Seo Jang Hoon)
(سيو جانغ هون)
(Shindong)
(شيندونغ)
(A show featuring Baebullians who must eat to survive)
(عرض يضم baebullians الذين يجب أن يأكلوا للبقاء على قيد الحياة)
(Shin Gi Ru)
(شين جي رو)
("Baebully Hills")
("بايبلي هيلز")
"Baebully Hills" will premiere on August 24.
"Baebully Hills" سيتم عرضها في 24 أغسطس.
That sounds like fun!
هذا يبدو وكأنه متعة!
- Show your support. - Good luck.
- أظهر دعمك. - حظ سعيد.
Good luck.
حظ سعيد.
This is the Between Masterpiece and Failure Race.
هذا هو بين تحفة وسباق الفشل.
The rival artist families...
العائلات الفنان المنافسة ...
- will face off with their drawings. - Really?
- سوف يواجه رسوماتهم. - حقًا؟
- This will be easy. - We'll see which family...
- سيكون هذا سهلاً. - سنرى أي عائلة ...
comes out on top.
يخرج على القمة.
Each of your drawings...
كل من رسوماتك ...
will be evaluated in a unique way...
سيتم تقييمها بطريقة فريدة من نوعها ...
to determine its price.
لتحديد سعره.
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
The family whose drawings have the higher total value...
العائلة التي لها رسوماتها أعلى القيمة الإجمالية ...
will win.
سوف يفوز.
- Okay! - Okay.
- تمام! - تمام.
The father of the winning family...
والد العائلة الفائزة ...
will be awarded a prize with no risk of penalty.
سيتم منح جائزة دون أي خطر.
- Just the father? - The family members...
- فقط الآب؟ - أفراد الأسرة ...
whose drawings have the two highest values...
رسوماتها لها أعلى قيمتين ...
will win a prize.
سيفوز بجائزة.
The one with the lowest value will receive a penalty.
واحد مع أدنى قيمة سوف تحصل على ركلة جزاء.
- But I'm bad at drawing. - As for the losing team,
- لكنني سيء في الرسم. - بالنسبة للفريق الخاسر ،
the father will receive a penalty, no matter what.
سوف يتلقى الأب ركلة جزاء ، بغض النظر عن ماذا.
Aside from those with the two highest-valued drawings,
بصرف النظر عن أولئك الذين لديهم رسومات ذات قيمة أعلى ،
the others will receive a penalty.
سوف يتلقى الآخرون عقوبة.
- The losing team... - I should wreak havoc.
- الفريق الخاسر ... - يجب أن أؤدي إلى الخراب.
Even if you lose,
حتى لو خسرت ،
- you won't receive a penalty... - With the two highest values.
- لن تتلقى ركلة جزاء ... - مع أعلى قيمتين.
if your family's drawing is pricier.
إذا كان رسم عائلتك أكثر أهمية.
What about those who are bad at drawing?
ماذا عن أولئك الذين هم سيئون في الرسم؟
- Just work hard on it, Jang Hoon. - You see...
- فقط اعمل بجد عليه ، يانغ هون. - هل ترى...
Stop whining.
توقف عن الأنين.
- You see, it's like this. - Seriously?
- كما ترى ، هذا مثل هذا. - بجد؟
The evaluation of the drawings will go beyond techniques.
سوف يتجاوز تقييم الرسومات التقنيات.
Am I not allowed to ask that?
هل لا يُسمح لي أن أسأل ذلك؟
They will consider your drawing skills.
سوف ينظرون في مهارات الرسم الخاصة بك.
- But... - Why are you scolding my brother?
- لكن ... - لماذا توبخ أخي؟
- Hold on. What was that? - Some people can't draw.
- يتمسك. ماذا كان هذا؟ - بعض الناس لا يستطيعون الرسم.
- That's my son you're scolding.
- هذا ابني أنت توبيخ. - بعض الناس لا يستطيعون الرسم.
That's my son you're scolding.
هذا ابني أنت توبيخ.
- Some people can't draw. - Jang Hoon, it's okay.
- بعض الناس لا يستطيعون الرسم. - جانغ هون ، لا بأس.
- What was that? - What's wrong with your family?
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - ما الخطأ في عائلتك؟
Father, step aside.
الأب ، تنحى جانبا.
(The teto daughter-in-law returns to the mound.)
(تعود زوجة Teto ابنة إلى التل.)
- What's with her? - She's intimidating for sure.
- ماذا معها؟ - إنها تخويف بالتأكيد.
Just know that she is not as strong as she looks.
فقط اعلم أنها ليست قوية كما تبدو.
- She may wear 300mm shoes, - Really?
- قد ترتدي أحذية 300 مم ، - حقا؟
- but she's weak. - Your shoe size is 300mm?
- لكنها ضعيفة. - حجم حذائك 300 مم؟
I'll win the drawing contest.
سأربح في مسابقة الرسم.
- You'll win with your drawing? - With her drawing.
- ستربح مع الرسم الخاص بك؟ - مع رسمها.
By playing today's games,
من خلال لعب ألعاب اليوم ،
you'll gain benefits...
ستحصل على فوائد ...
that let you boost...
هذا يتيح لك تعزيز ...
- Of course. - the price of your drawings,
- بالطبع. - سعر رسوماتك ،
- I knew it. - regardless of your talent.
- كنت أعرف. - بغض النظر عن موهبتك.
You'll regroup after changing into matching clothes.
سوف تعيد تجميع صفوفها بعد التغيير إلى مطابقة الملابس.
- Okay! - Let's go.
- تمام! - دعنا نذهب.
Our family has always had class.
كان لدى عائلتنا دائمًا الفصل.
My style is hyperrealism.
أسلوبي هو واقعية.
I'm glad our dad...
أنا سعيد والدنا ...
quit being a comedian and chose to draw.
استقال كونه ممثل كوميدي واختار الرسم.
- Let's go. - Sure.
- دعنا نذهب. - بالتأكيد.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Okay! Goodness!
تمام! يا إلهي!
(What shocked the members?)
(ما الذي صدم الأعضاء؟)
- What's that?
- ما هذا؟ - ما هذا؟
- Are you kidding me? - It's fried chicken.
- هل تمزح معي؟ - إنه دجاج مقلي.
(The Baebullians react to the fried chicken.)
(يتفاعل البوليانز مع الدجاج المقلي.)
- It's fried chicken. - Fried chicken.
- إنه دجاج مقلي. - الدجاج المقلي.
- No way. - I can't believe it.
- مستحيل. - لا أستطيع أن أصدق ذلك.
It's my favorite brand.
إنها علامتي التجارية المفضلة.
- No way. It's fried chicken. - It's fried chicken.
- مستحيل. إنه دجاج مقلي. - إنه دجاج مقلي.
Why are we getting fried chicken?
لماذا نحصل على الدجاج المقلي؟
- What's that? - You can't create art...
- ما هذا؟ - لا يمكنك إنشاء الفن ...
on an empty stomach,
على معدة فارغة ،
so you'll eat before we begin the race.
لذلك سوف تأكل قبل أن نبدأ السباق.
(Recharging their souls before letting their artistry flow)
(إعادة شحن أرواحهم قبل السماح لتدفق فنيهم)
- That must be the sauce. - Look at this.
- يجب أن تكون الصلصة. - انظر إلى هذا.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
- Hold on. - This looks delicious.
- يتمسك. - هذا يبدو لذيذ.
- No way. - Can you believe it?
- مستحيل. - هل تصدق ذلك؟
I taste pepper.
أنا أتذوق الفلفل.
That tastes good.
هذا طعم جيد.
What? No way.
ماذا؟ مستحيل.
That wasn't a normal crunch. It was more like a crack.
لم يكن ذلك أزمة طبيعية. كان أشبه الكراك.
- Crack? - The batter makes a cracking sound.
- كسر؟ - الخليط يجعل صوت تكسير.
- A crack? - Yes. Try one.
- صدع؟ - نعم. جرب واحد.
- I haven't had breakfast. - No way.
- لم أتناول وجبة الإفطار. - مستحيل.
(Gi Ru's busy getting ready to have fried chicken.)
(Gi Ru مشغول بالاستعداد لالتقاط الدجاج المقلي.)
(Fidgeting)
(تململ)
That's for Gi Ru alone.
هذا ل GI RU وحده.
- That's hers. - I see.
- هذا هو لها. - أرى.
(Just for Gi Ru)
(فقط من أجل GI RU)
- Enjoy it all. - That's mine.
- استمتع بكل شيء. - هذا لي.
- She almost hit you. - I almost got hit.
- لقد ضربتك تقريبا. - كدت أصبت.
- Ye Eun, where are your manners? - I'm sorry.
- أيها ايون ، أين أخلاقك؟ - أنا آسف.
- Ye Eun, she's your sister-in-law. - Yes, of course.
-أيها ايون ، إنها أختك. - نعم بالطبع.
- This is for your sister-in-law. - She's your sister-in-law.
-هذا لأختك. -إنها أختك.
That's for Gi Ru alone,
هذا من أجل GI RU وحده ،
- but Ye Eun almost took one. - My sister-in-law.
- لكن أيها كاد أخذ واحدة. -أختي.
- Did you almost take hers? - Yes, and I'm sorry.
- هل أخذت راتبها تقريبا؟ - نعم ، وأنا آسف.
Give her a warning, will you? A family should function better.
أعطها تحذيرًا ، أليس كذلك؟ يجب أن تعمل الأسرة بشكل أفضل.
I'm sorry, honey.
أنا آسف يا عزيزتي.
(She takes a bite once she's kept her family in line.)
(تأخذ لدغة بمجرد أن تبقي عائلتها في خط.)
Is it delicious?
هل هو لذيذ؟
- Totally. - Isn't it super crunchy?
- تماما. - أليس كذلك مقرمشًا؟
This must be the sauce.
يجب أن تكون هذه الصلصة.
Really? Should we have some with this?
حقًا؟ هل يجب أن يكون لدينا بعض مع هذا؟
That's too much.
هذا أكثر من اللازم.
- It's really good. - Is it delicious?
- إنه جيد حقًا. - هل هو لذيذ؟
- Totally. - Isn't it super crunchy?
- تماما. - أليس كذلك مقرمشًا؟
It's more than just crunchy.
إنه أكثر من مجرد مقدد.
(Perfect for the Food Fighter)
(مثالي لمقاتل الطعام)
The sauce is delicious.
الصلصة لذيذة.
- I see. I get it now. - It's so good.
- أرى. أحصل عليه الآن. - إنه جيد جدًا.
You can enjoy it with the sauce of your choice.
يمكنك الاستمتاع بها مع الصلصة التي تختارها.
- It's crunchy. - I want the pepper sauce.
- إنه مقرمش. - أريد صلصة الفلفل.
You can enjoy it with a variety of flavors.
يمكنك الاستمتاع بها مع مجموعة متنوعة من النكهات.
You put the sauce on top like so.
تضع الصلصة على القمة مثل ذلك.
(Opening another packet)
(فتح حزمة أخرى)
(She's opening all three packets?)
(إنها تفتح جميع الحزم الثلاث؟)
- I've never had powdered sauce. - Dip it like so.
- لم يكن لدي صلصة مسحوق. - غمسها مثل ذلك.
- There must be three sauces. - That's a proper feast.
- يجب أن يكون هناك ثلاث صلصات. - هذا عيد مناسب.
- Enjoy the three sauces. - Right.
- استمتع بالصلصات الثلاث. - يمين.
- She knows her stuff. - It's like lamb skewers.
- إنها تعرف أغراضها. - إنه مثل أسياخ الخروف.
Look at Gi Ru. That's a proper feast.
انظر إلى جي رو. هذا عيد مناسب.
(Just then)
(عندها فقط)
- Goodness. - Is that a penalty?
- الخير. - هل هذه عقوبة؟
- We... - Don't they get anything to eat?
- نحن ... - ألا يحصلوا على أي شيء نأكله؟
We're the faces...
نحن الوجوه ...
of different fried chicken brands.
من مختلف العلامات التجارية الدجاج المقلي.
(They're the faces of different fried chicken brands.)
(إنها وجوه العلامات التجارية الدجاج المقلية المختلفة.)
Jang Hoon's the face of one too.
يانغ هون وجه واحد أيضا.
(There are family members who can't eat the chicken.)
(هناك أفراد الأسرة الذين لا يستطيعون تناول الدجاج.)
Honey, open wide.
عسل ، مفتوح على نطاق واسع.
I sprinkled all three types of sauce on that.
لقد رشت جميع أنواع الصلصة الثلاثة على ذلك.
- Nice. - Is that it?
- لطيف - جيد. - هل هذا هو؟
If you want a snack, have this fried chicken.
إذا كنت تريد وجبة خفيفة ، يكون هذا الدجاج المقلي.
(They all enjoy the fried chicken.)
(كلهم يستمتعون بالدجاج المقلي.)
You can enjoy it with the sauce like so.
يمكنك الاستمتاع بها مع الصلصة مثل ذلك.
- No way. - It's so good.
- مستحيل. - إنه جيد جدًا.
- It's delicious. - Isn't it amazing?
- إنه لذيذ. - أليس كذلك؟
Fried chicken is a bit too heavy to have for breakfast.
الدجاج المقلي ثقيل بعض الشيء لتناول الإفطار.
If you're almost done with your meal,
إذا كنت قد انتهيت تقريبًا من وجبتك ،
- we'll move on to the game. - Okay.
- سننتقل إلى اللعبة. - تمام.
What if some of us haven't had enough?
ماذا لو لم يكن لدى البعض منا ما يكفي؟
Gi Ru can eat three fried chickens for brunch.
يمكن لـ GI RU أن تأكل ثلاثة دجاج مقلي لتناول الغداء.
Let's move on if we've had enough.
دعنا ننتقل إذا كان لدينا ما يكفي.
- Shindong... - Stop eating, will you?
- Shindong ... - توقف عن الأكل ، أليس كذلك؟
- Shindong's a big guy. - They're removing the table.
- شيندونغ رجل كبير. - يزيلون الجدول.
(The Baebullian keeps eating until the very end.)
(يستمر Baebullian في الأكل حتى النهاية.)
Stop eating, will you?
توقف عن الأكل ، أليس كذلك؟
(Glaring)
(صارخ)
You've had enough.
كان لديك ما يكفي.
Wait.
انتظر.
(She quickly secures her Coke.)
(قامت بسرعة بتأمين فحم الكوك.)
But I want more.
لكني أريد المزيد.
They took it away without even saying anything.
أخذوها بعيدا حتى حتى قول أي شيء.
(After the feast of a breakfast that left them wanting more)
(بعد عيد الإفطار الذي تركهم يريدون المزيد)
Hold on. Two, four...
يتمسك. اثنان ، أربعة ...
They have more members.
لديهم المزيد من الأعضاء.
- Over here. Sit here, honey. - Here?
- هنا. اجلس هنا يا عزيزتي. - هنا؟
(Immersed in the skit)
(منغمس في المسرحية الهوائية)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo and Shindong sit far apart.)
(وفي الوقت نفسه ، يجلس جي هيو وشيندونغ بعيدًا.)
- You take the inner seat. - I'll sit next to Gi Ru.
- تأخذ المقعد الداخلي. - سأجلس بجانب GI RU.
Okay!
تمام!
Shindong, you really need to pick a side.
Shindong ، تحتاج حقًا إلى اختيار جانب.
Tell me about it.
أخبرني عن ذلك.
Either gain more weight or lose it.
إما أن تكتسب المزيد من الوزن أو تفقده.
- Right? - He's right.
- يمين؟ - إنه على حق.
- You look too handsome right now. - Aren't I mediocre?
- تبدو وسيمًا جدًا الآن. - أليس أنا متواضع؟
He weighs over 100kg.
يزن أكثر من 100 كجم.
- He can't. - No way.
- لا يستطيع. - مستحيل.
- What do you mean? - How can he be 100kg?
- ماذا تقصد؟ - كيف يمكن أن يكون 100 كجم؟
- He's heavier than 100kg. - No way.
- إنه أثقل من 100 كجم. - مستحيل.
- Do you weigh over 100kg? - I'm 103kg.
- هل تزن أكثر من 100 كجم؟ - أنا 103 كجم.
Why do I feel like you're not exactly fat or slender?
لماذا أشعر أنك لست سمينًا أو نحيفًا تمامًا؟
We're nearly the same size.
نحن تقريبا بنفس الحجم.
- Exactly. - I shouldn't have been...
- بالضبط. - لا ينبغي أن أكون ...
- part of this group. - Why not?
- جزء من هذه المجموعة. - ولم لا؟
(He was robbed of his chance to talk.)
(تعرض للسرقة من فرصته للتحدث.)
(Sucking in every topic and making it about himself)
(مص في كل موضوع وجعله عن نفسه)
I'm on the slimmer side.
أنا على الجانب الأقل حجما.
- What? - No way.
- ماذا؟ - مستحيل.
- I... - You're a giant.
- أنا ... - أنت عملاق.
I'm slender.
أنا رفيع.
- Slender? - He says he's slender.
- نحيلة؟ - يقول إنه نحيف.
(Presenting himself appealingly to others)
(يقدم نفسه بجاذبية للآخرين)
Look at Gi Ru, for instance. She has a specific character.
انظر إلى GI RU ، على سبيل المثال. لديها شخصية محددة.
- Gi Ru's cute. - She's adorable.
- جي رو لطيف. - إنها رائعتين.
Gi Ru's adorable.
جي رو رائعتين.
- Absolutely. She looks like a cat. - Totally cute.
- قطعاً. انها تبدو مثل قطة. - لطيف تماما.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكون سخيفًا.
- She looks like a cat? - She looks like a cat.
- تبدو مثل قطة؟ - تبدو مثل قطة.
She's a water buffalo.
إنها جاموس ماء.
A water buffalo?
جاموس الماء؟
- One from Africa. - A buffalo.
- واحد من أفريقيا. - الجاموس.
He's known as Kim Woo Bin in "Baebully Hills."
يُعرف باسم Kim Woo Bin في "Baebully Hills".
From space...
من الفضاء ...
He's known as Kim Woo Bin.
يعرف باسم كيم وو بن.
- From space... - Kim Woo Bin?
- من الفضاء ... - كيم وو بن؟
Are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
Kim Woo Bin.
أمس بن.
- Don't you dare. - Don't irritate us.
- لا تجرؤ. - لا تهيجنا.
- Kim Woo Bin's my ideal man. - Isn't he like Mr. Bean?
- كيم وو بن هو الرجل المثالي. - أليس مثل السيد بين؟
- He's your ideal man, then. - I didn't call myself that.
- إنه الرجل المثالي ، إذن. - لم أسمي نفسي ذلك.
Kim Woo Bin, my foot.
كيم وو بن ، قدمي.
Come on. He's a taller Mr. Bean.
تعال. انه أطول السيد بين.
There's something peculiar about that family.
هناك شيء غريب عن تلك العائلة.
Jang Hoon looks like the father.
يانغ هون يشبه الأب.
- Tell me about it. - That's the vibe I'm getting.
- أخبرني عن ذلك. - هذا هو الأجواء التي أحصل عليها.
I'm 16.
أبلغ من العمر 16 عامًا.
- But... - I see.
- لكن ... - أرى.
- Are you 16? - He's still a minor.
- هل أنت 16؟ - إنه لا يزال قاصرًا.
- I said I was 16. - Let me explain the game.
- قلت أنني كنت في السادسة عشرة من عمره - اسمحوا لي أن أشرح اللعبة.
It's to determine how much time you'll get to draw.
إنه لتحديد مقدار الوقت الذي ستحصل عليه.
This is Swift Correct Answer Mode.
هذا وضع الإجابة الصحيح السريع.
- Okay. - I see.
- تمام. - أرى.
In order, each family member...
بالترتيب ، كل أحد أفراد الأسرة ...
must say three words that fit the category...
يجب أن تقول ثلاث كلمات تناسب الفئة ...
within the time limit.
في غضون الوقت الزمني.
- Three? - Yes.
- ثلاثة؟ - نعم.
- Three each. - Three each?
- ثلاثة لكل منها. - ثلاثة لكل منها؟
Three each?
ثلاثة لكل منها؟
You'll fail if you answer incorrectly...
سوف تفشل إذا أجبت بشكل غير صحيح ...
or don't say them in time.
أو لا تقلهم في الوقت المناسب.
If the other team gets it wrong,
إذا أخطأ الفريق الآخر ،
you can shoot them...
يمكنك إطلاق النار عليهم ...
- with the given water gun. - Sounds good.
- مع بندقية الماء المعطى. - ًيبدو جيدا.
Do we all get sprayed even if one person gets it wrong?
هل يتم رشنا جميعًا حتى لو أخطأ شخص ما؟
Yes. The team that gets all its family members to say...
نعم. الفريق الذي يحصل على جميع أفراد أسرته يقول ...
- the three words first will win. - Nice.
- الكلمات الثلاث أولاً ستفوز. - لطيف - جيد.
Since Team Jae Seok has five members,
منذ فريق جاي سوك لديه خمسة أعضاء ،
one will have to answer twice.
سيتعين على المرء أن يجيب مرتين.
Jae Seok, you can go twice.
جاي سوك ، يمكنك الذهاب مرتين.
I can't do that.
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
That won't be easy to do.
لن يكون من السهل القيام به.
Gi Ru, would you like go twice? Are you good at these things?
جي رو ، هل تحب الذهاب مرتين؟ هل أنت جيد في هذه الأشياء؟
- I'm terrible at playing games. - Are you?
- أنا فظيع في ممارسة الألعاب. - أنت؟
Ssaebssaeb, you'll do it.
ssaebssaeb ، سوف تفعل ذلك.
- Should I go twice at the end? - Yes.
- هل يجب أن أذهب مرتين في النهاية؟ - نعم.
- That's it. - Got it.
- هذا كل شيء. - فهمتها.
- Go first. - Should we go first?
- اذهب أولاً. - هل يجب أن نذهب أولاً؟
- Yes. - Jae Seok, will you go first?
- نعم. - جاي سوك ، هل ستذهب أولاً؟
I'll go first.
سأذهب أولاً.
Here's your keyword.
ها هي كلمتك الرئيسية.
- Okay. - We start with Jae Seok.
- تمام. - نبدأ مع جاي سوك.
Let's do this!
دعونا نفعل هذا!
Name Korean co-ed singing groups.
اسم مجموعات الغناء الكورية.
- One, two, three. - KOYOTE, the one with "Famous..."
- واحد اثنين ثلاثة. - Koyote ، الشخص مع "مشهور ..."
ALLDAY PROJECT.
مشروع Allday.
(Failed)
(فشل)
(They spray him with water as soon as he gets it wrong.)
(يرشونه بالماء بمجرد أن يخطئ.)
(Grinning from ear to ear at their own Waterbomb Festival)
(ابتسامة من الأذن إلى الأذن في مهرجان القنبلة المائية الخاصة بهم)
No hands!
لا يد!
- No hands! - Hold on.
- لا يد! - يتمسك.
- Hold on a second. - Don't cover your face.
- عقد ثانية. - لا تغطي وجهك.
- Only aim at him. - Guys.
- فقط تهدف إليه. - شباب.
- You all get sprayed. - Wait.
- يتم رش جميعكم. - انتظر.
- You should stop... - You all get sprayed.
- يجب أن تتوقف ... - يتم رشك جميعًا.
after having done enough.
بعد أن فعلت ما يكفي.
- What are you talking about? - Why did you keep shooting?
- ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ - لماذا واصلت إطلاق النار؟
Doesn't it look silly to cover your face...
ألا يبدو الأمر سخيفًا لتغطية وجهك ...
with your hands?
بيديك؟
(He nitpicks over the way Jae Seok gets shot at.)
(انه nitpicks على الطريقة التي يصيب بها جاي سوك.)
- Of course. - What are you saying?
- بالطبع. - ماذا تقول؟
- He should take it like a man. - Come on.
- يجب أن يأخذها كرجل. - تعال.
You shouldn't cover your face with your hands.
يجب ألا تغطي وجهك بيديك.
Why does Jang Hoon talk so much?
لماذا يتحدث جانغ هون كثيرا؟
That's how he is.
هكذا هو.
We can just ignore him.
يمكننا فقط تجاهله.
He does shows where he talks a lot.
إنه يظهر المكان الذي يتحدث فيه كثيرًا.
Why do you talk so much?
لماذا تتحدث كثيرا؟
- He does a lot of talk shows. - Was he always this talkative?
- يفعل الكثير من البرامج الحوارية. - هل كان دائما هذا ثرثارة؟
I do shows where I talk...
أفعل العروض أين أتحدث ...
- all day long. - His shows are like that.
- طوال اليوم. - عروضه هكذا.
Pretend you don't hear him.
تظاهر أنك لا تسمعه.
He's a chatterbox.
انه صندوق الثرثرة.
- It's your turn now. - He talks too slowly, that's why.
- حان دورك الآن. - يتحدث ببطء شديد ، لهذا السبب.
- Will Jong Kook go first? - Okay. I'll go first.
- هل سيذهب جونج كوك أولاً؟ - تمام. سأذهب أولاً.
- Good luck, Father! - Okay.
- حظا سعيدا يا أبي! - تمام.
Are you ready? Yu Jae Seok's nicknames.
هل أنت مستعد؟ يو جاي سوك الأسماء.
- One, - Grasshopper!
- واحد ، - جراد!
- two, - Grass...
- اثنان ، - العشب ...
Why does he have so many nicknames?
لماذا لديه الكثير من الأسماء المستعارة؟
- Two, three. - Grass... Why does he...
- اثنان ، ثلاثة. - العشب ... لماذا ...
(They start shooting before the verdict is announced.)
(يبدأون في إطلاق النار قبل الإعلان عن الحكم.)
Grasshopper, Small Nipples, Low-chested.
جراد ، حلمات صغيرة ، منخفضة الصلابة.
Hey.
يا.
It's true. You can look them up. They're on a site.
هذا صحيح. يمكنك البحث عنها. انهم على موقع.
- Grasshopper. - Low-chested.
- جراد. - منخفضة الصدر.
When did "Low-chested" become a nickname?
متى أصبحت "منخفضة الصدر" لقبًا؟
- Low-chested. - Jae Seok.
- منخفضة الصدر. - جاي سوك.
Your nipples are way down here.
حلماتك هي الطريق هنا.
Grasshopper, Low-chested...
الجندب ، منخفضة الصلابة ...
Let's be honest. Wasn't that a tough one?
لنكن صادقين. ألم يكن هذا صعبًا؟
- Grasshopper.
- جراد. - جراد.
- Ugly Face. - Lousy Shot.
- وجه قبيح. - لقطة رديئة.
- Beloved Host? - Front Teeth.
- مضيف محبوب؟ - الأسنان الأمامية.
Yu San Seul.
يو سان وحده.
- No... - He's Yu San Seul.
- لا ... - هو يو سان سول.
There are so many.
هناك الكثير.
They shot at me when I was trying to concentrate.
أطلقوا النار علي عندما كنت أحاول التركيز.
- What am I to do? - You shoot at us, then.
- ماذا أفعل؟ - أنت تطلق النار علينا ، ثم.
- You shoot at us. - Excuse me.
- أنت تطلق النار علينا. - اعذرني.
- Sir. - You shoot at us.
- سيد. - أنت تطلق النار علينا.
(The chatterbox has more to say.)
(لدى chatterbox المزيد ليقوله.)
- Hey! Shoot from over there. - Jang Hoon.
- يا! أطلق النار من هناك. - جانج هون.
(Pretending not to hear)
(التظاهر بعدم سماع)
No one's listening to Jang Hoon.
لا أحد يستمع إلى يانغ هون.
- Hey, if we're wrong... - Can someone get me earplugs?
- مهلا ، إذا كنا مخطئين ... - هل يمكن لأحد أن يحصل على سدادات الأذن؟
- If we're wrong... - I can't hear on this side.
- إذا كنا مخطئين ... - لا يمكنني سماع هذا الجانب.
They must start shooting after the referee decides...
يجب أن يبدأوا في إطلاق النار بعد أن يقرر الحكم ...
- they got it wrong. - Hey, Jang Hoon.
- لقد أخطأوا. - مهلا ، جانغ هون.
- Mister! Talk it out with us! - Jang Hoon.
- سيد! تحدث معنا! - جانج هون.
Yes, wait. Jang Hoon.
نعم ، انتظر. جانغ هون.
- Yes?
- جانج هون. - نعم؟
Why do you keep talking to the crew and not to us?
لماذا تستمر في التحدث إلى الطاقم وليس لنا؟
- You won't listen. - He's talking to the viewers.
- لن تستمع. - يتحدث إلى المشاهدين.
- That's why. - They won't listen.
- لهذا السبب. - لن يستمعوا.
He cares a lot about the public.
إنه يهتم كثيرًا بالجمهور.
Give it a go.
امنحها الذهاب.
- Then now... - Wait. Let's start from that end.
- ثم الآن ... - انتظر. لنبدأ من هذه الغاية.
- From this end? - Okay.
- من هذه الغاية؟ - تمام.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Three Super Junior members who are currently working.
ثلاثة أعضاء صغار سوبر يعملون حاليا.
Shindong, Kyu Hyun, Kim Hee Chul.
شيندونغ ، كيو هيون ، كيم هي تشول.
- Good. - Well done.
- جيد. - أحسنت.
That was easy!
كان ذلك سهلاً!
Father?
أب؟
- Why are you so whiny? - Father.
- لماذا أنت متهالك جدا؟ - أب.
I paint to release my anger.
أرسم لإطلاق غضبي.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
Next up is Ye Eun.
المقبل هو ye eun.
Three celebrities with your family name.
ثلاثة مشاهير يحملون اسم عائلتك.
Jee Seok Jin, Ji Ye Eun, Ji Chang Wook.
Deo Seook Jin ، Ji Yes ، Ji Yu ، Ji Chang Wook.
- Okay. - Okay!
- تمام. - تمام!
(2 successes in a row)
(2 نجاحات متتالية)
- Yes. Well done. - Come on!
- نعم. أحسنت. - تعال!
(The Yu Family is the 1st to succeed 2 times in a row.)
(عائلة يو هي الأولى التي تنجح مرتين متتاليتين.)
Gosh. They're good.
يا إلهي. انهم جيدون.
Don't be nervous. It's easy.
لا تكن عصبيا. إنه أمر سهل.
- Wait. I... - It's easy.
- انتظر. أنا ... - الأمر سهل.
Movies that Lee Byung Hun was in.
الأفلام التي كان Lee Byung Hun فيها.
One...
واحد...
(She just has to name 3 out of this long list.)
(يجب عليها فقط تسمية 3 من هذه القائمة الطويلة.)
- Two, - Tteok Bo's... No, wait.
- اثنان ، - tteok bo's ... لا ، انتظر.
- three. - Tteok Bo's...
- ثلاثة. - tteok bo's ...
(Tteok Bo?)
(tteok bo؟)
- "Tteok Bo's Day?" - What's that?
- "يوم tteok bo؟" - ما هذا؟
What on earth is "Tteok Bo's Day?"
ما هو على الأرض "يوم Tteok Bo؟"
What is that even?
ما هذا حتى؟
When was Byung Hun in "Tteok Bo's Day?"
متى كان بيونج هون في "يوم Tteok Bo؟"
- "Tteok Bo?" - Oh, "Squid Game."
- "tteok bo؟" - أوه ، "لعبة الحبار".
- "Squid Game?" - I confused that with this.
- "لعبة الحبار؟" - أنا في حيرة من هذا مع هذا.
- They're so different. - "Squid Game" and "Tteok Bo's Day?"
- إنها مختلفة جدا. - "لعبة الحبار" و "يوم Tteok Bo؟"
You can eat squid and rice cakes... Anyway, I got confused.
يمكنك أن تأكل كعكات الحبار والأرز ... على أي حال ، شعرت بالارتباك.
- Gosh. - What a shame.
- يا إلهي. - يا للعار.
Who will go first?
من سيذهب أولاً؟
Jang Hoon.
جانغ هون.
It's too much pressure to go first. I'll do it.
إنه الكثير من الضغط للذهاب أولاً. سأفعل ذلك.
- Which way do we go? - Okay.
- أي طريقة نذهب؟ - تمام.
- I'll start, and we'll go this way. - He went to Yonsei University.
- سأبدأ ، وسوف نذهب بهذه الطريقة. - ذهب إلى جامعة يونسي.
- Yonsei University. - Okay.
- جامعة Yonsei. - تمام.
Jang Hoon's impossible to miss.
من المستحيل تفويت جانج هون.
Jang Hoon's first.
جانغ هون الأول.
Three male idol groups.
ثلاث مجموعات المعبود الذكور.
- One, - What?
- واحد ، - ماذا؟
- two, - Super Junior...
- اثنان ، - سوبر جونيور ...
Come on, Jang Hoon. My dear younger brother.
هيا ، جانغ هون. أخي الأصغر العزيز.
Super Junior...
سوبر جونيور ...
Aim for his head.
تهدف إلى رأسه.
You're sitting next to a Super Junior member.
أنت تجلس بجانب عضو فائق الصغار.
A Super Junior member is next to you, Jang Hoon.
عضو سوبر جونيور هو بجوارك ، يانغ هون.
Ruin his hairstyle.
تدمر تصفيفة الشعر.
(He's getting a hydrating facial.)
(إنه يحصل على وجه رطب.)
You could name at least one!
يمكنك تسمية واحدة على الأقل!
- Jang Hoon... - Hey!
- جانغ هون ... - مهلا!
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
- Do you need a beating? - Jae Seok's overjoyed.
- هل تحتاج إلى ضرب؟ - جاي سوك بسعادة غامرة.
(He's pleased to see Jang Hoon drenched.)
(يسعده أن يرى يانغ هون غارقًا.)
- Hey. - Look at him.
- يا. - انظر إليه.
I love it.
أنا أحبه.
My gosh. Look.
يا إلهي. ينظر.
Hey. Look. See what he did?
يا. ينظر. ترى ماذا فعل؟
(Covering up shyly)
(تغطي بخجل)
(The culprit was...)
(كان الجاني ...)
(Yang Ssaebssaeb aimed for his groin.)
(يانغ ssaebssaeb يهدف إلى الفخذ.)
Hey, that's a low move. Se Chan... Why would he aim at...
مهلا ، هذه خطوة منخفضة. Se Chan ... لماذا يهدف إلى ...
Why were you sitting like that? Don't spread your legs out.
لماذا كنت جالسة هكذا؟ لا تنشر ساقيك.
I've never known someone to wear cotton slacks...
لم أكن أعرف أبدًا شخصًا يرتدي بنطال قطنية ...
to shoot an active, physical variety show like ours.
لإطلاق النار على مجموعة متنوعة نشطة وجسدية مثلنا.
- Long pants... - Hey.
- سروال طويل ... - مهلا.
- That's his uniform. - It's what he wears.
- هذا هو زيه. - هذا ما يرتديه.
(It happens to be pale and pretty fitting too.)
(يحدث أن يكون شاحبًا ومناسبًا جدًا.)
- He's wearing slacks. - So what?
- إنه يرتدي بنطلون. - وماذا في ذلك؟
- I'm sorry, but... - That's because he's 16.
- أنا آسف ، لكن ... - هذا لأنه يبلغ من العمر 16 عامًا.
this is what I usually wear on my other shows.
هذا ما أرتديه عادة على برامج أخرى.
- Yes, but we're... - It's because...
- نعم ، لكننا ... - هذا بسبب ...
he rarely shows his lower body on his other shows.
نادراً ما يظهر جسمه السفلي على عروضه الأخرى.
- It looks like it's washed. - Mr. Cotton Slacks.
- يبدو أنه تم غسله. - السيد كوتون سراونز.
I'd love to get that completely wet.
أحب أن أحصل على هذا الرطب تمامًا.
He looks funny.
يبدو مضحكا.
Who dresses like that for Running Man?
من يرتدي مثل هذا من أجل الجري الرجل؟
My gosh...
يا إلهي ...
Okay. Let's start with Jae Seok.
تمام. لنبدأ مع جاي سوك.
- Okay. - Let's go!
- تمام. - دعنا نذهب!
- Let's cheer. One, two, three. - Let's go. One, two, three.
- دعونا نبهج. واحد اثنين ثلاثة. - دعنا نذهب. واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
- Let's go! - Let's win!
- دعنا نذهب! - لنفوز!
Celebrities under the Antenna label. One...
المشاهير تحت علامة الهوائي. واحد...
(Celebrities under the Antenna label)
(المشاهير تحت ملصق الهوائي)
(Jae Seok and Se Chan are represented by Antenna!)
(Jae Seok و Se Chan يمثلان هوائي!)
- Yu Hui Yeol, me... - Three!
- يو هوي يول ، أنا ... - ثلاثة!
- Yu... - Come on.
- يو ... - هيا.
(Incorrect)
(غير صحيح)
Yang Se Chan.
يانغ سي تشان.
"Me?"
"أنا؟"
- Who is "me?" - Hey!
- من هو "أنا؟" - يا!
- That was easy! - Me!
- كان ذلك سهلاً! - أنا!
Me! I was right here!
أنا! كنت هنا!
- Why... - Jae Seok, Se Chan, Lee Hyo Ri!
- لماذا ... - جاي سوك ، شان ، لي هيو ري!
- Yes! Lee Seo Jin! - Not long ago...
- نعم! لي سيو جين! - منذ وقت ليس ببعيد ...
- Me! - you filmed together.
- أنا! - لقد قمت بتصويرها معًا.
Me!
أنا!
(Squelch)
(سحق)
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
- Me! - What was that?
- أنا! - ماذا كان هذا؟
- Hang on.
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - انتظر.
I think Jang Hoon is crushing on Ye Eun.
أعتقد أن Jang Hoon يسحق على أيها eun.
- Why? - He won't stop shooting at her.
- لماذا؟ - لن يتوقف عن إطلاق النار عليها.
(The love-crazed fool comes up with a weird subplot.)
(يأتي الخداع المثير للحب بحبكة فرعية غريبة.)
Are you showing how you feel with your water pistol?
هل تُظهر كيف تشعر مع مسدس الماء الخاص بك؟
(A weird subplot)
(حبكة فرعية غريبة)
(Giants from rival families falling in love?)
(عمالقة من عائلات منافسة تقع في الحب؟)
I thought he was harassing her, but he was flirting.
اعتقدت أنه كان يضايقها ، لكنه كان يمزح.
Hey.
يا.
- Mr. Cotton Slacks! - Seriously.
- السيد كوتون سراونز! - بجد.
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
- It's for real? - Really?
- إنه حقيقي؟ - حقًا؟
Hey. Nice.
يا. لطيف - جيد.
- Nice. - What's that?
- لطيف - جيد. - ما هذا؟
He confessed his love. What for?
اعترف بحبه. ماذا؟
- Nice. - "Nice."
- لطيف - جيد. - "لطيف - جيد."
- What? - You like her?
- ماذا؟ - هل تحبها؟
- You're professing your love? - For real?
- أنت تعرّض حبك؟ - لريال مدريد؟
Ye Eun said her ideal type was Kim Woo Bin.
قالت أيها يون أن نوعها المثالي كان كيم وو بن.
- Yes. - She's all about good looks.
- نعم. - إنها كل شيء عن المظهر الجيد.
(Ye Eun's 175cm, and he's 205cm, an exhilarating height difference.)
(أيها يون 175 سم ، وهو 205 سم ، وهو اختلاف في الارتفاع المبهج.)
Seo Jang Hoon!
سيو يانغ هون!
(It's a fake subplot made up purely for entertainment purposes.)
(إنه حبكة فرعية مزيفة مكونة بحتة لأغراض الترفيه.)
What is this, really?
ما هذا ، حقا؟
This is fun.
هذا ممتع.
- Is it that side? - I'll go first.
- هل هذا الجانب؟ - سأذهب أولاً.
- Okay. - Are you ready?
- تمام. - هل أنت مستعد؟
Three foreign singers.
ثلاثة مغنين أجانب.
Christina Aguilera, Britney Spears, Michael Jackson!
كريستينا أغيليرا ، بريتني سبيرز ، مايكل جاكسون!
(Christina Aguilera, Britney Spears, Michael Jackson)
(كريستينا أغيليرا ، بريتني سبيرز ، مايكل جاكسون)
(The Kim Family succeeds for the first time.)
(تنجح عائلة كيم لأول مرة.)
- Yes! - Yes.
- نعم! - نعم.
(Jong Kook is next.)
(Jong Kook هو التالي.)
Jong Kook, it's your turn.
جونغ كوك ، حان دورك.
Jong Kook, name three shows Seo Jang Hoon appears on.
يونغ كوك ، اسم ثلاثة عروض يظهر SEO Jang Hoon.
(Will Jang Hoon's good friend get it right?)
(هل سيحصل صديق جانج هون الجيد على ذلك بشكل صحيح؟)
- One, - "My Little Old Boy."
- واحد ، - "ابني العجوز الصغير".
two, three.
اثنان ، ثلاثة.
(Incorrect)
(غير صحيح)
(Ugly duckling!)
(البطة القبيحة!)
(His yell is followed by silence.)
(يتبع صراخه الصمت.)
Darn you.
الرتق لك.
- Hey! - You should know by now.
- يا! - يجب أن تعرف الآن.
- Hey. - He knows nothing.
- يا. - إنه لا يعرف شيئًا.
- I do so many... - The divorce show!
- أفعل الكثير ... - عرض الطلاق!
- You... - "My Little Old Boy."
- أنت ... - "ابني العجوز الصغير."
"Men on a Mission."
"الرجال في مهمة."
Come on, Kook Jong.
هيا ، كوك جونغ.
I watch them all, but the titles...
أشاهدهم جميعًا ، لكن العناوين ...
Who memorizes the titles these days?
من يحفظ العناوين هذه الأيام؟
Okay. You're making...
تمام. أنت تصنع ...
- so little progress. - We're useless.
- تقدم القليل جدا. - نحن عديمة الفائدة.
- It's hard. - It's too hard.
- إنه صعب. - إنه صعب للغاية.
We'll let you pass twice.
سنسمح لك بالمرتين.
- Okay, good. - Two passes.
- حسنا ، جيد. - ممران.
Who will go first on this side?
من سيذهب أولاً على هذا الجانب؟
- I'll go first. - You start it off.
- سأذهب أولاً. - أنت تبدأ.
Okay.
تمام.
- If you don't know, pass.
- إذا كنت لا تعرف ، مر. - إذا كنت لا تعرف ، مر.
- Let's do it this time.
- دعونا نفعل ذلك هذه المرة. - إذا كنت لا تعرف ، مر.
Three of Seok Jin's nicknames.
ثلاثة من الأسماء المستعارة Seok Jin.
- One, two, - Seok Sam, Big Nose,
- واحد ، اثنان ، - سوك سام ، أنف كبير ،
- feeble kid. - Okay.
- طفل ضعيف. - تمام.
"Feeble kid..." - Feeble kid.
"طفل ضعيف ..." - طفل ضعيف. - طفل ضعيف.
They're all names he came up with!
انهم كل الأسماء التي توصل إليها!
- They're all what he calls him! - He's feeble.
- كلهم ما يسميه! - إنه ضعيف.
What is "feeble kid?"
ما هو "الطفل الضعيف؟"
Feeble kid.
طفل ضعيف.
- What, feeble kid? - Feeble kid.
- ماذا ، طفل ضعيف؟ - طفل ضعيف.
We did this for decades.
لقد فعلنا هذا لعقود.
They should be nicknames...
يجب أن تكون مستعارة ...
- the viewers are familiar with. - The oh, so feeble kid.
- المشاهدون على دراية. - يا طفل ضعيف جدا.
- "Feeble kid?" - Feeble kid.
- "طفل ضعيف؟" - طفل ضعيف.
You can look it up online.
يمكنك البحث عنها عبر الإنترنت.
- Let's keep going. - Seok Jin is next.
- دعنا نستمر. - سيوك جين هو التالي.
- Okay. - Three of Jong Kook's songs...
- تمام. - ثلاث من أغاني Jong Kook ...
including Turbo songs.
بما في ذلك أغاني توربو.
- One, two, - "One Man," "Twist King,"
- واحد ، اثنان ، - "رجل واحد ،" "تويست كينج" ، "
- three! - Pass!
- ثلاثة! - يمر!
(He used his "pass" chance before the chime.)
(استخدم فرصة "المرور" قبل التناغم.)
- He passed. - I said "pass."
- مر. - قلت "الممر".
You can do this too?
يمكنك أن تفعل هذا أيضا؟
Three of Jong Kook's songs.
ثلاث من أغاني جونغ كوك.
"Twist King," "December," "Black Cat Nero."
"Twist King" ، "December ،" "Black Cat Nero."
- Okay! - "December,"
- تمام! - "ديسمبر" ، "
(She successfully answered the same question.)
(أجابت بنجاح على نفس السؤال.)
- Ye Eun's next. - Yes.
- أيها يون التالي. - نعم.
Three Chinese idioms. One,
ثلاثة تعابير صينية. واحد،
- two, - Yeokhak... Pass!
- اثنان ، - Yeokhak ... تمرير!
(No one can pass now.)
(لا يمكن لأحد أن يمر الآن.)
Three Chinese idioms.
ثلاثة تعابير صينية.
- Gojingamrae, yeokjisaji. - Two,
- Gojingamrae ، Yeokjisaji. - اثنين،
ilseokyijo!
ilseokyi!
You did it!
لقد فعلت ذلك!
(The leader of the empty heads is doing a great job.)
(زعيم الرؤوس الفارغة يقوم بعمل رائع.)
- Great! - They need to get one more right.
- عظيم! - يحتاجون إلى الحصول على واحد آخر.
You need one more right.
أنت بحاجة إلى واحدة أخرى.
- We need one more. - Who will do it?
- نحن بحاجة واحدة أخرى. - من سيفعل ذلك؟
(Se Chan's the one left.)
(Se chan's the on to on the on.)
(What is the last question that will decide the result?)
(ما هو السؤال الأخير الذي سيقرر النتيجة؟)
- He's the last one. - Are you ready?
- إنه الأخير. - هل أنت مستعد؟
Three English words starting with the letter M.
ثلاث كلمات إنجليزية تبدأ من الرسالة M.
- Memory! - One.
- الذاكرة! - واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
- Moya! - Three.
- مويا! - ثلاثة.
Gosh, what?
يا إلهي ، ماذا؟
Moya!
مويا!
(He runs out of time as he can't overcome the language barrier.)
(ينفد من الوقت لأنه لا يستطيع التغلب على حاجز اللغة.)
- What is "Moya?" - What? "Moya?"
- ما هو "مويا؟" - ماذا؟ "مويا؟"
(What is "Moya" supposed to be?)
(ما الذي يفترض أن يكون "مويا"؟)
Moya!
مويا!
"Moya?"
"مويا؟"
- MBC. - Hey, you could've said music.
- MBC. - مهلا ، هل يمكن أن تقول الموسيقى.
- Music, memory. - Oh, music.
- الموسيقى ، الذاكرة. - أوه ، الموسيقى.
Gosh, you could've succeeded.
يا إلهي ، يمكنك أن تنجح.
- Memory, music. - It's such a shame.
- الذاكرة ، الموسيقى. - إنه عار.
- Let's succeed this time. - Yes.
- لننجح هذه المرة. - نعم.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- تمام. - دعنا نذهب.
- We'll do this, no matter what. - Just once.
- سنفعل هذا ، مهما كان. - مرة واحدة فقط.
- If possible, try not to pass... - No matter what, just go.
- إن أمكن ، حاول ألا تمر ... - بغض النظر عن ماذا ، فقط اذهب.
- for the next person's sake. - Right.
- من أجل الشخص التالي. - يمين.
- Pass after you try. - Okay.
- مر بعد المحاولة. - تمام.
We have to buy time for the people behind us.
علينا أن نشتري وقتًا للأشخاص الذين يقفون وراءنا.
Also, you have to think about...
أيضا ، عليك أن تفكر في ...
the question before as much as you can.
السؤال قبل قدر الإمكان.
Okay.
تمام.
That way, you can get it right when it becomes your turn.
وبهذه الطريقة ، يمكنك الحصول عليها بشكل صحيح عندما يصبح دورك.
Who will go first?
من سيذهب أولاً؟
We'll start with our youngest.
سنبدأ مع أصغرنا.
- So, starting with Jang Hoon? - Yes.
- إذن ، بدءًا من Jang Hoon؟ - نعم.
- No, you go first. - That way.
- لا ، تذهب أولا. - بهذه الطريقة.
- Start there and go this way. - "You go first?"
- ابدأ هناك واذهب بهذه الطريقة. - "تذهب أولا؟"
- No, let's start with you, Dad. - Why, you rude punk!
- لا ، لنبدأ معك يا أبي. - لماذا ، أنت وقح الشرير!
Dad, you go first.
أبي ، تذهب أولاً.
(Getting shot right in the Adam's apple)
(الحصول على إطلاق النار في تفاحة آدم)
Let's start with Dad.
لنبدأ مع أبي.
- Then, starting with Jong Kook. - Yes.
- ثم ، بدءا من جونغ كوك. - نعم.
Okay, I'll go first.
حسنًا ، سأذهب أولاً.
All right.
حسنًا.
Three foreign sports stars.
ثلاثة نجوم رياضية أجنبية.
(Jong Kook is absolutely crazy about sports.)
(Jong Kook مجنونة تمامًا بالرياضة.)
- Three. - Park Ji... Oh, Cristiano Ronaldo!
- ثلاثة. - بارك جي ... أوه ، كريستيانو رونالدو!
- Messi! - Okay.
- ميسي! - تمام.
- Three! - Jordan!
- ثلاثة! - الأردن!
Why didn't you pass?
لماذا لم تمر؟
- Why didn't you pass? - Why won't you pass?
- لماذا لم تمر؟ - لماذا لا تمر؟
(An athlete with nothing but a loud voice)
(رياضي لا شيء سوى صوت عالي)
(Soccer Kim stumbles over the sports question as well as in sports.)
(كرة القدم كيم تتعثر على السؤال الرياضي وكذلك في الرياضة.)
I was going to pass...
كنت ذاهب لتمرير ...
- after doing as much as I could. - You say you love soccer so much.
- بعد أن أفعل قدر استطاعتي. - أنت تقول أنك تحب كرة القدم كثيرًا.
Jong Kook got it all wrong too.
لقد أخطأ جونج كوك أيضًا.
Okay, then.
حسنًا ، إذن.
Now, we'll only give you...
الآن ، سنعطيك فقط ...
- one last chance each. - Okay.
- فرصة أخيرة لكل منهما. - تمام.
- They're so harsh only on us.
- تمام. - إنهم قاسيون جدًا علينا فقط.
Hey, we should...
مهلا ، يجب علينا ...
- Yes, this sounds good. - Let's go with this.
- نعم ، هذا يبدو جيدا. - دعنا نذهب مع هذا.
- Let's go. - Pass if you don't know.
- دعنا نذهب. - مرر إذا كنت لا تعرف.
- We can pass twice, right? - Let's get this right.
- يمكننا المرور مرتين ، أليس كذلك؟ - دعونا نحصل على هذا بشكل صحيح.
- Pass if you don't know. - All right.
- مرر إذا كنت لا تعرف. - حسنًا.
Three great historical figures of Korea.
ثلاثة شخصيات تاريخية كبيرة لكوريا.
- One. - Admiral Yi Sun Sin.
- واحد. - الأدميرال يي صن خطيئة.
- Two. - Shin Saimdang.
- اثنين. - Shin Saimdang.
- Sejong the Great. - Okay!
- سيجونغ العظيم. - تمام!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Okay. Three foreign musicians.
تمام. ثلاثة موسيقيين أجانب.
- One. - Beethoven. Bach. Handel.
- واحد. - بيتهوفن. باخ. هاندل.
(Foreign musicians: Beethoven, Bach, Handel)
(الموسيقيين الأجانب: بيتهوفن ، باخ ، هاندل)
(He even succeeds in the difficult question.)
(حتى أنه نجح في السؤال الصعب.)
- So smart! - Let's go.
- ذكي جدا! - دعنا نذهب.
Okay, Gi Ru.
حسنًا ، فتاة.
Three foreign painters.
ثلاثة رسامين أجانب.
- Pass. - One.
- يمر. - واحد.
Foreign painters. One.
الرسامين الأجانب. واحد.
- Picasso. Pass. - Two.
- بيكاسو. يمر. - اثنين.
Three great historical figures with four syllables in their names.
ثلاثة شخصيات تاريخية رائعة مع أربعة مقاطع في أسمائهم.
- Historical figures? Shin Saimdang. - One.
- شخصيات تاريخية؟ شين سايمدانغ. - واحد.
- Two. - Madame Curie.
- اثنين. - مدام كوري.
Sejong the Great.
سيجونغ العظيم.
(Yang Se Chan succeeds again.)
(يانغ سي تشان ينجح مرة أخرى.)
Gosh, Se Chan!
يا إلهي ، شان!
Madame Curie?
مدام كوري؟
- Isn't it Marie Curie? - Madame Curie is correct!
- أليس ماري كوري؟ - مدام كوري صحيح!
- Madame Curie is her name. - Oh, even the "Madame" part?
- مدام كوري هو اسمها. - أوه ، حتى الجزء "مدام"؟
- Madame Curie. - What?
- مدام كوري. - ماذا؟
You said "Madame" Curie.
قلت "مدام" كوري.
- Madame Curie. - It's Marie Curie!
- مدام كوري. - إنه ماري كوري!
- Her name is Marie Curie. - Yes, but she's called...
- اسمها ماري كوري. - نعم ، لكنها تسمى ...
- You can't say Madame Curie. - Gosh, what's up with him?
- لا يمكنك أن تقول مدام كوري. - يا إلهي ، ما الأمر معه؟
- Jong Kook, isn't she Madame Curie? - Curie.
- جونغ كوك ، أليس مدام كوري؟ - كوري.
- Look. - Isn't she a "Madame?"
- ينظر. - أليس كذلك "مدام؟"
Then, Daddy Jae Seok.
ثم ، أبي جاي سوك.
Should Daddy Jae Seok also count as four syllables?
هل يجب أن يعتبر Daddy Jae Seok أيضًا أربعة مقاطع؟
- Big bro Jong Kook. Four syllables. - Gosh, Big bro Jong Kook?
- Big Bro Jong Kook. أربعة مقاطع. - يا إلهي ، Big Bro Jong Kook؟
- What is that? - My gosh!
- ما هذا؟ - يا إلهي!
Madame Curie?
مدام كوري؟
- Does that make sense? - I mean...
- هل هذا منطقي؟ - أعني...
- Also... Hang on. - Marie Curie should be right.
- أيضا ... انتظر. - يجب أن تكون ماري كوري على حق.
All right. They have one more left.
حسنًا. لديهم واحد آخر.
- Here's the last question. - They have one more left.
- هذا هو السؤال الأخير. - لديهم واحد آخر اليسار.
- The last question. - Me?
- السؤال الأخير. - أنا؟
Three well-known scientists.
ثلاثة علماء معروفين.
- Einstein. - One.
- أينشتاين. - واحد.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Two. Three.
اثنين. ثلاثة.
(Fail)
(يفشل)
(Madame Curie is a scientist too.)
(مدام كوري عالمة أيضًا.)
My gosh. Seriously?
يا إلهي. بجد؟
For this team, all but one succeeded.
لهذا الفريق ، نجحت جميع ما عدا واحد.
- Let's do it this time. - Okay.
- دعونا نفعل ذلك هذه المرة. - تمام.
For real. Let's do it.
لريال مدريد. دعونا نفعل ذلك.
- Starting with Shindong. - We'll go this way.
- بدءا من شيندونغ. - سنذهب بهذه الطريقة.
Three songs by Haha.
ثلاث أغنيات من هاها.
- One. Two. - Give him one hour.
- واحد. اثنين. - أعطه ساعة واحدة.
Pass. Gosh, I don't know.
يمر. يا إلهي ، لا أعرف.
"Dang Diggi Bang," "SSK," "You Are My Destiny."
"دانغ ديججي بانج" ، "SSK ،" "أنت مصيري".
- What's "SSK?" - "SSK?"
- ما هو "SSK؟" - "SSK؟"
- "Story of a Short Kid." - But you said...
- "قصة طفل قصير". - لكن قلت ...
No, you should've said "Story of..."
لا ، يجب أن تقول "قصة ..."
- You can't call it "SSK." - What is that?
- لا يمكنك تسميتها "SSK". - ما هذا؟
We let you get away with Madame Curie!
ندعك تفلت من مدام كوري!
- Okay. - Well, okay.
- تمام. - حسنًا ، حسنًا.
- Go ahead. - Madame Curie.
- تفضل. - مدام كوري.
- All right. Now, it's Daniel. - Okay.
- حسنًا. الآن ، إنه دانيال. - تمام.
Three songs by Super Junior.
ثلاث أغنيات من قبل Super Junior.
- That's so easy. - One.
- هذا سهل للغاية. - واحد.
- "Sorry Sorry." - Two.
- "آسف آسف." - اثنين.
- Pass!
- اثنين. - يمر!
- Okay. - All right.
- تمام. - حسنًا.
(They've already used up all of their passes.)
(لقد استخدموا بالفعل جميع تمريراتهم.)
- "Sorry, Sorry," "Rokuko..." - One.
- "آسف ، آسف ،" "روكوكو ..." - واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
(Will Jong Kook know Super Junior's songs?)
(هل يعرف جونغ كوك أغاني سوبر جونيور؟)
"Express Mode!"
"الوضع السريع!"
("Express Mode")
("الوضع السريع")
(Somehow, the old bachelor remembered a new song!)
(بطريقة ما ، تذكرت البكالوريوس القديمة أغنية جديدة!)
- "Express Mode." - My goodness.
- "الوضع السريع". - يا إلهي.
You've used all of your passes now.
لقد استخدمت كل ما تبذلونه الآن.
- There are two of us left. - Okay, Ji Hyo.
- هناك اثنان منا غادر. - حسنًا ، جي هيو.
Three four-syllable Chinese idioms.
ثلاثة تعابير صينية من أربعة مقاطع.
- One. - Ilseokyijo.
- واحد. - Ilseokyijo.
- Two. - "2 Days and 1 Night."
- اثنين. - "يومين وليلة واحدة."
- "2 Days and 1 Night?"
- "يومين وليلة واحدة؟" - "يومين وليلة واحدة."
("2 Days and 1 Night")
("يومين وليلة واحدة")
- "2 Days and 1 Night." - Hey, Ji Hyo.
- "يومين وليلة واحدة." - مهلا ، جي هيو.
Gosh, how could you ask Ji Hyo...
يا إلهي ، كيف يمكن أن تسأل جي هيو ...
How could you ask Ji Hyo for three four-syllable Chinese idioms?
كيف يمكن أن تسأل Ji Hyo عن ثلاثة تعابير صينية من أربع مقطع؟
- Isn't that too harsh? - They're our rival show!
- أليس هذا قاسيًا جدًا؟ - هم عرضنا المنافس!
- Our rival show! - Hey, but Ji Hyo.
- عرضنا المنافس! - مهلا ، لكن جي هيو.
- Ji Hyo, they're our rival show! - "2 Days and 1 Night" is...
- جي هيو ، إنهم عرضنا المنافس! - "يومين وليلة واحدة" ...
That's a show that airs at the same time as our show.
هذا عرض يبث في نفس الوقت الذي يتم فيه عرضنا.
I mean, four-syllable Chinese idioms for Ji Hyo?
أعني ، التعابير الصينية ذات الأربعة مقاطع لـ Ji Hyo؟
- Gosh, but "2 Days and 1 Night" is big. - It is big.
- يا إلهي ، لكن "يومين وليلة واحدة" كبيرة. - إنه كبير.
Here is the result of the mission.
هنا هي نتيجة المهمة.
The Yu Family has won.
فازت عائلة يو.
- So, - Okay!
- لذلك ، - حسنًا!
when you draw the picture at the end,
عندما ترسم الصورة في النهاية ،
you can choose two people...
يمكنك اختيار شخصين ...
to take two more minutes.
لأخذ دقيقتين أخريين.
Okay.
تمام.
- That's nice. - You can give two minutes...
- هذا جميل. - يمكنك إعطاء دقيقتين ...
- to those with less confidence. - Those who aren't confident.
- لأولئك الذين لديهم ثقة أقل. - أولئك الذين ليسوا واثقين.
Then, we'll move...
ثم ، سنتحرك ...
- and do the next mission. - Okay, let's go!
- والقيام بالمهمة التالية. - حسنًا ، دعنا نذهب!
Okay!
تمام!
- Look. - What is this?
- ينظر. - ما هذا؟
Hey, what is this?
مهلا ، ما هذا؟
- Hey, it's food. - What is this?
- مهلا ، إنه طعام. - ما هذا؟
- Gosh, look at this. - It's food.
- يا إلهي ، انظر إلى هذا. - إنه طعام.
- It's an interesting game. - Hey, Shindong.
- إنها لعبة مثيرة للاهتمام. - مهلا ، شيندونغ.
It's Shindong time now.
حان وقت Shindong الآن.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
(Groaning)
(يئن)
Gi Ru, you look cute.
GI RU ، تبدو لطيفًا.
Mister, be careful.
مستر ، كن حذرا.
- Why, you little... - I told you to be careful.
- لماذا ، أنت القليل ... - قلت لك أن تكون حذرا.
Come on.
تعال.
All right. That was great.
حسنًا. ًكان كبيرا.
You are...
أنت...
What am I saying? Even when you've gotten older,
ماذا أقول؟ حتى عندما تكبر ،
you're so full of energy.
أنت مليء بالطاقة.
- That's because they pay me. - What?
- هذا لأنهم يدفعون لي. - ماذا؟
That's because they pay me.
هذا لأنهم يدفعون لي.
By the way, Mr. Cotton Slacks,
بالمناسبة ، السيد كوتون سراونز ،
you changed into jeans.
لقد تحولت إلى الجينز.
- Mr. Jeans. - What...
- السيد جينز. - ماذا...
- Which pants will you wear next? - Who are you calling "Mister?"
- ما هي السراويل التي سترتديها بعد ذلك؟ - من الذي تسميه "سيد؟"
He's 16 years old.
يبلغ من العمر 16 عامًا.
He's our youngest.
إنه أصغرنا.
- I'm... - Don't talk about...
- أنا ... - لا تتحدث عن ...
- sixteen years old. - our youngest like that.
- ستة عشر عامًا. - أصغرنا من هذا القبيل.
My pants were a bit...
كانت سروالي قليلا ...
In case they made the viewers uncomfortable,
في حال جعلوا المشاهدين غير مرتاحين ،
- I changed into a new pair. - What a pro.
- لقد تحولت إلى زوج جديد. - يا له من محترف.
- He's a good kid. - I know.
- إنه طفل جيد. - أنا أعرف.
By the way, Seok Jin,
بالمناسبة ، سوك جين ،
why are you shaking your legs so much?
لماذا تهز ساقيك كثيرا؟
It's because he's nervous.
هذا لأنه عصبي.
- Who? - I'm just nervous.
- من؟ - أنا متوتر فقط.
Why do you care about my leg?
لماذا تهتم بساقي؟
Are you supposed to bite each other's heads off on this show?
هل من المفترض أن تعض رؤوس بعضكما في هذا العرض؟
- Yes, that's how you get paid. - That's right.
- نعم ، هكذا تتقاضى رواتك. - هذا صحيح.
- It's our routine. - It's a cliche.
- إنه روتيننا. - إنها كليشيهات.
- Is that how it's supposed to be? - A cliche.
- هل هذا كيف من المفترض أن يكون؟ - كليشيه.
When we go home, we get carried out like this.
عندما نذهب إلى المنزل ، يتم تنفيذ مثل هذا.
(They go home exhausted after growling at each other all day.)
(يذهبون إلى المنزل مرهقين بعد الهدر على بعضهم البعض طوال اليوم.)
- That's how you go home. - Oh, I...
- هكذا تذهب إلى المنزل. - أوه ، أنا ...
I love this kind of show.
أنا أحب هذا النوع من العرض.
- I'm good at being ferocious. - I mean, we just started,
- أنا جيد في أن أكون شرسة. - أعني ، لقد بدأنا للتو ،
- and everyone is... - That's how it is.
- والجميع ... - هكذا هو.
- I'm good at biting and gnawing. - Let me explain...
- أنا جيد في العض والقنص. - دعني أشرح ...
the next mission.
المهمة التالية.
Among the games submitted to us by foreign fans of Running Man,
من بين الألعاب المقدمة إلينا من قِبل المشجعين الأجانب من Running Man ،
there is a game that would be a good fit for our three guests.
هناك لعبة ستكون مناسبة لضيوفنا الثلاثة.
So, we've adjusted it slightly and prepared the game...
لذلك ، قمنا بتعديلها قليلاً وأعدنا اللعبة ...
called Eat Your Fill and Throw Mission.
يسمى أكل ملء ورمي مهمة.
Eat Your Fill and Throw?
أكل ملء ورمي؟
- Eat Your Fill and Throw. - Eat Your Fill and Throw?
- أكل ملء ورمي. - أكل ملء ورمي؟
Two representatives from each team will come up...
سيأتي ممثلان من كل فريق ...
and eat the buffet food...
وتناول طعام البوفيه ...
moving on the conveyor belt.
التحرك على حزام النقل.
Then, you have to build a tower of plates in the order you ate them.
بعد ذلك ، يجب عليك بناء برج من اللوحات بالطلب الذي أكلته.
We have to eat a lot.
علينا أن نأكل كثيرا.
(Build a tower of plates after eating the buffet food.)
(بناء برج من اللوحات بعد تناول طعام البوفيه.)
Then, that's too easy.
ثم ، هذا سهل للغاية.
- The order is important. - You can also throw empty plates...
- النظام مهم. - يمكنك أيضًا رمي لوحات فارغة ...
to attack the other team's plate tower...
لمهاجمة برج لوحة الفريق الآخر ...
and try to make it collapse.
وحاول أن تجعله ينهار.
You can also throw empty plates...
يمكنك أيضًا رمي لوحات فارغة ...
to attack the other team's plate tower...
لمهاجمة برج لوحة الفريق الآخر ...
and try to make it collapse.
وحاول أن تجعله ينهار.
- The team that gets attacked... - We have to knock it down.
- الفريق الذي يتعرض للهجوم ... - علينا أن ننزلق.
can keep piling plates...
يمكن أن تستمر في تكديس لوحات ...
- on top of the surviving plates. - I see.
- أعلى اللوحات الباقية. - أرى.
- We have to bother the other team. - We can either pile them up...
- علينا أن نزعج الفريق الآخر. - يمكننا إما تكديسهم ...
or throw them.
أو رميهم.
After the time is up,
بعد الوقت انتهى ،
we will measure the height of the plates still standing.
سنقوم بقياس ارتفاع اللوحات لا يزال قائما.
That's how we'll determine who wins and who loses.
هكذا سنحدد من يفوز ومن يخسر.
We'll play three rounds in total.
سنلعب ثلاث جولات في المجموع.
To the winning team of this mission,
إلى الفريق الفائز في هذه المهمة ،
we will give you a luxury frame...
سنعطيك إطارًا فاخرًا ...
that will increase the value of your drawing.
سيؤدي ذلك إلى زيادة قيمة الرسم.
If you earn it, that will be a huge advantage.
إذا كسبتها ، فستكون هذه ميزة كبيرة.
- A frame is important. - Okay.
- إطار مهم. - تمام.
- First, you can choose...
- أولاً ، يمكنك اختيار ... - حسنًا.
- two representatives. - Representatives?
- ممثلان. - ممثلون؟
- One more person... - Who eats well?
- شخص آخر ... - من يأكل جيدًا؟
Gi Ru, let's crush them.
جي رو ، دعنا نسحقهم.
- Can you eat a lot? - Should I go?
- هل يمكنك أن تأكل كثيرا؟ - هل يجب أن أذهب؟
- With who? - I'll go.
- مع من؟ - سأذهب.
- You should go. - With Ruru.
- يجب أن تذهب. - مع رورو.
- Me? Okay.
- مع رورو. - أنا؟ تمام.
- Ruru should go. - All right.
- يجب أن يذهب رورو. - حسنًا.
With my daughter-in-law.
مع ابنتي.
The daughter-in-law and father-in-law.
ابنة زوجها وصهره.
- Go, sweetie! You can do it! - Oh, right.
- اذهب يا حبيبتي! يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك! - أوه ، صحيح.
- Why isn't Shindong playing? - Let's go!
- لماذا لا يلعب Shindong؟ - دعنا نذهب!
- Come on, youngest brother.
- دعنا نذهب! - هيا يا أخي الأصغر.
- Okay. - They're really strong.
- تمام. - إنهم قويون حقًا.
- Gosh, Jang Hoon eats a lot. - Our youngest...
- يا إلهي ، يانغ هون يأكل كثيرا. - أصغرنا ...
I think Jang Hoon will eat a lot.
أعتقد أن Jang Hoon سوف يأكل كثيرًا.
Shin Gi Ru says that I eat a lot.
يقول شين جي رو إنني آكل كثيرًا.
We threw so many plates when we were little.
ألقينا الكثير من اللوحات عندما كنا صغيرين.
But is it okay to throw these plates?
ولكن هل من المقبول رمي هذه اللوحات؟
- Yes, you can throw them. - Are they nice plates?
- نعم ، يمكنك رميها. - هل هي لوحات جميلة؟
- Would we use glass plates, mister? - I know.
- هل نستخدم الألواح الزجاجية ، سيد؟ - أنا أعرف.
- No, I mean, new ones... - Well, our youngest just cares...
- لا ، أعني ، جديدة ... - حسنًا ، أصغرنا فقط يهتمون ...
- about the show and the viewers. - You keep calling him "Mister."
- حول العرض والمشاهدين. - تستمر في الاتصال به "مستر".
Well, that's because he's asking unnecessary questions.
حسنًا ، هذا لأنه يطرح أسئلة غير ضرورية.
- "Ask Us Anything Fortune Teller." - I mean...
- "اسألنا أي شيء صراف ثروة." - أعني...
That's right. Ask Us Anything."
هذا صحيح. اسألنا أي شيء ".
(Hoon suddenly cracks jokes.)
(Hoon يتشقق فجأة النكات.)
- Good job. - Right. That's another one.
- أحسنت. - يمين. هذا واحد آخر.
- Hey, you're that fortune teller! - Right.
- مهلا ، أنت ذلك صراف الثروة! - يمين.
- I do lots of odd jobs. - That's right.
- أفعل الكثير من الوظائف الفردية. - هذا صحيح.
- He has lots of part-time jobs. - I'm called...
- لديه الكثير من الوظائف بدوام جزئي. - أنا اتصل ...
- Chief, Fortune Teller... - He has many jobs.
- رئيس ، ثروة الصراف ... - لديه العديد من الوظائف.
- I have lots of jobs. - "Chief and Fortune Teller."
- لدي الكثير من الوظائف. - "رئيس وثروة الصراف."
- That's right. - Gi Ru.
- هذا صحيح. - جي رو.
They don't have the upper hand on us in terms of size.
ليس لديهم اليد العليا علينا من حيث الحجم.
- They're not that much bigger. - But I don't eat much.
- إنهم ليسوا أكبر بكثير. - لكني لا آكل كثيرا.
- Well, I eat a variety of foods. - Still, enjoy it.
- حسنا ، أنا آكل مجموعة متنوعة من الأطعمة. - لا يزال ، استمتع بها.
But I don't eat much.
لكني لا آكل كثيرا.
Well, I eat a variety of foods.
حسنًا ، أنا آكل مجموعة متنوعة من الأطعمة.
- Let me know if you get tired. - Seriously.
- اسمحوا لي أن أعرف إذا تعبت. - بجد.
Really, though. Don't come on someone else's successful show...
حقا ، رغم ذلك. لا تأتي في عرض شخص آخر ناجح ...
- and spew that nonsense. - He's been saying...
- وانطلق هذا الهراء. - كان يقول ...
- You don't eat much? - Hey, mister.
- أنت لا تأكل كثيرا؟ - مهلا ، سيد.
- She says she doesn't... - Hey, so...
- تقول إنها لا ... - مهلا ، لذا ...
Let me just say this.
دعني فقط أقول هذا.
She said she didn't like clams that much.
قالت إنها لا تحب البطلينوس كثيرًا.
- But then... - I can eat the clams, then.
- ولكن بعد ذلك ... - يمكنني أن آكل البطلينوس ، ثم.
No, she said she didn't like clams,
لا ، قالت إنها لا تحب البطلينوس ،
and she said she'd only eat a bit.
وقالت إنها ستأكل قليلا فقط.
Then, she ate this many clams.
ثم أكلت هذه البطلينوس.
Why would you say that, Jang Hoon?
لماذا تقول ذلك يا جانغ هون؟
She ate all the clams...
أكلت كل المحار ...
- in front of the sandy beach. - My goodness.
- أمام الشاطئ الرملي. - يا إلهي.
- Look here. Why would you... - Why are you doing this?
- انظر هنا. لماذا ... - لماذا تفعل هذا؟
Why would you bring up my weakness like that?
لماذا تثير ضعف هكذا؟
(The scene of the clam massacre that Jang Hoon witnessed)
(مشهد مذبحة البطلينوس التي شهدها جانغ هون)
- What if she liked them for real? - I'll eat them, okay?
- ماذا لو كانت تحبهم بشكل حقيقي؟ - سوف آكلهم ، حسنًا؟
- She eats clams until she's full. - Seriously, though.
- إنها تأكل البطلينوس حتى تكون ممتلئة. - على محمل الجد ، رغم ذلك.
- Well, so, - Until I'm full?
- حسنا ، إذن ، حتى أكون ممتلئًا؟
- what if she actually liked them? - Hyung In.
- ماذا لو كانت تحبهم بالفعل؟ - هيونغ في.
- I think you should sit here. - Why are you being so...
- أعتقد أنك يجب أن تجلس هنا. - لماذا أنت كذلك ...
I think he wants to talk to you.
أعتقد أنه يريد التحدث معك.
- She didn't like them, - Hey, Hyung In.
- لم تعجبهم ، - مهلا ، هيونغ في.
- but she ate this many clams. - Hey.
- لكنها أكلت هذا العديد من البطلينوس. - يا.
- Hey, tall guy. - Just talk to me.
- مهلا ، رجل طويل القامة. - فقط تحدث معي.
Why do you keep talking...
لماذا تستمر في الحديث ...
- as you look over here? - He's talking to Hyung In.
- كما تنظر هنا؟ - إنه يتحدث إلى هيونغ في.
Why are you talking to them?
لماذا تتحدث معهم؟
- Always. - Who are you talking to?
- دائماً. - من تتحدث؟
- He's just talking.
- دائماً. - إنه يتحدث فقط.
(Tripping)
(تعثر)
Talk to us.
تحدث إلينا.
- The viewers come first. - What's wrong with him?
- يأتي المشاهدون أولاً. - ما الخطأ معه؟
- Hey, what are you... - Why would you talk to...
- مهلا ، ماذا أنت ... - لماذا تتحدث ...
- the viewers? - What about us?
- المشاهدين؟ - ماذا عنا؟
The viewers come first.
يأتي المشاهدون أولاً.
- But why are you doing this? - Always.
- ولكن لماذا تفعل هذا؟ - دائماً.
- That's enough. - My gosh, seriously?
- هذا يكفي. - يا إلهي ، على محمل الجد؟
- Okay, that's enough. Come on. - Talking to those people...
- حسنًا ، هذا يكفي. تعال. - التحدث إلى هؤلاء الناس ...
- won't even get any screen time. - He keeps facing the front.
- لن يحصل حتى على أي وقت الشاشة. - يظل يواجه الجبهة.
- Why are you talking to the front? - You didn't even talk to us.
- لماذا تتحدث إلى الجبهة؟ - لم تتحدث إلينا حتى.
(As Jang Hoon speaks out about his beliefs)
(كما يتحدث يانغ هون عن معتقداته)
- Okay! - All right. Ready.
- تمام! - حسنًا. مستعد.
(The game begins.)
(تبدأ اللعبة.)
- Here it comes. - What is it?
- هنا يأتي. - ما هذا؟
(The time limit of 5 minutes begins.)
(يبدأ الحد الزمني لمدة 5 دقائق.)
- Enjoy it. - Hey.
- استمتع بها. - يا.
This is...
هذا هو...
What is that?
ما هذا؟
- What is it? - What is that?
- ما هذا؟ - ما هذا؟
- It's galbi. - One at a time.
- إنه جالبي. - واحد في وقت واحد.
Do I just have to stack it like this?
هل يجب علي فقط تكديسها هكذا؟
You can't flip it.
لا يمكنك قلبه.
(They must pile the plates in order without flipping them upside down.)
(يجب عليهم تكديس الألواح من أجل التقليب رأسًا على عقب.)
Gi Ru, don't eat the camera.
جي رو ، لا تأكل الكاميرا.
- What is it? - Jjajangmyeon.
- ما هذا؟ - Jjajangmyeon.
- The food just keeps on coming. - Jjajangmyeon sounds good.
- الطعام يستمر في المجيء. - jjajangmyeon تبدو جيدة.
We have to eat a lot.
علينا أن نأكل كثيرا.
Gi Ru, pick that up.
GI RU ، اختر ذلك.
Oh, I should eat too.
أوه ، يجب أن آكل أيضا.
(Macaron)
(معكرون)
(Shin Gi Ru empties three plates in a flash.)
(شين جي رو يفرغ ثلاث لوحات في فلاش.)
What is this?
ما هذا؟
- Do we win if we eat a lot or what? - They can eat together.
- هل نربح إذا كنا نأكل الكثير أم ماذا؟ - يمكنهم تناول الطعام معًا.
No, the team that piles up more plates,
لا ، الفريق الذي يربط المزيد من اللوحات ،
- but they can knock our tower over. - I see.
- لكن يمكنهم أن يطرقوا برجنا. - أرى.
- Here. Yes. - Is that a dumpling?
- هنا. نعم. - هل هذا زلابية؟
- Let's see. Me? - Eat it, you.
- دعونا نرى. أنا؟ - أكله ، أنت.
(The father and son duo)
(الأب والابن الثنائي)
Hold on a second.
تمسك بالثانية.
My son said, "Eat it, you."
قال ابني ، "أكلها ، أنت".
Act out like that again, and you'll get slapped.
تصرف هكذا مرة أخرى ، وستحصل على صفع.
Those aren't small portions. Is that a dumpling?
هذه ليست أجزاء صغيرة. هل هذا زلابية؟
- That's japchae. - It's not what I thought.
- هذا japchae. - هذا ليس ما فكرت به.
(Whining about it being too big)
(الأنين عن كونها كبيرة جدًا)
Here we go. That's japchae.
ها نحن. هذا japchae.
(He made his dad eat the big dumpling...)
(جعل والده يأكل الزلاب الكبير ...)
(and is enjoying the japchae he loves.)
(ويستمتع بـ Japchae الذي يحب.)
Our baby brother only eats what he likes.
شقيقنا الرضيع يأكل فقط ما يحبه.
- Exactly. - You're right.
- بالضبط. - أنت على حق.
Do you have any salt?
هل لديك أي ملح؟
What's that?
ما هذا؟
It's a piece of meat, but I'd like some salt.
إنها قطعة من اللحم ، لكنني أحب بعض الملح.
He wants salt.
يريد الملح.
(To the son complaining about his food,)
(للابن يشكو من طعامه ،)
(the dad says to chew properly.)
(يقول الأب للمضغ بشكل صحيح.)
Avoid eating things that are difficult to eat.
تجنب تناول الأشياء التي يصعب تناولها.
You need to eat faster.
تحتاج إلى تناول الطعام بشكل أسرع.
(The father and son take their time.)
(الآب والابن يأخذان وقتهما.)
- Hurry. - They just served a soup.
- عجل. - لقد خدموا فقط حساء.
- Eat things like this. - The plates differ in size.
- أكل أشياء مثل هذا. - اللوحات تختلف في الحجم.
- Is it the height or the number? - The height.
- هل هو الارتفاع أم الرقم؟ - الارتفاع.
- It's the height. - You need to stack it high.
- إنه الارتفاع. - تحتاج إلى تكديسها عالياً.
That looks tasty.
هذا يبدو لذيذ.
- Do we need to drink all the broth? - Yes.
- هل نحتاج إلى شرب كل المرق؟ - نعم.
But it's spicy.
لكنه حار.
- You need to stack those well. - Gi Ru.
- تحتاج إلى تكديس هؤلاء جيدا. - جي رو.
The plates and bowls aren't the same kind.
اللوحات والأوعية ليست من نفس النوع.
Hurry. Eat faster.
عجل. أكل أسرع.
- It's the height. - You need to stack it high.
- إنه الارتفاع. - تحتاج إلى تكديسها عالياً.
You need to stack as many plates as possible.
تحتاج إلى تكديس أكبر عدد ممكن من اللوحات.
So go with plates and bowls that are bigger.
لذا اذهب مع لوحات وأوعية أكبر.
- Do we need to drink all the broth? - They need to start...
- هل نحتاج إلى شرب كل المرق؟ - يحتاجون إلى البدء ...
- with bigger bowls on the bottom. - It's spicy.
- مع أوعية أكبر في القاع. - إنه حار.
You shouldn't have that, Jae Seok.
لا ينبغي أن يكون لديك ذلك ، جاي سوك.
Forget the dumpling.
ننسى الزلابية.
Don't have the dumpling.
لا تملك الزلابية.
Stack a flat plate. That's it, Gi Ru. No.
مكدس لوحة مسطحة. هذا كل شيء ، جي رو. لا.
- No, not at the bottom. - Make sure they're in order.
- لا ، ليس في القاع. - تأكد من أنهم في حالة جيدة.
- Jae Seok, you're next. - Stack a taller one.
- جاي سوك ، أنت التالي. - مكدس واحد أطول.
- Jae Seok, stack one on top. - That's right.
- جاي سوك ، كومة واحدة في الأعلى. - هذا صحيح.
It's getting taller.
إنه يزداد أطول.
They'll soon be throwing their bowls.
سيقومون قريبًا بإلقاء الأوعية الخاصة بهم.
- Nice. That's a good one. - Good.
- لطيف - جيد. هذا جيد. - جيد.
- Look at them. - Looking good, Gi Ru.
- انظر إليهم. - تبدو جيدة ، جي رو.
- Gi Ru! - Okay.
- مع ص! - لا.
My darling, you've got this.
حبيبي ، لقد حصلت على هذا.
Darling!
محبوب!
That's the bowl you should go for.
هذا هو الوعاء الذي يجب أن تذهب إليه.
(She had 7 while Jae Seok only had 2.)
(كان لديها 7 بينما كان جاي سوك فقط 2.)
Have the time of your life.
لديك وقت من حياتك.
(Because of Gi Ru,)
(بسبب جي رو ،)
(the Kim Family has fallen behind.)
(تعرضت عائلة كيم وراءها.)
(Jang Hoon, throw!)
(جانغ هون ، رمي!)
They'll now start throwing their plates.
سيبدأون الآن في إلقاء لوحاتهم.
Can we start throwing?
هل يمكننا البدء في الرمي؟
- Sure. - Can we throw these?
- بالتأكيد. - هل يمكننا رمي هذه؟
- Gi Ru, get out of the way. - They ate a lot.
- جي رو ، الخروج من الطريق. - أكلوا كثيرا.
- Gi Ru, move. - Can we start throwing?
- جي رو ، تحرك. - هل يمكننا البدء في الرمي؟
Are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
- Nice. - What is this?
- لطيف - جيد. - ما هذا؟
- She's good. - Good job.
- إنها جيدة. - أحسنت.
- Stand behind the line. - Move.
- الوقوف وراء الخط. - يتحرك.
(The legendary Seo Jang Hoon gets into position again.)
(يحصل SEO Jang Hoon الأسطوري على وضعه مرة أخرى.)
He used to be a basketball player.
اعتاد أن يكون لاعب كرة السلة.
He's a basketball player.
إنه لاعب كرة سلة.
Right.
يمين.
(He missed.)
(فاته.)
- Okay. - Good.
- تمام. - جيد.
(He immediately gets ready to throw another one.)
(يستعد على الفور لرمي واحد آخر.)
Don't stack that just yet. Wait for it.
لا تكدح ذلك بعد. انتظر ذلك.
(What about this time?)
(ماذا عن هذا الوقت؟)
(He misses again.)
(يفتقد مرة أخرى.)
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
- Didn't he play basketball?
- ألم يلعب كرة السلة؟ - ألم يلعب كرة السلة؟
(He wasted plates for no reason.)
(ضيع اللوحات دون سبب.)
(Swoosh)
(سووش)
(Jong Kook misses too.)
(يونغ كوك يخطئ أيضًا.)
If only we could stack this on top.
إذا استطعنا فقط تكديس هذا في الأعلى.
You need to stack more!
تحتاج إلى تكديس أكثر!
- That was close. - We already lost.
- كان ذلك قريبًا. - لقد فقدنا بالفعل.
(There's only 1 minute left.)
(لم يتبق سوى دقيقة واحدة.)
You have one minute left.
لديك دقيقة واحدة.
Eat faster and throw the plates.
أكل أسرع ورمي اللوحات.
We won. There's no way we can lose.
فزنا. لا توجد طريقة يمكن أن نخسرها.
We'll win unless they manage to knock our tower down.
سنفوز إلا إذا تمكنوا من ضرب برجنا لأسفل.
Jae Seok, you can stack more.
جاي سوك ، يمكنك تكديس المزيد.
(They are far ahead in the lead.)
(إنهم يتقدمون في المقدمة.)
This is tougher than it looks.
هذا أصعب مما يبدو.
Baby brother, throw it like you would a basketball.
أخي ، رميها كما لو كنت كرة سلة.
(Jang Hoon tries again.)
(يحاول Jang Hoon مرة أخرى.)
He's throwing one!
انه يرمي واحدة!
He's lost his basketball touch.
لقد فقد لمسة كرة السلة.
Just throw it.
فقط رميها.
(Throwing it in a different way!)
(رميها بطريقة مختلفة!)
(Well?)
(حسنًا؟)
He's lost his basketball touch.
لقد فقد لمسة كرة السلة.
(Bullseye)
(Bullseye)
(The tower comes tumbling down.)
(يأتي البرج ينهار.)
(Nice shot!)
(لقطة جميلة!)
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
Did you see that? Did you see it?
هل رأيت ذلك؟ هل رأيته؟
You're adorable.
أنت رائعتين.
(The baby brother is getting love he hasn't felt in a long time.)
(الأخ الصغير يحصل على الحب الذي لم يشعر به منذ فترة طويلة.)
Come on. Keep eating.
تعال. استمر في الأكل.
(The Yu Family quickly stacks more.)
(عائلة يو تتراكم بسرعة أكثر.)
- He played basketball. - He's a basketball player for sure.
- لعب كرة السلة. - إنه لاعب كرة سلة بالتأكيد.
We're still in the lead.
ما زلنا في المقدمة.
- You have 30 seconds left. - Nicely done.
- لديك 30 ثانية متبقية. - تم القيام به بشكل جيد.
Good job, baby brother.
عمل جيد ، أخي الطفل.
- Mr. Jeans played basketball. - Ours is still higher.
- لعب السيد جينز كرة السلة. - لا يزال لدينا أعلى.
- Ours is way higher.
- لا يزال لدينا أعلى. - لنا هو الطريق أعلى.
Have the soup and stack those bowls.
لديك الحساء وتكديس تلك الأوعية.
- Twenty seconds. - Jang Hoon, you don't have it.
- عشرين ثانية. - جانغ هون ، ليس لديك.
You have 20 seconds left.
لديك 20 ثانية متبقية.
Throw it.
رميها.
This is easy to knock down.
من السهل هدمه.
- Careful. That might topple down. - It's wobbly.
- حذر. قد يسقط ذلك. - إنه متذبذب.
- He won't hit it twice. - Ours is still higher.
- لن يضربها مرتين. - لا يزال لدينا أعلى.
He retired as a basketball player decades ago.
تقاعد كلاعب كرة السلة قبل عقود.
- My youngest, go for it. - Ten seconds remain.
- أصغر لي ، اذهب لذلك. - تبقى عشر ثوان.
- Ten seconds. Ten, nine... - Go for it.
- عشر ثوان. عشرة ، تسعة ... - اذهب لذلك.
- Ten seconds. Ten... - Go for it.
- عشر ثوان. عشرة ... - اذهب لذلك.
- Do better, will you? - Eight, seven...
- افعل أفضل ، أليس كذلك؟ - ثمانية ، سبعة ...
- Eight...
- افعل أفضل ، أليس كذلك؟ - ثمانية...
- Do better, will you? - Eight, seven,
- افعل أفضل ، أليس كذلك؟ - ثمانية ، سبعة ،
- six... - It's a miss. Keep eating.
- ستة ... - إنها ملكة جمال. استمر في الأكل.
- Have a soup. - He's not even aiming.
- لديك حساء. - إنه لا يهدف حتى.
- He's lost his touch. Keep eating! - Five, four...
- لقد فقد لمسه. استمر في الأكل! - خمسة ، أربعة ...
- Six, five, four... - He's lost his touch. Keep eating!
- ستة ، خمسة ، أربعة ... - لقد فقد لمسة. استمر في الأكل!
(Thud!)
(جلجل!)
Oh, no!
أوه ، لا!
(Is it about to topple over?)
(هل هو على وشك الإطاحة؟)
Three, two...
ثلاثة ، اثنان ...
(Some are still left!)
(لا يزال البعض ترك!)
- Nice. - Okay!
- لطيف - جيد. - تمام!
(Jae Seok and Gi Ru win.)
(جاي سوك و GI RU WIN.)
There's no need to attack. Just keep eating.
ليست هناك حاجة للهجوم. فقط استمر في الأكل.
- Yes, let's eat. - You just have to keep eating.
- نعم ، دعونا نأكل. - عليك فقط مواصلة الأكل.
(Jong Kook and Jang Hoon lose.)
(يخسر جونج كوك وجانغ هون.)
You couldn't even do that?
لا يمكنك حتى فعل ذلك؟
- You did great. - Seriously.
- لقد فعلت بشكل رائع. - بجد.
It was fun.
كان ممتعا.
- Why couldn't you hit it? - That's not it.
- لماذا لم تستطع ضربها؟ - هذا ليس هو.
- They couldn't hit our tower. - How were they so bad at this?
- لم يتمكنوا من ضرب برجنا. - كيف كانت سيئة للغاية في هذا؟
- Why couldn't you hit it? - They didn't eat much either.
- لماذا لم تستطع ضربها؟ - لم يأكلوا كثيرًا أيضًا.
How is this so hard?
كيف هذا صعب جدا؟
Are you sure Jang Hoon played basketball for years?
هل أنت متأكد من أن Jang Hoon لعب كرة السلة لسنوات؟
The height difference is 10cm.
فرق الارتفاع هو 10 سم.
We won by a landslide.
فزنا من قبل انهيار أرضي.
- Is that all you ate? - You just had to toss this.
- هل هذا كل ما أكلته؟ - كان عليك فقط أن ترمي هذا.
- Even I'd be able to hit it. - He retired ages ago.
- حتى سأكون قادرا على ضربها. - تقاعد منذ العصور.
Eat the food in the black bowls.
تناول الطعام في الأوعية السوداء.
The black bowls are easier to throw.
الأوعية السوداء أسهل في رميها.
Really? Are they easier to throw?
حقًا؟ هل هم أسهل في رمي؟
(Round 2: Seok Sam, Ye Eun versus Ji Hyo, Shindong)
(الجولة 2: سوك سام ، أيها آيات جيو ، شيندونغ)
I see a macaron.
أرى معكرون.
- Shindong... - I bet he can eat a lot.
- Shindong ... - أراهن أنه يمكن أن يأكل كثيرًا.
He's good at physical activities.
إنه جيد في الأنشطة البدنية.
- I think he'll be good at this. - I think so too.
- أعتقد أنه سيكون جيدًا في هذا. - أعتقد ذلك أيضًا.
- I'm suddenly hungry. - Do you have good aim?
- أنا جائع فجأة. - هل لديك هدف جيد؟
Get ready.
استعد.
(Their 5 minutes begin.)
(تبدأ 5 دقائق.)
(Shindong immediately picks up cold buckwheat noodles.)
(Shindong يلتقط على الفور المعكرونة الباردة الحنطة السوداء.)
That's it. Looking good, Shindong.
هذا كل شيء. تبدو جيدة ، Shindong.
- Nice. - That's it, Shindong.
- لطيف - جيد. - هذا كل شيء ، شيندونغ.
(He clears a bowl in 3 seconds.)
(يمسح وعاء في 3 ثوان.)
Stack them in one corner to make it harder for them.
تكديسهم في زاوية واحدة لجعل الأمر أكثر صعوبة بالنسبة لهم.
- That's it. Keep it up. - You've got this.
- هذا كل شيء. استمر. - لقد حصلت على هذا.
- Just keep eating. - Since they could be pushed back.
- فقط استمر في الأكل. - لأنه يمكن دفعها إلى الوراء.
Keep eating.
استمر في الأكل.
(Ji Hyo eats a fried tofu rice ball that's the size of her face.)
(تأكل جي هيو كرة أرز التوفو المقلية بحجم وجهها.)
- She's small but... - Look at her eat.
- إنها صغيرة ولكن ... - انظر إليها تأكل.
- Looking good. - Good job.
- تبدو جيدة. - أحسنت.
Nicely done, Shindong.
تم القيام به بشكل جيد ، Shindong.
(Looking cool)
(تبدو باردة)
- The Baebullians... - "Baebully Hills."
- The Baebullians ... - "Baebully Hills."
Shindong's smaller, but he's still eating a lot.
شيندونغ أصغر ، لكنه لا يزال يأكل الكثير.
He must've been born with the gene.
يجب أن يولد مع الجين.
(Toppling over)
(تجاوزت)
Okay.
تمام.
(He knocks down the tower he stacked.)
(انه يقرع البرج المكدسة.)
You can stack them again.
يمكنك تكديسهم مرة أخرى.
- You can't. - That's not allowed.
- لا يمكنك. - هذا غير مسموح به.
No way. You can't use what's on the ground.
مستحيل. لا يمكنك استخدام ما هو على الأرض.
Can't you throw what's on the ground?
ألا يمكنك رمي ما على الأرض؟
That's not allowed!
هذا غير مسموح به!
- Can't we throw them? - So stack them carefully.
- ألا يمكننا رميهم؟ - لذا تكدسهم بعناية.
Mister, come on.
مستر ، هيا.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
(Meanwhile, Chungju Ji and Jee)
(وفي الوقت نفسه ، تشونغجو جي وجي)
If you can't eat much, just think about throwing the plates.
إذا كنت لا تستطيع أن تأكل كثيرًا ، فما عليك سوى التفكير في رمي اللوحات.
- Don't stress out over it. - She's right.
- لا تشدد على ذلك. - إنها على حق.
Gosh, this chilled cucumber soup!
يا إلهي ، هذا حساء الخيار المبرد!
- Isn't it tasty? - It's tasty.
- أليس كذلك لذيذ؟ - إنه لذيذ.
(Udon)
(أودون)
Ye Eun, don't savor the food and stack the plates.
أيها ايون ، لا تتذوق الطعام وتكديس الألواح.
- That's good. - Stack them in order.
- هذا جيد. - تكديسهم بالترتيب.
Stack them in order.
تكدسهم بالترتيب.
Go with bowl, plate, bowl, and plate.
اذهب مع الوعاء واللوحة والوعاء واللوحة.
(They're advised to alternate between bowls and plates.)
(نصحوا بالتناوب بين الأوعية واللوحات.)
Stack them in order.
تكدسهم بالترتيب.
Looking good.
تبدو جيدة.
Go with a bowl. There you go.
اذهب مع وعاء. هناك تذهب.
You're doing great.
أنت بخير.
- Take that one. The soup bowl. - Eat that.
- خذ هذا. وعاء الحساء. - أكل ذلك.
Keep eating.
استمر في الأكل.
Have a soup.
لديك حساء.
(Slip)
(ينزلق)
(Seok Sam lost hold of his pickled radish.)
(خسر سوك سام من الفجل المخلل.)
Shouldn't he eat what he dropped?
ألا يجب أن يأكل ما أسقطه؟
- You should eat what you dropped. - Eat what you dropped!
- يجب أن تأكل ما أسقطته. - أكل ما أسقطته!
- That shouldn't count. - Come on!
- لا ينبغي أن يحسب. - تعال!
- You should eat it. - What's wrong?
- يجب أن تأكله. - ما هو الخطأ؟
- That shouldn't count. - Lose that plate.
- لا ينبغي أن يحسب. - تفقد تلك اللوحة.
- Take that off.
- تفقد تلك اللوحة. - خذ هذا.
- You're a Baebullian. - That's right.
- أنت baebullian. - هذا صحيح.
You should live up to the name and eat more.
يجب أن ترقى إلى مستوى الاسم وتناول أكثر.
- Baebullians. - "Baebully Hills."
- Baebullians. - "تلال بيبلي".
- Stack them well. - Make sure the bottom is secure.
- تكديسهم جيدًا. - تأكد من أن القاع آمن.
Ye Eun, don't savor the food and stack more plates.
أيها ايون ، لا تتذوق الطعام وتكديس المزيد من اللوحات.
(Inhaling the food without hesitating)
(استنشاق الطعام دون تردد)
(Ji Ye Eun, the Shin Gi Ru of Running Man)
(جي يي يون ، شين جي رو من الجري)
After Ye Eun is done, stack the bowl,
بعد الانتهاء من eun ، تكديس الوعاء ،
and then Seok Jin's plate.
ثم صفيحة سوك جين.
Gosh, that's sour.
يا إلهي ، هذا حامض.
Hurry up and stack more plates!
اسرع وتكديس المزيد من اللوحات!
Shindong, throw one right about now.
Shindong ، رمي واحدة على اليمين الآن.
(Attacking the fish cake ball without taking a break)
(مهاجمة كرة كعكة السمك دون أخذ قسط من الراحة)
Mr. Jeans, throw better yourself.
السيد جينز ، رمي نفسك بشكل أفضل.
(While Ye Eun focuses on defense,)
(بينما تركز أيها ايون على الدفاع ،)
(Seok Sam plays offense.)
(سوك سام يلعب جريمة.)
- Move out of the way. - He stepped on the line.
- الخروج من الطريق. - صعد على الخط.
- You stepped on the line.
- صعد على الخط. - صعدت على الخط.
- Okay.
- صعدت على الخط. - تمام.
- Throw it.
- رميها. - رميها.
- Aim for the center. - Throw it hard.
- هدف للمركز. - رميها بشدة.
- He's terrible. - Put more muscle into it!
- إنه فظيع. - ضع المزيد من العضلات فيه!
You should've let it soar.
يجب أن تدعها ترتفع.
- By the way... - Throw one.
- بالمناسبة ... - رمي واحد.
The food is delicious.
الطعام لذيذ.
Throw one already.
رمي واحدة بالفعل.
(A piece of rolled omelet)
(قطعة من عجة ملفوفة)
- What the heck? - No, not like that.
- ما هيك؟ - لا ، ليس هكذا.
- Are you kidding me? - What's wrong?
- هل تمزح معي؟ - ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
- What is it? - What's wrong?
- ما هذا؟ - ما هو الخطأ؟
Who put mustard in the rolled omelet?
من وضع الخردل في عجة المدحونة؟
(He chose the mustard bomb hidden among the food.)
(اختار قنبلة الخردل المخبأة بين الطعام.)
- Watch it. - You stepped on the line.
- شاهده. - صعدت على الخط.
- Seriously? - Come on!
- بجد؟ - تعال!
Nice!
لطيف - جيد!
(The tower toppled over even though he hit the stand.)
(ألقى البرج على الرغم من أنه ضرب الموقف.)
(Ye Eun eats while Seok Sam throws.)
(أيها يون يأكل بينما سوك سام رميات.)
(Their strategy worked.)
(عملت استراتيجيتهم.)
You shouldn't stack them like that.
يجب ألا تكدسهم هكذا.
- Okay, we won. - Nice.
- حسنًا ، فزنا. - لطيف - جيد.
Ji Hyo!
جي هيو!
(She wasted three plates trying to get revenge.)
(ضيعت ثلاث لوحات تحاول الانتقام.)
- Stop it! - Look at her.
- توقف! - انظر إليها.
We've won. It's done.
لقد فزنا. لقد تم.
Stop it!
توقف!
- How are you so bad at this? - Aim at that.
- كيف حالك سيئة للغاية في هذا؟ - تهدف إلى ذلك.
- Try to hit the stand. - That won't work.
- حاول أن تصل إلى الموقف. - هذا لن ينجح.
- Jang Hoon, come on. - Mr. Jeans, stay out of it.
- جانغ هون ، هيا. - السيد جينز ، ابق خارجها.
- Stay out of it. - What's your problem?
- ابق خارجها. - ما هي مشكلتك؟
I'm sorry to say this,
أنا آسف لقول هذا ،
but I'm the one who has hit the most so far.
لكنني الشخص الذي ضرب أكثر حتى الآن.
- That's true. - Yes!
- هذا صحيح. - نعم!
(Ji Hyo managed to hit the stand as well.)
(تمكنت جي هيو من ضرب المنصة كذلك.)
- No! - Yes!
- لا! - نعم!
That's it!
هذا كل شيء!
- Just aim for the stand. - We'll win anyway.
- مجرد هدف للمنف. - سنفوز على أي حال.
We've already won.
لقد فزنا بالفعل.
Stack it.
مكدسها.
(Food Fighter stacks another empty plate right away.)
(Food Fighter يتراكم لوحة فارغة أخرى على الفور.)
You startled me.
لقد أذهلتني.
- You have 30 seconds left. - Finish the food first.
- لديك 30 ثانية متبقية. - إنهاء الطعام أولاً.
- All right. - You need to keep throwing now.
- حسنًا. - تحتاج إلى الاستمرار في الرمي الآن.
Throw. It's time to throw.
يرمي. حان الوقت لرمي.
- Hang in there. - Throw one.
- شنق هناك. - رمي واحد.
Shindong, aim well.
Shindong ، هدف جيد.
- Okay! - Throw another one.
- تمام! - رمي واحدة أخرى.
- You have 20 seconds left. - Keep throwing!
- لديك 20 ثانية متبقية. - استمر في الرمي!
Focus, darn it!
التركيز ، الرتق!
- Yes! - That's it!
- نعم! - هذا كل شيء!
(Right before the game ended)
(قبل انتهاء اللعبة مباشرة)
(Food Fighter's tower of plates came crashing down.)
(جاء برج اللوحات المقاتلة الغذائية.)
- Eat more. Stack more. - Hang in there.
- أكل أكثر. كومة أكثر. - شنق هناك.
- Eat more. - Eat more!
- أكل أكثر. - أكل أكثر!
- Nice! - Eat faster!
- لطيف - جيد! - أكل أسرع!
- Ten, nine... - Find a tall one.
- عشرة ، تسعة ... - ابحث عن واحد طويل.
- Eight. - There aren't any.
- ثمانية. - ليس هناك أي.
- Seven. - We've got this.
- سبعة. - لدينا هذا.
Stack it!
مكدسها!
- Five. - Put it down!
- خمسة. - ضعه!
- Four. Three. - A tall one!
- أربعة. ثلاثة. - واحد طويل!
- Two. - Isn't there a tall one?
- اثنين. - أليس هناك واحد طويل؟
Grab anything.
احصل على أي شيء.
- Okay. That's it. - You got it!
- تمام. هذا كل شيء. - لقد حصلت عليه!
- Oh, nice. - You did it.
- أوه ، لطيف. - لقد فعلت ذلك.
- Darn it. - When did they stack those?
- الرتق. - متى تكدس هؤلاء؟
- I know, right? - We did it.
- أنا أوافق؟ - فعلنا ذلك.
- Gosh, that was great. - Ji Ye Eun...
- يا إلهي ، كان ذلك رائعًا. - جي يي يون ...
(The whistle)
(صافرة)
- put it down after the whistle. - There weren't any tall ones.
- ضعه بعد صافرة. - لم يكن هناك أي منها طويل القامة.
Please take the last one out.
من فضلك خذ آخر واحد.
- Ji Ye Eun put it down... - I think...
- جي يي يون وضعها ... - أعتقد ...
after the whistle.
بعد صافرة.
You have great eyesight. You see everything, don't you?
لديك بصر كبير. ترى كل شيء ، أليس كذلك؟
You can't play basketball with bad eyesight.
لا يمكنك لعب كرة السلة ببصر سيئ.
- Oh, that's right. - Mister.
- أوه ، هذا صحيح. - سيد.
- You're totally like a chameleon...
- أنت تمامًا مثل الحرباء ... - سيد.
- Hey, you can't come across! - Mister, are you the referee?
- مهلا ، لا يمكنك أن تصادف! - مستر ، هل أنت الحكم؟
Are you the referee or something?
هل أنت الحكم أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
- Are you the referee? - You can't come across this line.
- هل أنت الحكم؟ - لا يمكنك أن تصادف هذا الخط.
- Mister. - Of course.
- سيد. - بالطبع.
- You can't come across. - Don't treat our kid like that.
- لا يمكنك أن تصادف. - لا تعامل طفلنا من هذا القبيل.
They're all pretty similar, right?
انهم جميعا متشابهة جدا ، أليس كذلك؟
They're too thin.
إنهم رفيعون جدًا.
Sweetie, are you taking a moment to eat lunch?
حبيبتي ، هل تأخذ لحظة لتناول الغداء؟
- No. - Are you eating lunch?
- لا. - هل تتناول الغداء؟
- Excuse me, Gi Ru. - Don't eat that.
- معذرة ، جي رو. - لا تأكل ذلك.
- What are you doing right now? - I mean...
- ماذا تفعل الآن؟ - أعني...
- Why are you eating dessert? - I was wondering what was going on.
- لماذا تأكل الحلوى؟ - كنت أتساءل ما الذي كان يجري.
I'm sorry, but are you on vacation?
أنا آسف ، لكن هل أنت في إجازة؟
(Embarrassed)
(مُحرَج)
Do you think we're at a hotel buffet right now?
هل تعتقد أننا في بوفيه فندق الآن؟
Hey, Locust. The two bucktoothed guys should go.
مهلا ، الجراد. يجب أن يذهب اثنين من الرجال bucktoothed.
- It was this one. - This.
- كان هذا واحد. - هذا.
- This or this. - Don't go for these.
- هذا أو هذا. - لا تذهب لهذه.
- Don't go for those? - No.
- لا تذهب لهؤلاء؟ - لا.
Daniel, eat the ones in the soup bowls.
دانيال ، أكل تلك الموجودة في أوعية الحساء.
(The final round starts.)
(تبدأ الجولة النهائية.)
- Just eat this one first. - This?
- فقط أكل هذا أولاً. - هذا؟
Eat.
يأكل.
(Haha's strategy: build a tall tower out of soup bowls)
(استراتيجية هاها: بناء برج طويل من أوعية الحساء)
- All right. Good. - Nice.
- حسنًا. جيد. - لطيف - جيد.
- Good. That's better. - Should I try throwing it once?
- جيد. هذا أفضل. - هل يجب أن أحاول رميها مرة واحدة؟
Okay!
تمام!
(They succeed right away.)
(ينجحون على الفور.)
(Daniel succeeded in one try!)
(نجح دانيال في محاولة واحدة!)
- Good job! - Hey, Daniel!
- أحسنت! - مهلا ، دانيال!
- That was awesome. - So awesome.
- كان ذلك رائعًا. - رائع جدا.
(Ssaebssaeb's counterattack!)
(الهجوم المضاد لـ SSAEBSSAEB!)
- That's okay. - What was that?
- هذا جيد. - ماذا كان هذا؟
- It's okay. - Hey.
- لا بأس. - يا.
- Ssaebssaeb went over the line. - He stepped over the line.
- ذهب ssaebssaeb على الخط. - صعد فوق الخط.
He threw it with his foot here.
ألقى به بقدمه هنا.
- He stepped over it! - It's fine.
- صعد فوقه! - لا بأس.
We can do a bench cleaner.
يمكننا أن نفعل منظف مقعد.
- What's a bench cleaner? - A bench cleaner?
- ما هو منظف مقاعد البدلاء؟ - منظف مقعد؟
(A bench cleaner?)
(منظف مقعد؟)
- Bench cleaning? - Are you wiping them clean?
- تنظيف مقاعد البدلاء؟ - هل تمسحهم نظيفًا؟
- I don't know. Anyway... - It's bench clearing.
- لا أعرف. على أي حال ... - إنه مقعد المقعد.
- Anyway, do the bench thing. - What was that?
- على أي حال ، افعل الشيء. - ماذا كان هذا؟
You have 20 seconds left.
لديك 20 ثانية متبقية.
(Now, they only have 20 seconds left!)
(الآن ، لديهم 20 ثانية فقط متبقية!)
- Haha, throw it. - Good. Ours is taller.
- هاها ، رميها. - جيد. لنا أطول.
- Go for it. - Throw it.
- أذهب خلفها. - رميها.
You have ten seconds left.
لديك عشر ثوان متبقية.
- No, Niel should throw. - Ten.
- لا ، يجب على نيل رمي. - عشرة.
- Hit the table! - Niel, you should throw.
- ضرب الطاولة! - نيل ، يجب أن ترمي.
- Eight. - The table!
- ثمانية. - الجدول!
- We should throw too. - Seven. Six. Five.
- يجب أن نرمي أيضا. - سبعة. ستة. خمسة.
- Right now! Hit it! - Just one more.
- الآن! ضربها! - واحد فقط.
- Three. - Eat more!
- ثلاثة. - أكل أكثر!
(Haha throws his last plate.)
(هاها يلقي طبقه الأخير.)
- Okay! That's good! - Eat more!
- تمام! هذا جيد! - أكل أكثر!
- No, don't do that. That's it. - Two...
- لا ، لا تفعل ذلك. هذا كل شيء. - اثنين...
- One. - Okay.
- واحد. - تمام.
- That's it. - Hey, that was awesome.
- هذا كل شيء. - مهلا ، كان ذلك رائعًا.
- I told you to hit the table. - That was awesome.
- قلت لك أن تضغط على الطاولة. - كان ذلك رائعًا.
- That was so good. - Good job.
- كان ذلك جيدًا جدًا. - أحسنت.
- You have to hit the table. - Gosh, we were so close.
- عليك أن تضغط على الطاولة. - يا إلهي ، كنا قريبين جدا.
- It only took one blow. - Right.
- استغرق الأمر ضربة واحدة فقط. - يمين.
- My goodness. - Hitting the table was a good idea.
- يا إلهي. - كان ضرب الطاولة فكرة جيدة.
Daniel and Haha, our warriors...
دانيال وهاها ، محاربينا ...
- You guys did great. - Warriors.
- يا رفاق فعلت رائعا. - المحاربين.
- We played three rounds. - That was so close.
- لعبنا ثلاث جولات. - كان ذلك قريبًا جدًا.
It's lunchtime after this, so we'll give it to you then.
إنه وقت الغداء بعد هذا ، لذلك سنعطيه لك بعد ذلك.
- Lunch... - Look over there.
- غداء ... - انظر هناك.
Excuse me. We're having lunch later on.
اعذرني. نتناول الغداء لاحقًا.
- Oh, isn't this our lunch? - No.
- أوه ، أليس هذا غداءنا؟ - لا.
Is there a separate lunch? Sorry.
هل هناك غداء منفصل؟ آسف.
(Taking the repeat offender away immediately)
(أخذ الجاني المتكرر على الفور)
- Then, who will eat all that food? - Nice.
- إذن ، من سيأكل كل هذا الطعام؟ - لطيف - جيد.
- Don't worry about it. - My goodness.
- لا تقلق بشأن هذا. - يا إلهي.
- Gosh, that was spicy. - Jae Seok's team,
- يا إلهي ، كان ذلك حارًا. - فريق جاي سوك ،
your total for the 3 rounds was 23cm.
وكان إجمالي لجولات 3 23 سم.
- My goodness. - That's not a lot.
- يا إلهي. - هذا ليس كثيرًا.
- Jong Kook's team had 41cm. - Yes!
- كان فريق Jong Kook 41 سم. - نعم!
- We lost big time. - They didn't even come close!
- فقدنا الوقت الكبير. - لم يقتربوا حتى!
(Chewing furiously)
(مضغ غاضب)
My gosh.
يا إلهي.
- They were so critical about me, - At the end...
- لقد كانوا حاسمين للغاية بالنسبة لي ، - في النهاية ...
because I couldn't knock over the pile of plates.
لأنني لم أستطع ضرب كومة اللوحات.
They couldn't hit anything, though.
لم يتمكنوا من ضرب أي شيء.
Who are you talking to?
مع من تتحدث؟
- The viewers! - Why are you talking to the front?
- المشاهدين! - لماذا تتحدث إلى الجبهة؟
- The frame is so cool. - This time,
- الإطار بارد جدا. - هذه المرة ،
I was talking to Shindong.
كنت أتحدث مع شيندونغ.
- Oh, were you talking to me? - Gosh, it's so cool.
- أوه ، هل كنت تتحدث معي؟ - يا إلهي ، إنه رائع جدًا.
We said the judging would be based on special standards.
قلنا أن الحكم سيستند إلى معايير خاصة.
- This will help a lot. - Is that right? Okay!
- هذا سوف يساعد كثيرا. - هل هذا صحيح؟ تمام!
Only one person from the family can take this.
شخص واحد فقط من العائلة يمكنه أخذ هذا.
- You can choose who it will be. - Is that right?
- يمكنك اختيار من سيكون. - هل هذا صحيح؟
- Right now? - Yes.
- الآن؟ - نعم.
First, the dad,
أولا ، الأب ،
- as the pillar of the family, - Yes?
- بصفتها عمود الأسرة ، - نعم؟
should survive...
يجب البقاء ...
- What? Then... - so that later on...
- ماذا؟ ثم ... - لذلك في وقت لاحق ...
- Dad is getting greedy. - They're fighting.
- أبي يزداد الجشع. - إنهم يقاتلون.
If we give it to someone who can't draw,
إذا قدمناها لشخص لا يستطيع الرسم ،
it'll only lower the average. It's better to boost our odds.
سوف يقلل فقط من المتوسط. من الأفضل تعزيز احتمالاتنا.
- No, but those who can't draw... - Excuse me.
- لا ، لكن أولئك الذين لا يستطيعون الرسم ... - عفوا.
- How much longer must we watch? - Putting it in the frame will be...
- كم من الوقت يجب أن نشاهد؟ - وضعه في الإطار سيكون ...
- You're just taking a mere thing! - I know!
- أنت فقط تأخذ شيء! - أنا أعرف!
My daughter-in-law is done digesting!
تم تنفيذ زوجتي في الهضم!
She might eat the plate at this rate!
قد تأكل اللوحة بهذا المعدل!
My daughter-in-law is done digesting now!
تم إنجاز زوجتي في الهضم الآن!
Don't you guys usually let the guest have the benefit?
ألا تدعكم عادةً ما تسمح للضيف بالفائدة؟
- No, we don't do that. - You don't?
- لا ، نحن لا نفعل ذلك. - لم تكن؟
- Rock-paper-scissors!
-مقص الورق الصخور! -مقص الورق الصخور!
- Okay, good. Rock-paper-scissors!
- حسنا ، جيد. مقص الورق الصخور! -مقص الورق الصخور!
- Okay! - Okay, you take it.
- تمام! - حسنًا ، تأخذها.
- It's fine. - Then, Haha...
- لا بأس. - ثم ، هاها ...
will take the frame.
سوف يأخذ الإطار.
- Only Haha's picture will be... - Hey, today...
- فقط صورة هاها ستكون ... - مهلا ، اليوم ...
- put in the frame when it's done. - We should do...
- ضع في الإطار عندما يتم ذلك. - يجب أن نفعل ...
This is so delicious.
هذا لذيذ جدا.
Goodness, I'm full.
يا إلهي ، أنا ممتلئ.
What could it be?
ماذا يمكن أن يكون؟
- Okay, what is this now? Curling? - What is it?
- حسنًا ، ما هذا الآن؟ الشباك؟ - ما هذا؟
- Curling! - What is this?
- الشباك! - ما هذا؟
- It's curling. - Gosh, they put something...
- إنه تجعيد. - يا إلهي ، وضعوا شيئا ...
- on the floor. - Curling was fun last time.
- على الأرض. - كان الشباك ممتعًا آخر مرة.
I don't think Jang Hoon will fit.
لا أعتقد أن Jang Hoon سوف يناسب.
Curling.
الشباك.
- Curling is fun. - It's curling.
- الشباك ممتع. - إنه تجعيد.
- It sounds fun. - Curling is fun.
- يبدو ممتعا. - الشباك ممتع.
Gosh, I'm good at physical activities.
يا إلهي ، أنا جيد في الأنشطة البدنية.
- Curling is fun. - Curling.
- الشباك ممتع. - الشباك.
Where did Jang Hoon go?
أين ذهب يانغ هون؟
- Jang... - Where is our youngest?
- جانغ ... - أين أصغرنا؟
(By the way, the Kim family's youngest is nowhere to be seen.)
(بالمناسبة ، فإن أصغر عائلة كيم ليس في أي مكان يمكن رؤيته.)
Where did our youngest go? Hey, have you seen him?
أين ذهب أصغرنا؟ مهلا ، هل رأيته؟
The youngest ran away from home.
هرب الأصغر من المنزل.
- The youngest... - Oh, your youngest...
- الأصغر ... - أوه ، أصغرك ...
He's nowhere to be seen.
إنه ليس في أي مكان يمكن رؤيته.
- Hey, Dad. - Right when he arrives...
- مهلا أبي. - الحق عندما يصل ...
Should we pretend to be playing?
هل يجب أن نتظاهر بأن نلعب؟
- A few of us should go. - Yes, go.
- يجب أن يذهب عدد قليل منا. - نعم ، اذهب.
- Let's cheer. - That sounds like fun.
- دعونا نبهج. - هذا يبدو وكأنه متعة.
- I bet he never experienced this. - That sounds fun.
- أراهن أنه لم يختبر هذا أبدًا. - هذا يبدو ممتعا.
- A few of us should go. - It sounds like fun.
- يجب أن يذهب عدد قليل منا. - يبدو الأمر ممتعًا.
- Go over there. - The same team should push.
- اذهب إلى هناك. - يجب أن يدفع الفريق نفسه.
(While using the restroom, the giant becomes the pranksters' target .)
(أثناء استخدام الحمام ، يصبح العملاق هدف المخادع.)
- Cheer loudly when he comes in. - The same team should push.
- ابتهج بصوت عالٍ عندما يأتي. - يجب أن يدفع الفريق نفسه.
- Cheer. - Let's go!
- تهتف. - دعنا نذهب!
All right. Let's go.
حسنًا. دعنا نذهب.
- Here we go. - Let's go!
- ها نحن. - دعنا نذهب!
- I'll be in here.
- دعنا نذهب! - سأكون هنا.
- Be careful. Don't fall over. - I'll go like this.
- احرص. لا تسقط. - سأذهب هكذا.
- Let's go!
- دعنا نذهب! - دعنا نذهب!
Let's do this!
دعونا نفعل هذا!
Okay, go! Hey.
حسنًا ، اذهب! يا.
- Let's go! - Hey!
- دعنا نذهب! - يا!
- In 1, 2, 3. - Okay!
- في 1 ، 2 ، 3. - حسنًا!
- Block him. - Let's go!
- منعه. - دعنا نذهب!
(How will he react to this absurd situation?)
(كيف سيتفاعل مع هذا الوضع السخيف؟)
- Let's go! - Come on!
- دعنا نذهب! - تعال!
- We can do it!
- دعنا نذهب! - يمكننا أن نفعل ذلك!
- That's it! Down the middle! - Yes!
- هذا كل شيء! أسفل الوسط! - نعم!
(After relieving himself and feeling refreshed,)
(بعد تخفيف نفسه والشعور بالانتعاش ،)
(the shoot has already begun.)
(بدأ إطلاق النار بالفعل.)
- So close! - Yes!
- قريب جدا! - نعم!
(Feeling awkward)
(الشعور بالحرج)
(Everyone is having a blast without Jang Hoon.)
(الجميع يعاني من انفجار بدون Jang Hoon.)
Is it okay if we fall over?
هل هو بخير إذا سقطنا؟
- Is it okay if we fall over? - Are you okay?
- هل هو بخير إذا سقطنا؟ - هل أنت بخير؟
- He's totally fine. - What is this?
- إنه بخير تمامًا. - ما هذا؟
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
- Where did you go? - Hey, youngest guy!
- أين ذهبت؟ - مهلا ، أصغر رجل!
- Why were you so late? - I mean...
- لماذا تأخرت جدا؟ - أعني...
We're in the middle of the shoot.
نحن في منتصف إطلاق النار.
You can't come in when we're shooting. Leave if you want to,
لا يمكنك المجيء عندما نطلق النار. اترك إذا كنت تريد ،
or come in early if you're going to join us.
أو تأتي مبكرًا إذا كنت ستنضم إلينا.
- We can start over now. - Apologize!
- يمكننا أن نبدأ من جديد. - يعتذر!
- Get up. Apologize properly, punk! - Hang on.
- استيقظ. اعتذر بشكل صحيح ، فاسق! - انتظر.
- What is going on? I will. - Apologize, punk!
- ما الذي يجري؟ أنا سوف. - اعتذر ، فاسق!
- Apologize. - Hey, why are you so darn rude?
- يعتذر. - مهلا ، لماذا أنت وقح جدا؟
He hit him.
ضربه.
- That's it. Good job. - Are you crazy?
- هذا كل شيء. أحسنت. - هل أنت مجنون؟
Seriously.
بجد.
That's it. Yes, that's how an older brother should act.
هذا كل شيء. نعم ، هكذا يجب أن يتصرف الأخ الأكبر.
- I'm really sorry. - Hey.
- أنا حقا آسف. - يا.
Why would you pretend to hit him just to swear at him for real?
لماذا تتظاهر بأن تضربه فقط لأقسم عليه بشكل حقيقي؟
- Hey, what is this? - You just wanted to swear.
- مهلا ، ما هذا؟ - أردت فقط أن أقسم.
- What are you doing? - He just wanted to...
- ماذا تفعل؟ - أراد فقط ...
You're really happy to see me after a long time apart, aren't you?
أنت سعيد حقًا برؤيتي بعد فترة طويلة عن بعضها البعض ، أليس كذلك؟
It's good to see you.
من الجيد رؤيتك.
Gosh, that's funny.
يا إلهي ، هذا مضحك.
With colors, the most important part of the drawing, on the line,
مع الألوان ، الجزء الأكثر أهمية في الرسم ، على الخط ،
- That's right. - we'll start...
- هذا صحيح. - سنبدأ ...
- the Colorful Curling mission. - Okay.
- مهمة الشباك الملونة. - تمام.
When drawing the picture that will decide who wins or loses in the end,
عند رسم الصورة التي ستقرر من يفوز أو يخسر في النهاية ،
the basic colors you will be given are black and light peach.
الألوان الأساسية التي ستحصل عليها هي الأسود والخوخ الخفيف.
Just those two.
فقط هذين.
This is how you can win extra colors.
هذه هي الطريقة التي يمكنك بها الفوز بألوان إضافية.
You will get in the rubber tubs and play human curling.
سوف تحصل في أحواض المطاط ولعب الشباك البشرية.
You will gain the number of colors...
سوف تكتسب عدد الألوان ...
written on the spot...
مكتوب على الفور ...
where your tub ends up.
حيث ينتهي حوضك.
However, if you stop in the sections where it says silver,
ومع ذلك ، إذا توقفت في الأقسام التي تقول فيها الفضة ،
you can only get silver as your extra color.
يمكنك فقط الحصول على الفضة كل لونك الإضافي.
- Also, - You can express a lot with silver.
- أيضًا ، - يمكنك التعبير كثيرًا عن الفضة.
if you go completely off the curling board,
إذا خرجت تمامًا عن لوحة الشباك ،
you may only draw with black and light peach,
يمكنك فقط الرسم مع الخوخ الأسود والخفيف ،
the basic colors you will be provided with.
الألوان الأساسية التي سيتم تزويدك بها.
Light peach?
الخوخ الخفيف؟
Anyway, this will be an individual match.
على أي حال ، ستكون هذه مباراة فردية.
- Individually. - Okay, individual.
- بشكل فردي. - حسنًا ، فرد.
Please choose the 3 people who will play in the 1st round,
الرجاء اختيار الأشخاص الثلاثة الذين سيلعبون في الجولة الأولى ،
and they can come to the front.
ويمكنهم القدوم إلى المقدمة.
- Nice. We have a good balance. - Okay.
- لطيف - جيد. لدينا توازن جيد. - تمام.
This is an individual match. You live your life on your own.
هذه مباراة فردية. أنت تعيش حياتك بنفسك.
- But how do we ride in these? - Be careful.
- ولكن كيف نركب هذه؟ - احرص.
(Sliding in for a test run)
(انزلاق في اختبار الاختبار)
Be careful. Oh, my.
احرص. أوه ، بلدي.
- Why? - One second. My gosh.
- لماذا؟ - ثانية واحدة. يا إلهي.
I was lifted up like this.
لقد رفعت هكذا.
- Okay. - Hey, that's no joke.
- تمام. - مهلا ، هذه ليست مزحة.
- You have to go right in. - Hey, that's good.
- عليك أن تذهب مباشرة. - مهلا ، هذا جيد.
- My goodness. - There you go.
- يا إلهي. - هناك تذهب.
Sweetie, let's go!
حبيبتي ، دعنا نذهب!
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
- Let's go, Gi Ru! - How much longer are we doing this?
- دعنا نذهب ، جي رو! - كم من الوقت نفعل هذا؟
I think he's too into this.
أعتقد أنه أيضًا في هذا.
It's creepy.
إنه زاحف.
She said it was creepy.
قالت إنه كان زاحفًا.
Gi Ru says Seok Jin is creepy.
يقول جي رو يقول سوك جين زاحف.
(The deeply immersed husband is creepy.)
(الزوج المنغمس للغاية زاحف.)
- It's only our second meeting, - But I think...
- إنه اجتماعنا الثاني فقط ، لكنني أعتقد ...
- and we're married. - I get what she means.
- ونحن متزوجون. - أحصل على ما تعنيه.
Should we practice once? Just in case...
هل يجب أن نمارس مرة واحدة؟ فقط في حالة ...
- Let's try it. - Okay.
- لنجربها. - تمام.
- Sweetie, let's go! - Gi Ru, let's go!
- حبيبتي ، دعنا نذهب! - جي رو ، دعنا نذهب!
Hang on. Point the wheels forward.
انتظر. أشر العجلات إلى الأمام.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
- All right. Ready. - Okay.
- حسنًا. مستعد. - تمام.
One.
واحد.
(Taking a big breath)
(أخذ نفسا كبيرا)
- One. - Se Chan, sorry,
- واحد. - Se Chan ، آسف ،
but don't struggle too much.
لكن لا تكافح كثيرًا.
- It's making me uncomfortable. - All right.
- إنه يجعلني غير مرتاح. - حسنًا.
- You're right by my ear. - Oh, boy. Gi Ru.
- أنت على حق من قبل أذني. - أوه ، فتى. جي رو.
Did you just say, "Oh, boy?"
هل قلت للتو ، "أوه ، يا فتى؟"
- Seriously. - My goodness.
- بجد. - يا إلهي.
- We're not just saying this, Gi Ru. - I'm already exhausted.
- نحن لا نقول هذا فقط ، جي رو. - أنا مرهق بالفعل.
- You invited me here. Gosh, what? - Sweetie.
- لقد دعوتني هنا. يا إلهي ، ماذا؟ - حبيبي.
Sweetie, let's go.
حبيبتي ، دعنا نذهب.
- They're so cute together. - Let's go. I'll pull you along.
- إنهم لطيفون للغاية معًا. - دعنا نذهب. سأسحبك.
(Totally absorbed in his role)
(تمتصه تمامًا في دوره)
- One! - No, we'll do it.
- واحد! - لا ، سنفعل ذلك.
- We can do it ourselves. - Why? I could do it...
- يمكننا أن نفعل ذلك بأنفسنا. - لماذا؟ يمكنني أن أفعل ذلك ...
with the power of love.
مع قوة الحب.
- We're going to do it! - Sorry!
- سنفعل ذلك! - آسف!
- It's the three of us! - Why don't you know the rules?
- إنه الثلاثة منا! - لماذا لا تعرف القواعد؟
- Gosh, that man. - I said it was fine, though.
- يا إلهي ، هذا الرجل. - قلت إنه جيد ، رغم ذلك.
He must really like me.
يجب أن يعجبني حقًا.
- Mister, stop that. - What are you doing?
- مستر ، توقف عن ذلك. - ماذا تفعل؟
- It's creepy. - Let's go!
- إنه زاحف. - دعنا نذهب!
She keeps saying it's creepy.
إنها لا تزال تقول أنها زاحفة.
She says you're creepy.
تقول أنك زاحف.
(After getting rid of her leech of a husband, they begin practicing.)
(بعد التخلص من علقة زوجها ، يبدأون في التدريب.)
- I think she'll go really fast. - Two.
- أعتقد أنها سوف تذهب بسرعة حقا. - اثنين.
- I think she'll go super fast. - I know.
- أعتقد أنها سوف تذهب بسرعة كبيرة. - أنا أعرف.
(Gi Ru stone manages to set off.)
(GI RU Stone تمكنت من الانطلاق.)
- Hey, this is too strong. - Hey, how far am I going? What?
- مهلا ، هذا قوي جدا. - مهلا ، إلى أي مدى أنا ذاهب؟ ماذا؟
- It's too strong. - Too strong.
- انها قوية جدا. - قوي جدا.
- It's going to break. - There you go.
- سوف ينكسر. - هناك تذهب.
- It'll break. - It's too strong.
- سوف تنكسر. - انها قوية جدا.
- Okay. - Too strong.
- تمام. - قوي جدا.
- With the acceleration, - I got it.
- مع التسارع ، - حصلت عليه.
- she doesn't stop. - It was too strong.
- لا تتوقف. - كان قويا جدا.
- This was practice, right? - If you go out like this,
- كانت هذه الممارسة ، أليس كذلك؟ - إذا خرجت هكذا ،
- You're out. - you only get light peach.
- أنت خارج. - تحصل فقط على الخوخ الخفيف.
- Oh, okay. - I got it.
- أوه ، حسنًا. - حصلت عليه.
- Am I out? Was this practice? - I get how to do this.
- هل أنا خارج؟ هل كانت هذه الممارسة؟ - أحصل على كيفية القيام بذلك.
Can you pull me all the way back? Should I get up?
هل يمكنك سحبني طوال الطريق؟ هل يجب أن أستيقظ؟
- You should get up. I'll help you. - Give us your hand.
- يجب أن تنهض. سأساعدك. - أعطنا يدك.
- Can you two do this? - No, just pull her like this.
- هل يمكنك القيام بهذا؟ - لا ، فقط اسحبها هكذا.
Hang on.
انتظر.
(Coming back holding...)
(العودة عقد ...)
(her father-in-law and brother-in-law's hands)
(والد زوجها وأب شقيق زوجها)
- Oh, we can lift her like this. - So cute.
- أوه ، يمكننا رفعها هكذا. - ظريف جدًا.
- So cute! - Let's do this.
- ظريف جدًا! - دعونا نفعل هذا.
- So adorable. - You look like people...
- رائعتين جدا. - تبدو مثل الناس ...
- out on a walk with their cat. - Gi Ru, you're so light.
- في المشي مع قطهم. - GI RU ، أنت خفيف جدًا.
(Struggling to stop)
(تكافح للتوقف)
- Turn me around. - Turn around.
- اقلبني. - التف حوله.
- All right. - A baby...
- حسنًا. - طفل ...
She's practically a baby.
إنها عمليا طفل.
Jae Seok, so...
جاي سوك ، لذلك ...
Play rock-paper-scissors to decide who will go first.
العب مقصات الروك الورقية لتحديد من سيذهب أولاً.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors! Okay.
-مقص الورق الصخور! -مقص الورق الصخور! تمام.
Let them go first.
دعهم يذهبون أولاً.
- Am I going 1st? - Gi Ru, you go 1st.
- هل أنا ذاهب الأول؟ - GI RU ، تذهب 1st.
- How about Gi Ru goes last? - Right.
- ماذا عن GI RU GOES GOES؟ - يمين.
- I think that would be better. - She should go last.
- أعتقد أن ذلك سيكون أفضل. - يجب أن تذهب أخيرًا.
I think it'll be better for me to push everyone.
أعتقد أنه سيكون من الأفضل بالنسبة لي دفع الجميع.
- Will you be able to do it? - Yes.
- هل ستتمكن من القيام بذلك؟ - نعم.
Okay. Good.
تمام. جيد.
- Do you want to go 1st? - I'll go 1st.
- هل تريد أن تذهب الأول؟ - سأذهب الأول.
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
-مقص الورق الصخور. -مقص الورق الصخور.
- Gi Ru, let's go last. - Go first.
- GI RU ، دعنا نذهب أخيرًا. - اذهب أولاً.
- Hey, have Gi Ru go last. - Okay.
- مهلا ، هل gi ru go last. - تمام.
Jae Seok, you'll topple over...
جاي سوك ، سوف تسقط ...
- if you lean back too much. - Okay.
- إذا كنت تميل كثيرًا. - تمام.
- Go ahead. - Here we go.
- تفضل. - ها نحن.
- How about this speed? - Okay. It's good.
- ماذا عن هذه السرعة؟ - تمام. إنه جيد.
Is it good?
هل هو جيد؟
- It's perfect. - It's good.
- إنه مثالي. - إنه جيد.
(Jae Seok Stone sets off.)
(جاي سوك ستون ينطلق.)
I think this is great.
أعتقد أن هذا رائع.
- It's better to fall short. - Move slowly.
- من الأفضل أن تقصر. - تحرك ببطء.
- I think he'll reach the target.
- من الأفضل أن تقصر. - أعتقد أنه سيصل إلى الهدف.
- It's really great.
- إنه رائع حقًا. - إنه رائع حقًا.
Jae Seok, it's great.
جاي سوك ، إنه رائع.
(It'll be much more advantageous to take the center first.)
(سيكون من المفيد أن تأخذ المركز أولاً.)
- It's the best. - It's really great.
- إنه الأفضل. - إنه رائع حقًا.
(But he passes the center.)
(لكنه يمر المركز.)
- Jae Seok, it's okay. - Good.
- جاي سوك ، لا بأس. - جيد.
(Glancing over)
(نظرة خاطفة)
Jae Seok, it's okay.
جاي سوك ، لا بأس.
- Okay. - Come on!
- تمام. - تعال!
What's wrong with him?
ما الخطأ معه؟
- Jae Seok, it's okay. - Good.
- جاي سوك ، لا بأس. - جيد.
(He uses his feet to cheat.)
(يستخدم قدميه للغش.)
What's wrong with him?
ما الخطأ معه؟
- He cheated. - That's...
- لقد خدع. - هذا ...
He put his feet down!
وضع قدميه لأسفل!
What's wrong with him?
ما الخطأ معه؟
- He cheated. - That's...
- لقد خدع. - هذا ...
- I didn't use my feet. - He put his feet down!
- لم أستخدم قدمي. - وضع قدميه لأسفل!
I didn't use my feet.
لم أستخدم قدمي.
Don't lie. We were watching.
لا تكذب. كنا نراقب.
You used your feet.
لقد استخدمت قدميك.
- Look at his facial expression. - Push him.
- انظر إلى تعبير وجهه. - ادفعه.
Look at his facial expression.
انظر إلى تعبير وجهه.
I won't use my feet now.
لن أستخدم قدمي الآن.
- For goodness' sake. - All right.
- من أجل الخير. - حسنًا.
He's ridiculous.
إنه مثير للسخرية.
It'll be better for us.
سيكون أفضل بالنسبة لنا.
I won't use my feet now.
لن أستخدم قدمي الآن.
Am I moving this way?
هل أنتقل بهذه الطريقة؟
- I'll send you to Jae Seok. - You can use your feet.
- سأرسلك إلى جاي سوك. - يمكنك استخدام قدميك.
Just don't use your hands. Don't pull another person.
فقط لا تستخدم يديك. لا تسحب شخصًا آخر.
Here we go.
ها نحن.
(Kim Family's Choi Daniel, Not good at anything)
(كيم عائلة تشوي دانيال ، ليس جيدًا في أي شيء)
- Push hard. - Push hard. No, it's too hard.
- دفع بقوة. - دفع بقوة. لا ، إنه صعب للغاية.
(Daniel Stone sets off.)
(دانيال ستون ينطلق.)
(Shindong succeeds in aiming for Jae Seok.)
(ينجح Shindong في الهدف من جاي سوك.)
- Jae Seok will get pushed off. - Push him with your feet.
- سوف يتم دفع جاي سوك. - ادفعه بقدميك.
It'll be a match.
ستكون مباراة.
(If he hits Jae Seok, he'll be able to push Jae Seok off.)
(إذا ضرب جاي سوك ، فسيكون قادرًا على دفع جاي سوك.)
- He pushed hard. - Isn't the direction off?
- دفع بقوة. - أليس الاتجاه خارج؟
Push him with your feet.
ادفعه بقدميك.
(Daniel pushes him.)
(دانيال يدفعه.)
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
(He succeeds in a takeout with his long legs!)
(ينجح في تناول الطعام في تناول الطعام مع ساقيه الطويلة!)
There you go!
هناك تذهب!
(Daniel sends Jae Seok off and lands in a good spot.)
(يرسل دانيال جاي سوك ويهبط في مكان جيد.)
(Shouting)
(يصرخ)
(He goes far from the curling sheet.)
(يذهب بعيدا عن ورقة الشباك.)
For goodness' sake.
من أجل الخير.
Gosh, what's wrong with him?
يا إلهي ، ما الخطأ معه؟
Daniel, well done.
دانيال ، أحسنت.
He's too light.
إنه خفيف جدًا.
- Yes! - There you go! - Gi Ru, push me. - There you go.
- نعم! - هناك تذهب! - جي رو ، ادفعني. - هناك تذهب.
(Gi Ru's engine is on.)
(محرك GI RU يعمل.)
(Yu Family's Yang Se Chan, Stone head)
(Yu Family's Yang Se Chan ، Stone Head)
- Gi Ru. - We need to push him off.
- جي رو. - نحن بحاجة إلى دفعه.
- Se Chan, push him off.
- نحن بحاجة إلى دفعه. - Se Chan ، ادفعه.
- Push him off.
- دفعه. - Se Chan ، دفع Heam قبالة.
- Gi Ru, your grip is no joke. - Hey.
- جي رو ، قبضتك ليست مزحة. - يا.
You're so strong.
أنت قوي جدا.
Gi Ru. You're so scary, big brother.
جي رو. أنت مخيف جدا ، الأخ الأكبر.
- Don't push too hard. - "You're so scary, big brother?"
- لا تدفع بشدة. - "أنت مخيف جدا يا أخي كبير؟"
- Start from the back. - I'm scared, big brother.
- ابدأ من الخلف. - أنا خائف ، الأخ الأكبر.
He's Gi Ru's favorite toy.
إنه لعبة جي رو المفضلة.
Where am I going?
إلى أين أنا ذاهب؟
Go! Push him!
يذهب! ادفعه!
(Se Chan Stone goes toward Daniel.)
(Se Chan Stone يذهب نحو دانيال.)
- Go! Push him! - Are you coming?
- يذهب! ادفعه! - هل أنت قادم؟
- Push him off. - Good.
- دفعه. - جيد.
(The power is perfect.)
(القوة مثالية.)
(The direction is perfect.)
(الاتجاه مثالي.)
- He's stopping. It's okay. - Good.
- إنه يتوقف. لا بأس. - جيد.
(He topples over right in front of his target.)
(يتساقط على اليمين أمام هدفه.)
- That's your spot.
- هذا مكانك. - هذا مكانك.
- Oh, no. - My goodness.
- أوه ، لا. - يا إلهي.
- Get up. - That's your spot.
- استيقظ. - هذا مكانك.
This is my spot. I just need to get up.
هذا هو مكاني. أنا فقط بحاجة إلى النهوض.
- Se Chan. - That's what you get...
- Se Chan. - هذا ما تحصل عليه ...
for being greedy.
لكونك الجشع.
Will you push Se Chan off from the side?
هل ستدفع SE Chan من الجانب؟
- Shall I send you straight to him? - Yes, I'll get him.
- هل سأرسلك مباشرة إليه؟ - نعم ، سأحضره.
- Hey, let Haha push you. - Okay.
- مهلا ، دع هاها تدفعك. - تمام.
Then you'll hit Daniel behind you.
ثم ستضرب دانيال خلفك.
(Seok Jin predicts that Daniel will be affected.)
(يتنبأ سوك جين بأن دانيال سيتأثر.)
- Let's go. - The red zone is behind you.
- دعنا نذهب. - المنطقة الحمراء خلفك.
- Go. - Hold on.
- يذهب. - يتمسك.
- Push me from there. - Really?
- ادفعني من هناك. - حقًا؟
- Will you go between them?
- ادفعني من هناك. - هل ستذهب بينهما؟
- I'll push Se Chan that way. - Okay.
- سأدفع SE Chan بهذه الطريقة. - تمام.
(Haha changes the angle so that Daniel won't be affected.)
(هاها يغير الزاوية حتى لا يتأثر دانيال.)
Yes. That'll be better.
نعم. سيكون ذلك أفضل.
- It'll be like pool. - Father.
- سيكون مثل البلياردو. - أب.
- Here we go. - Go ahead.
- ها نحن. - تفضل.
- In the back... - One,
- في الخلف ... - واحد ،
two...
اثنين...
Good.
جيد.
Good. Let him push you.
جيد. دعه يدفعك.
- Good. - Gosh, it's too...
- جيد. - يا إلهي ، إنه أيضًا ...
(Scared)
(مقدس)
Good. Let him push you.
جيد. دعه يدفعك.
Let him push you. There you go.
دعه يدفعك. هناك تذهب.
- What?
- ماذا؟ - ماذا؟
(When Haha pushes Se Chan, Daniel gets pushed as well.)
(عندما يدفع هاها شان ، يتم دفع دانيال كذلك.)
(Despite the calculation, Haha took out his teammate.)
(على الرغم من الحساب ، أخرج هاها زميله في الفريق.)
The person in the back got pushed.
تم دفع الشخص في الظهر.
- Gosh. - Are you stupid?
- يا إلهي. - هل أنت غبي؟
- You should've gone further. - Nice.
- يجب أن تذهب أبعد من ذلك. - لطيف - جيد.
(Thanks to Haha, Se Chan Stone is in a better spot!)
(بفضل Haha ، Se Chan Stone في مكان أفضل!)
- Nice. - It's my turn now.
- لطيف - جيد. - حان دوري الآن.
Gi Ru!
جي رو!
Push him off.
ادفعه.
(Yu Family's last big stone is coming!)
(آخر حجر كبير لعائلة Yu قادم!)
You're twice as heavy as him.
أنت ثقيل مرتين مثله.
Her facial expression is solemn.
تعبير وجهها هو رسمي.
She's scary.
إنها مخيفة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Why are you so weak?
لماذا أنت ضعيف جدا؟
- Where are you sending me? - Hold on.
- إلى أين ترسل لي؟ - يتمسك.
For goodness' sake.
من أجل الخير.
(Collapsing)
(الانهيار)
- I need someone else. - What are you doing?
- أحتاج إلى شخص آخر. - ماذا تفعل؟
(His weak legs are overwhelmed.)
(ساقيه الضعيفة غارقة.)
- Gosh, Seok Jin. - Help him.
- يا إلهي ، سوك جين. - ساعده.
- Why are you so weak?
- لماذا أنت ضعيف جدا؟ - ساعده.
- I thought... - I mean...
- فكرت ... - أعني ...
I thought my knees gave out.
اعتقدت أن ركبتي أعطوا.
All right.
حسنًا.
- I need to go to the center. - One...
- أنا بحاجة للذهاب إلى المركز. - واحد...
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
Her facial expression is solemn.
تعبير وجهها هو رسمي.
- Gosh. - You get pushed a lot.
- يا إلهي. - يتم دفعك كثيرًا.
(She's aimed at Haha.)
(إنها تهدف إلى هاها.)
- There she goes. - No.
- هناك تذهب. - لا.
(Kicking)
(الركل)
No!
لا!
(Se Chan, who was in the back, gets pushed.)
(Se Chan ، الذي كان في الخلف ، يتم دفعه.)
(He goes out.)
(يخرج.)
No!
لا!
There we go.
هناك نذهب.
Yes!
نعم!
(Due to action and reaction, Se Chan Stone is out.)
(بسبب العمل ورد الفعل ، SE Chan Stone خارج.)
Se Chan got pushed out.
تم دفع Se Chan.
- I can push back from here. - Two stones.
- يمكنني العودة من هنا. - اثنين من الحجارة.
But Shindong is strong.
لكن شيندونغ قوي.
The center? You'll get pushed back.
المركز؟ سوف يتم دفعها إلى الوراء.
You won't land on the scoreboard if you push her.
لن تهبط على لوحة النتائج إذا دفعتها.
Okay. I'll go between them.
تمام. سأذهب بينهما.
- Between them? - Yes.
- بينهما؟ - نعم.
(It's his goal to go between Gi Ru and Haha.)
(هدفه هو الذهاب بين Gi Ru و Haha.)
- I won't push her. - Will you go past them?
- لن أدفعها. - هل ستتجاوزهم؟
How will you go between us?
كيف ستذهب بيننا؟
The speed shouldn't be too high.
لا ينبغي أن تكون السرعة مرتفعة للغاية.
- No, it shouldn't be. - Right?
- لا ، لا ينبغي أن يكون. - يمين؟
The wheels are lined up nicely.
تصطف العجلات بشكل جيد.
(Even the wheels are lined up.)
(حتى العجلات تصطف.)
- There you go. - Good.
- هناك تذهب. - جيد.
All right.
حسنًا.
- Perfect. - Good.
- ممتاز. - جيد.
- He'll go between them.
- جيد. - سوف يذهب بينهما.
(He quickly goes toward his target.)
(يذهب بسرعة نحو هدفه.)
(Ouch!)
(أوتش!)
She's too strong.
إنها قوية جدًا.
Good.
جيد.
(Gi Ru stops him easily with her feet!)
(جي رو يوقفه بسهولة مع قدميها!)
He'll go between them.
سوف يذهب بينهما.
(The camera dies after Gi Ru's feet push it.)
(تموت الكاميرا بعد أن دفعها أقدام Gi Ru.)
- She's too strong. - That's right.
- إنها قوية جدًا. - هذا صحيح.
- What?
- إنها قوية جدًا. - ماذا؟
I just lifted my feet briefly.
أنا فقط رفعت قدمي لفترة وجيزة.
- Now, - Haha, you're the only one.
- الآن ، - هاها ، أنت الوحيد.
- the result of Round One is out. - You're the only one inside.
- نتيجة الجولة الأولى. - أنت الوحيد في الداخل.
Only Haha acquired one additional color.
هاها فقط اكتسب لونًا إضافيًا واحدًا.
- Okay. - She's too strong.
- تمام. - إنها قوية جدًا.
(In Round 1, only Haha acquired 1 additional color.)
(في الجولة 1 ، HAHA فقط حصل على لون إضافي.)
That dirty mustache.
هذا الشارب القذر.
- Gi Ru, you're strong. - That's right.
- GI RU ، أنت قوي. - هذا صحيح.
- You're strong. Play again. - Okay.
- أنت قوي. العب مرة أخرى. - تمام.
- Go last.
- اذهب أخيرًا. - تمام.
- Ye Eun, go 1st. - Shall I go 1st?
- أيها يون ، اذهب 1st. - هل سأذهب الأول؟
- Then I'll go next. - Okay.
- ثم سأذهب بعد ذلك. - تمام.
Gi Ru is like a cheat code.
GI RU يشبه رمز الغش.
They have Jang Hoon too.
لديهم Jang Hoon أيضًا.
Why am I sweating?
لماذا أنا أتعرق؟
All right.
حسنًا.
Smooth.
سلس.
We'll begin.
سنبدأ.
- Ji Hyo, I like your gaze. - Here we go.
- جي هيو ، أحب نظرتك. - ها نحن.
(Kim Family's Song Ji Hyo, She plays with her spirit.)
(أغنية عائلة كيم جي هيو ، تلعب مع روحها.)
- Stop. - Don't go far.
- قف. - لا تذهب بعيدا.
- That's good. Stop.
- لا تذهب بعيدا. - هذا جيد. قف.
It'll be better to stop there.
سيكون من الأفضل التوقف عند هذا الحد.
(Yu Family's Ji Ye Eun, Yeongdeok's snow crab)
(عائلة يو جي يي يون ، سلطعون الثلج يونغدوك)
Push me gently.
ادفعني بلطف.
- There you go. - Good.
- هناك تذهب. - جيد.
- Nice.
- جيد. - لطيف - جيد.
Well done.
أحسنت.
- Excuse me. - Don't stop.
- اعذرني. - لا تتوقف.
Drone pilot, I'm sorry,
طيار الطائرات بدون طيار ، أنا آسف ،
but please make it fly higher.
ولكن من فضلك اجعلها تطير أعلى.
- A moment ago... - That's right.
- منذ لحظة ... - هذا صحيح.
A moment ago,
منذ لحظة ،
- the drone passed this way. - Jang Hoon.
- مرت الطائرة بدون طيار بهذه الطريقة. - جانج هون.
(Not considering the utility pole, the drone was flown as usual.)
(لا تفكر في عمود المنفعة ، تم نقل الطائرة بدون طيار كالمعتاد.)
- Jang Hoon, did it cut your hair? - I mean...
- جانغ هون ، هل قطع شعرك؟ - أعني...
I'm sorry, but please make it fly higher.
أنا آسف ، لكن من فضلك اجعله يطير أعلى.
- I thought it was a hair salon. - I was so startled.
- اعتقدت أنه صالون شعر. - كنت مندهشا جدا.
Is Jang Hoon going next?
هل يانغ هون يلي؟
Here comes Jang Hoon.
هنا يأتي يانغ هون.
Do you want to stay at the front?
هل تريد البقاء في المقدمة؟
- Will that be better? - What?
- هل سيكون ذلك أفضل؟ - ماذا؟
It might be better to stay at the front.
قد يكون من الأفضل البقاء في المقدمة.
- In front of Ye Eun. - Yes.
- أمام أيها يون. - نعم.
- Others will push you. - That's right.
- سوف يدفعك الآخرون. - هذا صحيح.
Jang Hoon is so scary.
يانغ هون مخيف جدا.
- Send me toward Ye Eun. - Push Jang Hoon hard...
- أرسل لي نحو أيها يون. - دفع جانغ هون بقوة ...
- so that he can push off everyone. - I'm so scared.
- حتى يتمكن من دفع الجميع. - أنا خائف جدا.
- That's right. Push him. - Just push him.
- هذا صحيح. ادفعه. - فقط ادفعه.
- Jang Hoon, you like Ye Eun. - Go to the front.
- جانغ هون ، أنت تحب ايون. - اذهب إلى المقدمة.
- Are you ready? - You like me.
- هل أنت مستعد؟ - أنت تحبني.
Go to the person you like.
اذهب إلى الشخص الذي تحب.
(The rock sets off.)
(صخرة تنطلق.)
- What's wrong with her? - Push her.
- ما هو الخطأ معها؟ - ادفعها.
It's a bumper car.
إنها سيارة الوفير.
He's coming.
إنه قادم.
- Gosh. - All right. There you go.
- يا إلهي. - حسنًا. هناك تذهب.
(He just needs to push her!)
(يحتاج فقط لدفعها!)
(Without pushing her, he just laughs!)
(دون دفعها ، يضحك فقط!)
(The lack of attack is quite intentional.)
(عدم وجود هجوم مقصود للغاية.)
- What? - All right.
- ماذا؟ - حسنًا.
- What's up with him? - What?
- ما الأمر معه؟ - ماذا؟
He likes me.
يحبني.
She stopped me.
أوقفتني.
- What was that? - Come on.
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - تعال.
- She...
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - هي...
- She stopped me. - Do you like her?
- أوقفتني. - هل تحبها؟
"Do you like her?"
"هل تحبها؟"
- For goodness' sake.
- هل تحبها؟ - من أجل الخير.
- She stopped me. - Are you guys dating or something?
- أوقفتني. - هل أنتم يا رفاق يعودون أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
I stopped him.
أوقفته.
Jang Hoon isn't usually like that.
Jang Hoon ليس هكذا عادة.
I know. What's up with him?
أنا أعرف. ما الأمر معه؟
- Good luck. - Ye Eun...
- حظ سعيد. - أيها ايون ...
- He likes Ye Eun a lot. - Good luck.
- يحب ايون كثيرا. - حظ سعيد.
- This is nice. We're doing well. - This is nice.
- هذا جميل. نحن بخير. - هذا جميل.
We're doing well.
نحن بخير.
- I'll push you. - Seok Jin.
- سأدفعك. - سوك جين.
- Seok Jin, we can score. - Yes.
- سوك جين ، يمكننا تسجيل. - نعم.
Send me between them.
أرسل لي بينهما.
- Send me between them. - Of course.
- أرسل لي بينهما. - بالطبع.
- Trust me. - I'll push Jang Hoon off.
- ثق بي. - سأدفع يانغ هون.
- You can break them off. - Yes. As I break them off,
- يمكنك قطعها. - نعم. بينما أقطعهم ،
I won't push Ye Eun too much.
لن أدفع أيها الكثير.
- Send me between them. - Of course.
- أرسل لي بينهما. - بالطبع.
- Trust me. - I'll push Jang Hoon off.
- ثق بي. - سأدفع يانغ هون.
Okay.
تمام.
- Let's go.
- دعنا نذهب. - دعنا نذهب.
- All right. - Seok Jin.
- حسنًا. - سوك جين.
- Let's see an explosion. - That isn't the direction.
- دعونا نرى انفجار. - هذا ليس هو الاتجاه.
Jae Seok, push him with your full power.
جاي سوك ، ادفعه بقوتك الكاملة.
- Do it with your full power. - Full power.
- افعلها بقوتك الكاملة. - القوة الكاملة.
- Full power is good. - Let's go.
- القوة الكاملة جيدة. - دعنا نذهب.
Big Nose power!
قوة الأنف الكبيرة!
- Jang Hoon will fly off. - Let's go, Big Nose.
- يانغ هون سوف يطير. - دعنا نذهب ، أنف كبير.
- Good. - Hey, where are you sending me?
- جيد. - مهلا ، إلى أين ترسل لي؟
- What are you doing? - What's this?
- ماذا تفعل؟ - ما هذا؟
(Hey, where are you sending me? What are you doing?)
(مهلا ، أين ترسلني؟ ماذا تفعل؟)
- Good. - Hey, where are you sending me?
- جيد. - مهلا ، إلى أين ترسل لي؟
- What are you doing? - What's this?
- ماذا تفعل؟ - ما هذا؟
(Crawling)
(الزحف)
(Jae Seok couldn't help but toy with him.)
(لم يستطع جاي سوك إلا أن يلعب معه.)
- What's this? - What?
- ما هذا؟ - ماذا؟
(The engine goes out before the halfway point.)
(المحرك يخرج قبل نقطة منتصف الطريق.)
- What's wrong with him? - What's this?
- ما الخطأ معه؟ - ما هذا؟
(Flustered)
(مرتفعة)
- It's so... - It suits him.
- إنه كذلك ... - إنه يناسبه.
My hands became weak.
أصبحت يدي ضعيفة.
- I'm sorry, Seok Jin. - I can't believe it.
- أنا آسف يا سوك جين. - لا أستطيع أن أصدق ذلك.
- I'm sorry.
- أنا آسف. - لا أستطيع أن أصدق ذلك.
- Play the next game well. - This is...
- لعب اللعبة التالية بشكل جيد. - هذا هو...
- Hey. "Play the next game well?" - He's like a remote island.
- يا. "العب اللعبة التالية بشكل جيد؟" - إنه مثل جزيرة نائية.
Why did I put these on?
لماذا وضعت هذه على؟
(Crying)
(بكاء)
Hey, Jae Seok!
مهلا ، جاي سوك!
Why did I put these on?
لماذا وضعت هذه على؟
- Why did I put these on? - Seok Jin, you never know.
- لماذا وضعت هذه على؟ - سوك جين ، أنت لا تعرف أبدًا.
- You never know.
- سوك جين ، أنت لا تعرف أبدًا. - أنت لا تعرف أبدا.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- سوك جين ، أنت لا تعرف أبدًا. - لا تكون سخيفًا.
- It suits you so well. - Okay. I can turn around, right?
- يناسبك بشكل جيد. - تمام. يمكنني الالتفاف ، أليس كذلك؟
(He becomes a spectator in the end.)
(يصبح متفرجًا في النهاية.)
- I can do it. - Precision is important.
- أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك. - الدقة مهمة.
- Shindong, let's go! Father! - All right.
- Shindong ، دعنا نذهب! أب! - حسنًا.
- I'm scared. - Good luck.
- أنا خائف. - حظ سعيد.
Father, good luck.
الأب ، حظا سعيدا.
(Jong Kook Stone sets off.)
(Jong Kook Stone ينطلق.)
- I'm scared. - Good.
- أنا خائف. - جيد.
(Fast)
(سريع)
(Kicking)
(الركل)
- There you go. - Good. There you go.
- هناك تذهب. - جيد. هناك تذهب.
(He quickly takes Ye Eun out. But he ends up sliding off as well.)
(سرعان ما يخرج أيها. لكنه ينتهي أيضًا.)
I'm sliding off.
أنا انزلق.
You slid off.
لقد انزلقت.
(Unable to control his strength, he went out of the curling sheet.)
(غير قادر على السيطرة على قوته ، خرج من ورقة الشباك.)
- I slid off. - Both of them went out.
- انزلق. - كلاهما خرج.
(Only Ji Hyo is in the section for 3 additional colors.)
(Ji Hyo فقط في القسم لمدة 3 ألوان إضافية.)
- Gi Ru. - Whom shall I push? Jang Hoon?
- جي رو. - من سأدفع؟ جانغ هون؟
You should push Jang Hoon off and get one point.
يجب عليك دفع Jang Hoon والحصول على نقطة واحدة.
Okay.
تمام.
- Stretch your legs to the left. - Okay.
- تمتد ساقيك إلى اليسار. - تمام.
Here we go.
ها نحن.
I'll need to kick the middle.
سأحتاج إلى ركلة الوسط.
Gosh, Gi Ru is scary.
يا إلهي ، جي رو مخيف.
You can push very hard. I'm going for Jang Hoon.
يمكنك الدفع بقوة. أنا ذاهب لجانغ هون.
Show us.
أظهر لنا.
- Two. - Get ready.
- اثنين. - استعد.
We'll push.
سندفع.
- Okay. Let's go. - Here we go.
- تمام. دعنا نذهب. - ها نحن.
Heave-ho.
heave-ho.
(Gi Ru Stone sets off.)
(Gi Ru Stone ينطلق.)
Let's go. Heave-ho.
دعنا نذهب. heave-ho.
- Here she comes.
- هنا تأتي. - هنا تأتي.
- What? - My goodness.
- ماذا؟ - يا إلهي.
(She's already fast,)
(إنها سريعة بالفعل ،)
(but she adds a booster with her body.)
(لكنها تضيف داعم مع جسدها.)
- What? - There she goes.
- ماذا؟ - هناك تذهب.
(She pushes them off!)
(هي تدفعهم!)
(Will they go out?)
(هل سيخرجون؟)
(They come back in!)
(يعودون إلى!)
(They spin and land in the better sections!)
(يدورون ويهبطون في أقسام أفضل!)
- Good. - Both of them came back in.
- جيد. - عاد كلاهما.
- Seven.
- سبعة. - سبعة.
(Figuring out the score)
(اكتشاف النتيجة)
Ji Hyo will acquire...
سيحصل جي هيو ...
- seven additional colors. - Okay.
- سبعة ألوان إضافية. - تمام.
As for Jang Hoon...
أما بالنسبة لجانغ هون ...
- One.
- واحد. - واحد.
He'll acquire...
سوف يكتسب ...
- one additional color. - Okay.
- لون واحد إضافي. - تمام.
Thus, the ones who acquired additional colors are...
وهكذا ، فإن الذين اكتسبوا ألوانًا إضافية ...
three members, Haha, Ji Hyo, and Jang Hoon.
ثلاثة أعضاء ، هاها ، جي هيو ، وجانغ هون.
(He's playing regardless of the result.)
(إنه يلعب بغض النظر عن النتيجة.)
- We did well. - My team...
- لقد فعلنا جيدا. - فريقي ...
- Let's make a cool drawing. - Hold on. Let's do ssireum.
- دعونا نتخلى عن الرسم الرائع. - يتمسك. دعونا نفعل ssireum.
- Ssireum. - That's scary.
- ssireum. - هذا مخيف.
- Let's do ssireum. - Let's do something like that.
- دعونا نفعل ssireum. - دعونا نفعل شيئًا كهذا.
The timing was perfect.
كان التوقيت مثاليًا.
(Hitting)
(ضرب)
(A collision)
(تصادم)
Stop playing around!
توقف عن اللعب!
- I'm sorry. - Why do you keep playing around?
- أنا آسف. - لماذا تستمر في اللعب؟
Jae Seok, the utility pole nearly fell.
جاي سوك ، قطب المنفعة سقط تقريبا.
- I'm sorry. - Can I get...
- أنا آسف. - هل يمكنني الحصول على ...
Can I get workers' compensation?
هل يمكنني الحصول على تعويض العمال؟
- Yes. - For the last drawing match,
- نعم. - لمباراة الرسم الأخيرة ،
- we'll move to the ending location. - Okay.
- سننتقل إلى موقع النهاية. - تمام.
- That sounds good.
- تمام. - فكرة جميلة.
(They move to make the very last drawing!)
(ينتقلون لجعل الرسم الأخير!)
It's time to draw.
حان الوقت للرسم.
Will all of us draw?
هل نرسم جميعًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
What kind of drawing do we need to make?
ما نوع الرسم الذي نحتاج إلى صنعه؟
This place is really pretty.
هذا المكان جميل حقا.
Look outside.
انظر بالخارج.
- It's really pretty. - What is this place?
- إنه جميل حقًا. - ما هذا المكان؟
- This place is really pretty.
- إنه جميل حقًا. - هذا المكان جميل حقا.
- It's really pretty. - I mean...
- إنه جميل حقًا. - أعني...
(The overly nice view will give them inspiration.)
(المنظر اللطيف المفرط سيمنحهم الإلهام.)
You know, it's pretty.
أنت تعرف ، إنها جميلة.
- I didn't know this place existed. - It's like a palace.
- لم أكن أعرف أن هذا المكان موجود. - إنه مثل القصر.
It's so pretty.
انها جميلة جدا.
Will we create some art today?
هل سنخلق بعض الفن اليوم؟
All right. This is the last match.
حسنًا. هذه هي المباراة الأخيرة.
For the two families' pride,
لفخر العائلتين ،
you'll have the Drawing Match.
سيكون لديك مباراة الرسم.
- How am I supposed to draw? - Okay.
- كيف من المفترض أن أرسم؟ - تمام.
For three minutes,
لمدة ثلاث دقائق ،
- make a drawing... - Three minutes?
- جعل الرسم ... - ثلاث دقائق؟
- for the theme of "Happy home." - My home?
- لموضوع "Happy Home". - بيتي؟
Your current home. Your family.
منزلك الحالي. عائلتك.
(Jae Seok's family, Jong Kook's family)
(عائلة جاي سوك ، عائلة جونج كوك)
- My home. - Yes.
- بيتي. - نعم.
We'll collect the completed drawings...
سنقوم بجمع الرسومات المكتملة ...
and ask the AI, "How much will you pay for this drawing?"
واسأل الذكاء الاصطناعي ، "كم ستدفع مقابل هذا الرسم؟"
The answer it gives...
الجواب الذي يعطيه ...
will be the price of the drawing.
سيكون سعر الرسم.
Really?
حقًا؟
Since the Kim Family has 6 members, there will be 6 drawings.
منذ أن تضم عائلة كيم 6 أعضاء ، سيكون هناك 6 رسومات.
Since the Yu Family has five members,
منذ أن تضم عائلة يو خمسة أعضاء ،
please pick a member.
الرجاء اختيار عضو.
The price of his or her drawing will be doubled...
سيتم تضاعف سعر رسمه ...
- for the total. - Okay.
- للمجموع. - تمام.
Please pick a member before you start drawing.
الرجاء اختيار عضو قبل البدء في الرسم.
They'll pick either Jae Seok or Se Chan.
سوف يختارون إما جاي سوك أو شان.
- Jae Seok is terrible at drawing. - Really?
- جاي سوك فظيع في الرسم. - حقًا؟
Se Chan too.
Se chan أيضا.
But a bad drawing might be judged differently.
ولكن قد يتم الحكم على رسم سيء بشكل مختلف.
- It might be seen as artistic. - It might happen, right?
- قد ينظر إليها على أنها فنية. - قد يحدث ، أليس كذلك؟
- So... - It isn't at that level.
- إذن ... - ليس في هذا المستوى.
It's seriously bad.
إنه أمر سيء للغاية.
- Then pick the worst one. - Jae Seok is the worst at drawing.
- ثم اختر أسوأ واحد. - جاي سوك هو الأسوأ في الرسم.
- Jong Kook. - What?
- جونغ كوك. - ماذا؟
- I mean...
- ماذا؟ - أعني...
It doesn't matter since the AI...
لا يهم منذ الذكاء الاصطناعي ...
might focus on the artistry.
قد تركز على الفن.
- The soul. - For goodness' sake.
- الروح. - من أجل الخير.
- The price of Jae Seok's drawing... - Okay.
- سعر رسم جاي سوك ... - حسنًا.
will be doubled.
سوف يتضاعف.
The Yu Family won the earlier mission,
فازت عائلة يو بالمهمة السابقة ،
- right? - Yes.
- يمين؟ - نعم.
Thus, 2 members will get 2 additional minutes.
وبالتالي ، سيحصل أعضاء على دقيقتين.
They'll be able to draw for five minutes.
سيكونون قادرين على الرسم لمدة خمس دقائق.
Then we should pick people with potential.
ثم يجب أن نختار الأشخاص ذوي الإمكانات.
The price of my drawing will he doubled,
ثمن الرسم الخاص بي سوف يتضاعف ،
so I need to receive a high score.
لذلك أحتاج إلى الحصول على درجة عالية.
Grasshopper and me.
جراد وأنا.
- Haha will receive the frame. - Okay.
- هاها سوف تتلقى الإطار. - تمام.
Some people acquired additional colors.
اكتسب بعض الناس ألوان إضافية.
I want red.
اريد أحمر.
I want light blue.
أريد الأزرق الفاتح.
Ji Hyo can use seven additional colors.
يمكن لـ Ji Hyo استخدام سبعة ألوان إضافية.
Can we only use light peach?
هل يمكننا استخدام الخوخ الخفيف فقط؟
- Black and light peach. - Okay.
- الأسود والخوخ الخفيف. - تمام.
Get ready.
استعد.
- It's hard to use paint.
- تمام. - من الصعب استخدام الطلاء.
This is hard.
هذا صعب.
(They begin to draw with the tool of their choice.)
(يبدأون في الرسم باستخدام الأداة التي يختارونها.)
(Yu Family members can only use light peach and black.)
(لا يمكن لأفراد عائلة يو استخدام الخوخ الخفيف والأسود فقط.)
Home... Hold on. Home...
الصفحة الرئيسية ... تمسك. بيت...
My house looks strange.
منزلي يبدو غريباً.
(The artists struggle with the limited tools.)
(يكافح الفنانون مع الأدوات المحدودة.)
Drawing with markers...
الرسم مع علامات ...
This is hard.
هذا صعب.
(Drawing)
(رسم)
My drawing is going so well.
الرسم الخاص بي يسير على ما يرام.
Gi Ru, I drew you.
GI RU ، لقد رسمتك.
Why am I the size of the house?
لماذا أنا بحجم المنزل؟
(He went beyond perspective.)
(ذهب أبعد من منظور.)
I'm the size of the house.
أنا حجم المنزل.
- I started with you. - I see.
- لقد بدأت معك. - أرى.
It must be because I'm the biggest.
يجب أن يكون ذلك لأنني الأكبر.
(Glancing over at Gi Ru)
(نظرة خاطفة على GI RU)
- Your artwork is incredible. - You know...
- عملك الفني لا يصدق. - أنت تعرف...
- It's incredible. - I like philosophical work.
- إنه أمر لا يصدق. - أحب العمل الفلسفي.
- What are you doing to your foot? - You know,
- ماذا تفعل لقدمك؟ - أنت تعرف،
- I like philosophical work. - It's incredible.
- أحب العمل الفلسفي. - إنه أمر لا يصدق.
This is a work of art.
هذا عمل فني.
(Not bound by the tools,)
(غير ملزم بالأدوات ،)
(she adds a philosophical touch.)
(تضيف لمسة فلسفية.)
My work...
عملي ...
We need to fool the AI.
نحن بحاجة لخداع الذكاء الاصطناعي.
(What will her masterpiece look like?)
(كيف ستبدو تحفة لها؟)
We need to make it look like it has a deep meaning.
نحن بحاجة إلى جعلها تبدو وكأنها لها معنى عميق.
An expert would give...
سيعطي خبير ...
the highest score to my work.
أعلى درجة لعملي.
(Meanwhile, the Kim Family is absorbed in drawing.)
(وفي الوقت نفسه ، تم امتصاص عائلة كيم في الرسم.)
(Compared to the other family, they draw humanlike figures.)
(بالمقارنة مع الأسرة الأخرى ، يرسمون شخصيات إنسانية.)
I'm using the cartoon style. It's easy.
أنا أستخدم نمط الكرتون. إنه أمر سهل.
The judge is the AI, right? The AI.
القاضي هو الذكاء الاصطناعي ، أليس كذلك؟ الذكاء الاصطناعي.
What time is it now?
ما هو الوقت الآن؟
That came out wrong.
الذي خرج خطأ.
One minute and forty-five seconds have passed.
مرت دقيقة وخمسة وأربعين ثانية.
- Already?
- بالفعل؟ - بالفعل؟
This is driving me crazy.
هذا يدفعني إلى الجنون.
We don't have much time.
ليس لدينا الكثير من الوقت.
I need to make it artistic.
أنا بحاجة لجعلها فنية.
- We should blur the lines. - Yes. We should do that.
- يجب أن نطمس الخطوط. - نعم. يجب أن نفعل ذلك.
We should blur the lines.
يجب أن نطمس الخطوط.
Gosh, I can't do it.
يا إلهي ، لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
(Rustling)
(سرقة)
(Absorbed)
(ممتص)
(This catfish goes wild on the canvas.)
(هذا سمك السلور يسير على القماش.)
We'll need more time.
سنحتاج إلى مزيد من الوقت.
- Seriously. - Three minutes.
- بجد. - ثلاث دقائق.
I don't want to draw more. It came out well.
لا أريد رسم المزيد. لقد خرج بشكل جيد.
He's confident.
إنه واثق.
(3 minutes are up.)
(3 دقائق ترتفع.)
(9 members without more time get their drawings taken away.)
(9 أعضاء دون المزيد من الوقت يحصلون على رسوماتهم.)
- Is it over? - For goodness' sake.
- هل انتهى؟ - من أجل الخير.
- I need some more time. - Did three minutes pass?
- أنا بحاجة إلى مزيد من الوقت. - هل مرر ثلاث دقائق؟
- I didn't get to use any colors. - Time's up.
- لم أتمكن من استخدام أي ألوان. - الوقت يصل.
You're the one at fault for not using any colors.
أنت على خطأ لعدم استخدام أي ألوان.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
- Seriously. - Gosh.
- بجد. - يا إلهي.
- Come on. - I didn't get to draw Haha.
- تعال. - لم أحصل على رسم هاها.
We needed five minutes at the very least.
كنا بحاجة إلى خمس دقائق على الأقل.
Then you should've won the game.
ثم يجب أن تفوز باللعبة.
Why are you talking so much when you're drawing so relaxed?
لماذا تتحدث كثيرًا عندما ترتاح جدًا؟
Gosh, this is bad.
يا إلهي ، هذا سيء.
Time passed so quickly.
مر الوقت بسرعة.
There's a geometric feel, right?
هناك شعور هندسي ، أليس كذلك؟
It's a house with people inside.
إنه منزل مع الناس في الداخل.
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
- You don't know? Why not? - No.
- أنت لا تعرف؟ ولم لا؟ - لا.
I don't think you should draw more.
لا أعتقد أنك يجب أن ترسم المزيد.
Should I stop here?
هل يجب أن أتوقف هنا؟
I think the AI...
أعتقد أن الذكاء الاصطناعي ...
will give me a high score.
سوف تعطيني درجة عالية.
I think the AI will get fooled. Right?
أعتقد أن الذكاء الاصطناعي سوف ينخدع. يمين؟
There's a bit of an artistic style.
هناك القليل من الأسلوب الفني.
It looks cool.
يبدو رائعا.
All right.
حسنًا.
- Let's stop. - Stop.
- دعنا نتوقف. - قف.
- Stop!
- قف. - قف!
- Okay. - For goodness' sake.
- تمام. - من أجل الخير.
- What's that?
- ما هذا؟ - من أجل الخير.
I fooled the AI,
لقد خدعت الذكاء الاصطناعي ،
Mine looks like Picasso's work.
يبدو لي مثل عمل بيكاسو.
Look at mine. Mine has...
انظر إلى الألغام. لي ...
- Really? - Ha Jung Woo's style.
- حقًا؟ - أسلوب ها يونج وو.
Mine will surprise you.
سوف يفاجئك
The AI will consider the theme, right?
سوف تنظر الذكاء الاصطناعي في الموضوع ، أليس كذلك؟
- It's so embarrassing. - I know.
- إنه أمر محرج للغاية. - أنا أعرف.
I can't show it to anyone.
لا يمكنني إظهاره لأي شخص.
- What?
- ماذا؟ - ماذا؟
- Your drawing? - There isn't a stool for me.
- الرسم الخاص بك؟ - ليس هناك براز بالنسبة لي.
Didn't I get two stools?
ألم أحصل على برازان؟
(She took 2 stools.)
(أخذت 2 براز.)
- That's right. - Didn't I get two stools?
- هذا صحيح. - ألم أحصل على براز؟
Yes, you did. You got two stools.
نعم ، لقد فعلت. حصلت على براز اثنين.
- I mean... - That's right.
- أعني ... - هذا صحيح.
- Gi Ru. - It was comfortable.
- جي رو. - كان مريحًا.
- You got one stool. - One stool per buttock.
- حصلت على براز واحد. - براز واحد لكل رد.
It was really comfortable to use one stool per buttock.
كان من المريح حقًا استخدام براز واحد لكل رد.
- So... - It was like sitting on a bench.
- هكذا ... - كان مثل الجلوس على مقعد.
I was so thankful for their consideration.
كنت ممتنًا جدًا للنظر فيها.
We'll alternate between the two families.
سنناوب بين العائلتين.
Let's first ask the AI...
دعونا أولاً نسأل الذكاء الاصطناعي ...
how much it would pay for Se Chan's drawing.
كم ستدفع مقابل رسم SE Chan.
Please bring out Se Chan's drawing.
يرجى إخراج رسم شان.
Se Chan will go first.
سيذهب Se Chan أولاً.
(He used his entire body to make a drawing in Ha Jung Woo's style.)
(لقد استخدم جسده بالكامل للقيام برسم بأسلوب ها يونج وو.)
(Will it be as beautiful as his performance?)
(هل ستكون جميلة مثل أدائه؟)
- He drew it well. - He did well.
- رسمها جيدا. - لقد فعل بشكل جيد.
- What?
- لقد فعل بشكل جيد. - ماذا؟
- Se Chan did well. - He drew it well.
- Se Chan فعلت بشكل جيد. - رسمها جيدا.
(Did Se Chan draw well?)
(هل رسمت شان بشكل جيد؟)
- What? - Is that Se Chan's drawing?
- ماذا؟ - هل هذا رسم شان؟
- What? Is that Se Chan's drawing? - It's artistic.
- ماذا؟ هل هذا رسم شان؟ - إنه فني.
- It isn't half bad.
- ليس نصف سيء. - إنه فني.
- It looks meaningful. - Please explain the intention...
- تبدو ذات مغزى. - يرجى توضيح النية ...
of your drawing.
من الرسم الخاص بك.
Picasso is one of my favorite artists,
بيكاسو هو أحد الفنانين المفضلين لدي ،
so I paid homage to him.
لذلك أشادت به.
You did really well.
لقد فعلت بشكل جيد حقًا.
- It isn't bad. It'll fool the AI. - Seriously.
- ليس سيئا. سوف يخدع الذكاء الاصطناعي. - بجد.
- You know... - It looks nice.
- أنت تعرف ... - يبدو لطيفًا.
- It looks cool. - I didn't expect such reactions.
- يبدو رائعًا. - لم أكن أتوقع مثل هذه ردود الفعل.
- You guys like it. - You drew it well.
- يا رفاق تحبها. - لقد رسمتها جيدًا.
- You did well. - It's a nice drawing.
- لقد قمت بعمل جيد. - إنه رسم جميل.
- Oh, my. - It looks artistic.
- أوه ، بلدي. - يبدو فنيًا.
- What? - You have a talent.
- ماذا؟ - لديك موهبة.
I didn't make the faces round,
لم أجعل الوجوه جولة ،
- but square. - Why?
- لكن المربع. - لماذا؟
The AI might think that the round faces are...
قد يعتقد الذكاء الاصطناعى أن الوجوه المستديرة ...
- too ordinary. - I see.
- عادي جدا. - أرى.
- My goodness. - You gave it a twist.
- يا إلهي. - لقد أعطيته تطورًا.
It's a nice strategy.
إنها استراتيجية لطيفة.
It's artistic.
إنه فني.
You regard your family with love in your eyes.
أنت تعتبر عائلتك بالحب في عينيك.
So the eyes are heart-shaped.
لذا فإن العيون على شكل قلب.
- I drew them that way. - Not bad.
- رسمتهم بهذه الطريقة. - ليس سيئًا.
- It's the best. - Really?
- إنه الأفضل. - حقًا؟
- I don't want to go next. - It's nice.
- لا أريد أن أذهب بعد ذلك. - إنه لطيف.
Now...
الآن...
- They like that. - Then we'll ask the AI...
- هم يحبون ذلك. - ثم سنطلب من الذكاء الاصطناعي ...
how much it can pay for the art pieces,
كم يمكن أن تدفع ثمن القطع الفنية ،
starting from Se Chan's.
بدءا من Se Chan's.
- He's good. - People like that.
- إنه جيد. - الناس من هذا القبيل.
It's not bad. He did a good job in a short period of time.
هذا ليس سيئا. لقد قام بعمل جيد في فترة زمنية قصيرة.
- Will the AI evaluate it too? - He did really well.
- هل سيقوم منظمة العفو الدولية بتقييمها أيضًا؟ - لقد فعل بشكل جيد حقًا.
The price of that will show us the standard.
سعر ذلك سيظهر لنا المعيار.
He did really well.
لقد فعل بشكل جيد.
- Really? - It almost makes you sad.
- حقًا؟ - يكاد يجعلك حزينًا.
- That's how good it is. - You have an artistic sense.
- هذا ما هو جيد. - لديك شعور فني.
How much will you pay for this art piece?
كم ستدفع ثمن هذه القطعة الفنية؟
- That's the question? - That's how they'll ask?
- هذا هو السؤال؟ - هكذا سيسألون؟
- Will it give it a price? - It's the same.
- هل ستعطيه ثمناً؟ - هذا هو نفسه.
- Something is coming. - It's so long.
- شيء ما قادم. - إنه طويل جدًا.
It's so long.
إنه طويل جدًا.
The background looks like rough pencil shading,
الخلفية تبدو وكأنها تظليل قلم رصاص ،
with four square robot faces that seem to be copied and pasted.
مع أربعة وجوه روبوت مربعة يبدو أنها تم نسخها ولصقها.
Their eyes are drawn as hearts.
يتم رسم عيونهم كقلوب.
I'm not sure if that was done to show feeling...
لست متأكدًا مما إذا كان قد تم ذلك لإظهار الشعور ...
or if they were just overused.
أو إذا كانت الإفراط في الاستخدام.
(It's a harsh criticism.)
(إنه انتقاد قاسي.)
- Why, that... - It's unsure...
- لماذا ، ذلك ... - ليس من المؤكد ...
if the hearts were overused.
إذا كانت القلوب مفرطة في الاستخدام.
(The evaluation isn't finished.)
(لم ينتهي التقييم.)
It's like the painter is saying, "This piece is abstract,"
إنه مثل الرسام يقول ، "هذه القطعة مجردة" ، "
"so just look at the feeling," and ends there.
"لذا انظر فقط إلى الشعور" وينتهي هناك.
Visually, it lacks any uniqueness, and inwardly, it's an empty shell.
بصريا ، فإنه يفتقر إلى أي تفرد ، وداخله ، إنها قذيفة فارغة.
So how much is it?
إذن كم هو؟
How much is it?
كم سعره؟
The price of frozen food at a convenience store is enough.
سعر الطعام المجمد في متجر صغير يكفي.
Seven dollars.
سبعة دولارات.
(7 dollars)
(7 دولارات)
It's a psycho.
إنه نفسي.
Seven dollars.
سبعة دولارات.
(The AI appraiser taught him the reality.)
(علمه المثمن الذكاء الاصطناعي الواقع.)
It's a chic AI.
إنه منظمة العفو الدولية الأنيقة.
- It's a type T AI. - That's right.
- إنه نوع T AI. - هذا صحيح.
- It's type T. - Seriously.
- إنه النوع T. - على محمل الجد.
Seven dollars?
سبعة دولارات؟
- Seven dollars can be a high price. - Right.
- يمكن أن يكون سبعة دولارات ثمناً مرتفعاً. - يمين.
- This is amazing. - If this is worth that price...
- هذا مذهل. - إذا كان هذا يستحق هذا السعر ...
- The price was set... - Seven dollars.
- تم تعيين السعر ... - سبعة دولارات.
- at seven dollars. - It could be a high price.
- بسبعة دولارات. - يمكن أن يكون سعر مرتفع.
Seven dollars. It's quite detailed.
سبعة دولارات. إنه مفصل تمامًا.
It's different.
الأمر مختلف.
- But it feels good... - It's nice.
- لكنه شعور جيد ... - إنه لطيف.
since you think my drawing is nice.
بما أنك تعتقد أن رسم جميل.
You really did well, though.
لقد فعلت ذلك جيدًا حقًا.
- It's good. - If this is seven dollars,
- إنه جيد. - إذا كان هذا سبعة دولارات ،
- the rest would be worth much less. - I'll hang it at home.
- الباقي سيكون أقل بكثير. - سأعلقه في المنزل.
Give that to me. I'll take it home.
أعط ذلك لي. سآخذها إلى المنزل.
The AI's view is different from that of humans.
وجهة نظر الذكاء الاصطناعى تختلف عن وجهة نظر البشر.
- I'll go with the frame. - Okay.
- سأذهب مع الإطار. - تمام.
Will it give it a higher price...
هل ستعطيه سعرًا أعلى ...
- if it has a frame? - The picture...
- إذا كان لديه إطار؟ - الصورة ...
- Yes. This is unfinished. - It's a bit...
- نعم. هذا غير مكتمل. - إنه قليلا ...
This is what happened yesterday.
هذا ما حدث بالأمس.
- What's that? - How did I give him a frame...
- ما هذا؟ - كيف أعطيته إطارًا ...
for such a drawing?
لمثل هذا الرسم؟
- It's such a bad drawing. - I drew what happened...
- إنه رسم سيء. - وجهت ما حدث ...
in our family yesterday.
في عائلتنا أمس.
I went to Yongin for my father's birthday.
ذهبت إلى يونغين في عيد ميلاد والدي.
- I got so annoyed on the way back. - It's pretty.
- لقد انزعجت جدا في طريق العودة. - إنها جميلة.
I wasn't smiling, but everybody else was enjoying it.
لم أكن أبتسم ، لكن الجميع كان يستمتع بها.
Right.
يمين.
It's like a commercial.
إنه مثل إعلان تجاري.
- Everyone else but me is happy. - Okay.
- كل شخص آخر ولكن أنا سعيد. - تمام.
- I say 3 dollars. - I say 2 dollars.
- أقول 3 دولارات. - أقول 2 دولار.
- Thirty cents. - We'll ask the AI.
- ثلاثون سنتا. - سوف نسأل الذكاء الاصطناعي.
- A frame for such a bad drawing. - The frame...
- إطار لمثل هذا الرسم السيئ. - الإطار ...
The frame may make it seem...
قد يجعل الإطار يبدو ...
- like an expensive one. - Right.
- مثل واحد باهظ الثمن. - يمين.
But I don't think that will fool the AI.
لكنني لا أعتقد أن هذا سوف يخدع الذكاء الاصطناعي.
- This one. The frame... - It's out!
- هذا. الإطار ... - إنه خارج!
- "Well, this..."
- "حسنًا ، هذا ..." - "حسنًا ، هذا ..."
Well, this is like a rough doodle...
حسنًا ، هذا مثل رسومات الشعار المبتكرة ...
that was drawn while going on a group retreat.
تم رسم ذلك أثناء الذهاب في تراجع جماعي.
- What is it? - "Well, this..."
- ما هذا؟ - "حسنًا ، هذا ..."
- How much is it? - It starts with "Well, this..."
- كم سعره؟ - يبدأ بـ "حسنًا ، هذا ..."
"Going on a group retreat."
"الذهاب في تراجع جماعي."
It looks like people were just crammed into the box.
يبدو أن الناس كانوا محشرين في الصندوق.
The character on the left has an open mouth in excitement.
الشخصية على اليسار لها فم مفتوح في الإثارة.
The driver on the right has a rotten expression.
السائق على اليمين لديه تعبير فاسد.
The two contrast so much that it gets some attention.
يتناقض الاثنان لدرجة أنه يحظى ببعض الاهتمام.
That much?
هذا كثيرا؟
(He's upset.)
(انه منزعج.)
- This piece costs 18 dollars. - There.
- هذه القطعة تكلف 18 دولار. - هناك.
- How much? - Eighteen dollars?
- كم ثمن؟ - ثمانية عشر دولار؟
- Eighteen dollars.
- ثمانية عشر دولارًا. - ثمانية عشر دولار؟
(A generous appraisal compared to a harsh rating)
(تقييم سخي مقارنة بالتصنيف القاسي)
- What is this? - This piece costs 18 dollars.
- ما هذا؟ - هذه القطعة تكلف 18 دولار.
The drawing costs 3 dollars, and the frame costs 15 dollars.
يكلف الرسم 3 دولارات ، ويكلف الإطار 15 دولارًا.
"The frame costs 15 dollars..."
"الإطار يكلف 15 دولارًا ..."
- Three dollars. - Mine costs more.
- ثلاثة دولارات. - يكلف الألغام أكثر.
I guessed it correctly. I guessed it right.
لقد خمنت ذلك بشكل صحيح. لقد خمنت ذلك بشكل صحيح.
(Why, you...)
(لماذا ، أنت ...)
Anyway, Haha got 18 dollars.
على أي حال ، هاها حصلت على 18 دولار.
That's the price of the frame.
هذا هو سعر الإطار.
(Still, the frame helped Haha a lot.)
(ومع ذلك ، ساعد الإطار هاها كثيرًا.)
- Anyway. Hey! - Nice.
- على أي حال. يا! - لطيف - جيد.
If you took that,
إذا أخذت ذلك ،
- you should have done well. - The frame mattered.
- كان يجب أن تفعل جيدا. - الإطار مهم.
It really hurts you.
إنه يؤلمك حقًا.
It's not sane. People liked my drawing.
إنه ليس عاقلًا. أحب الناس الرسم الخاص بي.
That's not true. Your drawing was poor.
هذا ليس صحيحا. كان الرسم سيئًا.
- I get it now. - Next is Seok Jin's...
- أحصل عليه الآن. - التالي هو سوك جين ...
- I'm excited. - drawing.
- أنا متحمس. - رسم.
- This is no joke. - Goodness.
- هذه ليست مزحة. - الخير.
Seok Sam.
سوك سام.
- It's scary.
- إنه أمر مخيف. - إنه أمر مخيف.
Is this occult? What is that?
هل هذا غامض؟ ما هذا؟
- I... - What is that?
- أنا ... - ما هذا؟
I drew a house.
رسمت منزل.
I drew a house to look like a person.
رسمت منزلاً لتبدو وكأنه شخص.
There are hearts on the side.
هناك قلوب على الجانب.
- It's there. - Our happy house.
- إنه هناك. - منزلنا السعيد.
It's a depiction of a person and a house.
إنه تصوير لشخص ومنزل.
- He made a sly move. - This is...
- لقد اتخذ خطوة خبيثة. - هذا هو...
- My dream... - He signed it.
- حلمي ... - وقع عليه.
- The signature. The AI... - I signed it.
- التوقيع. الذكاء الاصطناعي ... - لقد وقعت عليه.
- can sign it. - Right.
- يمكن التوقيع عليه. - يمين.
The signing is the point.
التوقيع هو النقطة.
- But that... - Famous artists sign their work.
- ولكن هذا ... - الفنانين المشهورين يوقعون على عملهم.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
- I say 2.5 dollars. - It's a bit...
- أقول 2.5 دولار. - إنه قليلا ...
- It's weird. - It is scary.
- إنه غريب. - إنه أمر مخيف.
It's weird.
إنه غريب.
- It is a bit scary. - Horror. That's the point.
- إنه أمر مخيف بعض الشيء. - رعب. هذه هي النقطة.
How much will you pay for this art piece?
كم ستدفع ثمن هذه القطعة الفنية؟
I'm not sure if the house is smiling or the person is the house.
لست متأكدًا مما إذا كان المنزل يبتسم أو أن الشخص هو المنزل.
It is bewildering to look at it.
إنه أمر محير للنظر إليه.
Looking at the signature,
النظر إلى التوقيع ،
the artist seems to think this is art.
يبدو أن الفنان يعتقد أن هذا الفن.
I'd buy that confidence.
سأشتري هذه الثقة.
I added ten dollars for the signature premium.
أضفت عشرة دولارات لتوقيع قسط.
So the piece is worth 12 dollars.
وبالتالي فإن القطعة تساوي 12 دولار.
Twelve dollars.
اثنا عشر دولار.
- What? - Twelve dollars.
- ماذا؟ - اثني عشر دولار.
(That is worth 12 dollars?)
(هذا يستحق 12 دولار؟)
How much?
كم ثمن؟
- The signature is ten dollars. - A signature premium.
- التوقيع هو عشرة دولارات. - قسط توقيع.
- Really? - The signature is ten dollars?
- حقًا؟ - التوقيع هو عشرة دولارات؟
- The signature?
- التوقيع هو عشرة دولارات؟ - التوقيع؟
The signature is ten dollars.
التوقيع هو عشرة دولارات.
(This is worth ten dollars.)
(هذا يستحق عشرة دولارات.)
How would it know that's his signature?
كيف يعرف هذا هو توقيعه؟
- So the signature... - I should have signed mine.
- إذن التوقيع ... - كان ينبغي عليّ توقيع الألغام.
It recognized the famous artist's signature.
لقد تعرفت على توقيع الفنان الشهير.
I aimed for that.
أنا استهدفت ذلك.
- This is... - Seok Jin's piece...
- هذا ... - قطعة Seok Jin ...
is worth 12 dollars. Next is Jang Hoon's piece.
يستحق 12 دولار. التالي هو قطعة Jang Hoon.
- Please show it to us. - But this...
- يرجى إظهارها لنا. - لكن هذا ...
I'm curious to see Jang Hoon's piece.
أشعر بالفضول لرؤية قطعة Jang Hoon.
I doubt it will be worth ten cents.
أشك في أنه سيكون قيمته عشرة سنتات.
(Would the drawing be as delicate as his personality?)
(هل سيكون الرسم حساسًا مثل شخصيته؟)
This is troublesome.
هذا مزعج.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
- This is trouble. - What is this?
- هذه مشكلة. - ما هذا؟
They gave me so little time.
أعطوني القليل من الوقت.
- But this... - What is this?
- لكن هذا ... - ما هذا؟
They took it from me while I was sketching.
أخذوها مني بينما كنت أرسم.
- What are they doing? - Are they aliens?
- ماذا يفعلون؟ - هل هم الأجانب؟
- But... - This side.
- لكن ... - هذا الجانب.
- This is a spaceship, and this... - No.
- هذه سفينة فضائية ، وهذا ... - رقم
Are they aliens?
هل هم أجانب؟
I was drawing the people one by one at the end...
كنت أرسم الناس واحدًا تلو الآخر في النهاية ...
- when they took it from me. - But...
- عندما أخذوها مني. - لكن...
I'm worried about the price he'll get for this.
أنا قلق بشأن السعر الذي سيحصل عليه لهذا.
But this...
لكن هذا ...
This is the kind of drawing where a frustrating friend says,
هذا هو نوع الرسم حيث يقول صديق محبط ،
"Hey, I drew a family and house," and you have to force yourself...
"مهلا ، لقد رسمت عائلة ومنزل" ، وعليك أن تجبر نفسك ...
to say, "Yes, it's a family."
أن أقول ، "نعم ، إنها عائلة".
The piece isn't even worth one dollar,
هذه القطعة لا تساوي حتى دولار واحد ،
but I'll give it that as a cleanup fee.
لكنني سأعطيه ذلك كرسوم تنظيف.
- This is... - But it...
- هذا ... - لكنه ...
But this drawing... What is that?
لكن هذا الرسم ... ما هذا؟
It makes a reasonable judgment.
يصدر حكمًا معقولًا.
This...
هذا...
They're leading.
انهم يقودون.
- The signature one. - What is that?
- التوقيع واحد. - ما هذا؟
Now, it's Gi Ru's drawing.
الآن ، إنه رسم GI RU.
- She stamped her foot. - What's this?
- ختمت قدمها. - ما هذا؟
- I like philosophical things. - You're amazing.
- أحب الأشياء الفلسفية. - أنت مدهش.
I like philosophical things.
أنا أحب الأشياء الفلسفية.
(A philosophical painter using her foot, Gi Ru)
(رسام فلسفي باستخدام قدمها ، جي رو)
- But mine... - The team has to win.
- لكن لي ... - يجب على الفريق الفوز.
Mine has a body part. It could get a high price.
منجم لديه جزء الجسم. يمكن أن تحصل على سعر مرتفع.
- She stamped her foot. - What is this?
- ختمت قدمها. - ما هذا؟
- That's... - That's the worst.
- هذا ... - هذا هو الأسوأ.
The worst?
الأسوأ؟
- This has a meaning. - It's the worst.
- هذا له معنى. - إنه الأسوأ.
From home...
من المنزل ...
- You all leave home, - It's the worst.
- أنت جميعا تغادر المنزل ، - إنه الأسوأ.
earn money, and go out to eat. Those feet represent that.
كسب المال ، والخروج لتناول الطعام. تمثل تلك القدمين ذلك.
- What's that 110v? - The 110v?
- ما هذا 110 فولت؟ - 110 فولت؟
- A pig's nose. - That's a pig's nose?
- أنف خنزير. - هذا أنف خنزير؟
- A pork belly restaurant? - No.
- مطعم لحم لحم الخنزير؟ - لا.
Isn't that the Jangchung-dong king jokbal?
أليس هذا ملك يانغشونغ-دونغ جوكبال؟
I say 30 dollars.
أقول 30 دولار.
- It's meaningful. - I give it 30 dollars.
- إنه مفيد. - أعطيها 30 دولار.
How much would you pay for this art piece?
كم تدفع ثمن هذه القطعة الفنية؟
- This is worth 11 dollars. - How much?
- هذا يستحق 11 دولار. - كم ثمن؟
- Ten dollars for the feet. - Eighteen dollars?
- عشرة دولارات للقدم. - ثمانية عشر دولار؟
- How much? - Ten dollars for the feet.
- كم ثمن؟ - عشرة دولارات للقدم.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
- We have a chance.
- لدينا فرصة. - لدينا فرصة.
- It's doable. - Shin Gi Ru.
- إنه قابل للتنفيذ. - شين جي رو.
- Yours was worth 11 dollars. - It was higher than I thought.
- لك كان قيمته 11 دولار. - كان أعلى مما اعتقدت.
It's cute.
إنه لطيف.
Worth 25 dollars for its potential as an emotional education poster.
بقيمة 25 دولارًا لإمكاناتها كملصق تعليمي عاطفي.
- Twenty-five dollars! - Twenty-five dollars! Okay.
- خمسة وعشرون دولار! - خمسة وعشرون دولار! تمام.
Jang Hoon, our youngest, almost got scratched here.
جانغ هون ، أصغرنا ، كاد خدش هنا.
It's worth 14 dollars for being a witness sketch of the incident.
إنها تساوي 14 دولارًا لكونها رسمًا شاهدًا للحادث.
- Fourteen dollars! - Fourteen dollars! Not bad.
- أربعة عشر دولار! - أربعة عشر دولار! ليس سيئًا.
Hey!
يا!
I couldn't draw the face.
لم أستطع رسم الوجه.
Worth 12 dollars as the rainbow won diligence points.
بقيمة 12 دولارًا حيث فاز قوس قزح بنقاط العناية.
We're in trouble.
نحن في ورطة.
- I highlighted the texture. - It gives it a mood.
- أبرزت الملمس. - إنه يعطيها مزاجًا.
At least an hour was put into this. Worth 18 dollars.
تم وضع ساعة على الأقل في هذا. بقيمة 18 دولار.
(The Kim Family made a comeback thanks to Artist Shindong!)
(عدت عائلة كيم بفضل الفنان شيندونغ!)
- What? - Amazing.
- ماذا؟ - مدهش.
- What is this?
- مدهش. - ما هذا؟
(Only Jae Seok and Jong Kook are left.)
(فقط ترك جاي سوك وجونغ كوك.)
- That's right. - No way.
- هذا صحيح. - مستحيل.
- Good. We won. - We won.
- جيد. فزنا. - فزنا.
- We won now.
- فزنا الآن. - فزنا.
- This is over.
- فزنا. - هذا قد انتهى.
- We won with that. - They can't beat this.
- فزنا بذلك. - لا يمكنهم التغلب على هذا.
I think Jae Seok's will get a high price.
أعتقد أن جاي سوك سيحصل على ثمن مرتفع.
- Now, we'll check... - Okay.
- الآن ، سوف نتحقق ... - حسنًا.
Jong Kook's drawing.
رسم جونغ كوك.
Mine. But mine is unfinished.
مِلكِي. لكن لي غير مكتملة.
- Jong Kook! - I didn't finish it.
- جونغ كوك! - لم أنتهي منه.
- This... - He drew well.
- هذا ... - جذب جيدا.
- That's at least 30 dollars.
- هذا 30 دولار على الأقل. - وجه جيدا.
- That's like a cartoon. - It's pretty.
- هذا مثل الكرتون. - إنها جميلة.
- That's at least... - He drew well.
- هذا على الأقل ... - جذب جيدا.
You could draw cartoons.
يمكنك رسم الرسوم الكاريكاتورية.
- I ran out of time.
- وجه جيدا. - لقد نفدت الوقت.
- He drew well. - Draw a webtoon.
- وجه جيدا. - ارسم webtoon.
- Is the person in the middle me? - It's you.
- هل الشخص في الوسط لي؟ - إنه أنت.
- That looks so much like me. - What?
- هذا يشبهني كثيرًا. - ماذا؟
- Who is this baby?
- من هو هذا الطفل؟ - ماذا؟
- That's me.
- من هو هذا الطفل؟ - هذا أنا.
- This baby. - I drew myself to look cute.
- هذا الطفل. - رسمت نفسي لتبدو لطيفة.
Who is that caveman?
من هو رجل الكهف؟
A caveman?
رجل الكهف؟
- That's obviously Jang Hoon. - Jang Hoon.
- من الواضح أن هذا يانغ هون. - جانج هون.
How could you draw me...
كيف يمكن أن ترسمني ...
like that?
هكذا؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
- What's wrong? - He drew so well.
- ما هو الخطأ؟ - وجه جيدا.
Is that Frankenstein?
هل هذا فرانكشتاين؟
But why doesn't Ji Hyo have a body?
ولكن لماذا لا يكون لدى جي هيو جسم؟
I was drawing Ji Hyo, but I didn't have time.
كنت أرسم جي هيو ، لكن لم يكن لدي وقت.
- He drew well. - But...
- وجه جيدا. - لكن...
I think it will get a good price.
أعتقد أنه سيحصل على سعر جيد.
- Right. - This would be worth 50 dollars.
- يمين. - هذا سيكون 50 دولار.
- Please. - It would be worth 50 dollars.
- لو سمحت. - سيكون قيمته 50 دولار.
But the AI doesn't know that.
لكن الذكاء الاصطناعي لا يعرف ذلك.
So how much is it worth?
إذن كم يستحق؟
This picture has the most...
هذه الصورة لديها أكثر ...
painting-like composition and depiction of figures...
تكوين تشبه اللوحة وتصوير الأشكال ...
- that I have seen so far. - No way.
- التي رأيتها حتى الآن. - مستحيل.
- Amazing. - "The most painting-like."
- مدهش. - "الأكثر تشبه اللوحة."
- Jong Kook. Look. - Really? Hold on.
- جونغ كوك. ينظر. - حقًا؟ يتمسك.
- Give it 50 dollars. - What is it?
- امنحها 50 دولارًا. - ما هذا؟
(The evaluation starts differently.)
(يبدأ التقييم بشكل مختلف.)
(Feeling anxious)
(الشعور بالقلق)
Simple but observant.
بسيطة ولكن الملاحظة.
The biggest strength of this painting...
أكبر قوة لهذه اللوحة ...
is that viewers can tell who is who.
هل يمكن للمشاهدين معرفة من هو.
- Detail. - That's the highest praise.
- التفاصيل. - هذا هو أعلى الثناء.
Amazing.
مدهش.
- How much is it? - What?
- كم سعره؟ - ماذا؟
- Please. - How much is it?
- لو سمحت. - كم سعره؟
The characters' acting drove up the price.
رفع التمثيل الشخصيات السعر.
- This drawing is worth 42 dollars. - How much?
- هذا الرسم يستحق 42 دولار. - كم ثمن؟
- It's 42 dollars! - Yes!
- إنه 42 دولار! - نعم!
(The highest price ever, 42 dollars)
(أعلى سعر على الإطلاق ، 42 دولار)
(The Yu Family: 55 dollars, the Kim Family: 102 dollars)
(عائلة يو: 55 دولارًا ، عائلة كيم: 102 دولار)
(The price difference widened in an instant.)
(اتسع فرق السعر في لحظة.)
- This is amazing. - Yes!
- هذا مذهل. - نعم!
- It's unbelievable. - This is good.
- لا يصدق. - هذا جيد.
(Painter Kim made the stingy AI generous.)
(جعل الرسام كيم ذا بغيض من الذكاء الاصطناعي.)
(We're in trouble.)
(نحن في ورطة.)
- It's 42 dollars. - This is...
- إنه 42 دولار. - هذا هو...
Let me use the AI we know.
اسمحوا لي أن أستخدم الذكاء الاصطناعي الذي نعرفه.
- I don't think this one is right. - My gosh.
- لا أعتقد أن هذا صحيح. - يا إلهي.
- We did it. - All right.
- فعلنا ذلك. - حسنًا.
- This is high. - That's really...
- هذا مرتفع. - هذا حقا ...
- It's precise. - We can use it at a gallery.
- إنه دقيق. - يمكننا استخدامه في معرض.
- It's detailed. - We did it.
- إنه مفصل. - فعلنا ذلك.
Detail.
التفاصيل.
How did he draw me like that?
كيف رسمني هكذا؟
I'm so relieved.
أنا مرتاح جدا.
- We can say it's over. - Me.
- يمكننا أن نقول أن الأمر قد انتهى. - أنا.
- It's my turn. - Yu Jae Seok's drawing.
- حان دوري. - يو يو جاي سوك رسم.
- We will know once we see it. - Let's see.
- سنعرف بمجرد رؤيته. - دعونا نرى.
- All right.
- حسنًا. - دعونا نرى.
My drawing...
الرسم الخاص بي ...
I should've added my autograph.
كان يجب أن أضيف توقيعي.
- He should've signed it. - Let's go.
- كان يجب أن يوقعه. - دعنا نذهب.
Things are going smoothly with my drawing.
تسير الأمور بسلاسة مع الرسم.
I think...
أظن...
(For his precise AI targeting,)
(لاستهداف الذكاء الاصطناعي الدقيق ،)
(Painter Yu got an extra 2 minutes.)
(حصلت الرسام يو على دقيقتين إضافيين.)
- I'm excited. - It might say it's artistic.
- أنا متحمس. - قد يقول إنه فني.
There's no point in the drawing.
ليس هناك فائدة من الرسم.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
(The drawing is like his fingerprint.)
(الرسم يشبه بصماته.)
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
- What's that? - My goodness.
- ما هذا؟ - يا إلهي.
- There's no point. - It's like a little kid's drawing.
- ليس هناك فائدة. - إنه مثل رسم طفل صغير.
There's no point in the drawing.
ليس هناك فائدة من الرسم.
- What's that? - That counts for two people.
- ما هذا؟ - هذا مهم لشخصين.
Jae Seok's is for two people.
جاي سوك هو لشخصين.
All right. This is Gi Ru.
حسنًا. هذا هو جي رو.
Seok Sam.
سوك سام.
- I think I know which one is me. - Here's Se Chan.
- أعتقد أنني أعرف أي واحد هو أنا. - ها هي شان.
- Everyone's here. Ye Eun. - Okay.
- الجميع هنا. أيها ايون. - تمام.
Who is the person in the lower right area?
من هو الشخص في المنطقة السفلية اليمنى؟
Who? This one?
من؟ هذا؟
- I just drew a person. - Who is it?
- أنا فقط رسمت شخص. - من هذا؟
Didn't Ji Hyo draw this when he was two years old?
ألم يرسم جي هيو هذا عندما كان عمره عامين؟
- Isn't that Mushroom Boy? - I just drew it.
- أليس هذا الفتى الفطر؟ - لقد رسمتها للتو.
- We will ask the AI then. - Let's do that.
- سوف نسأل الذكاء الاصطناعي بعد ذلك. - دعونا نفعل ذلك.
I'm curious about this one.
أنا فضولي بشأن هذا.
- This is really... - I'm curious.
- هذا حقًا ... - أنا فضولي.
Let's pull off a miracle.
دعنا ننسحب معجزة.
A miracle.
معجزة.
We can do this.
يمكننا أن نفعل هذا.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Miracle. It's taking some time.
معجزة. يستغرق الأمر بعض الوقت.
It's taking a long time.
يستغرق وقتا طويلا.
This is what you get...
هذا ما تحصل عليه ...
after giving kids some colored pencils...
بعد إعطاء الأطفال بعض أقلام الرصاص الملونة ...
and having them draw something on a canvas.
وجعلهم يرسمون شيئًا على قماش.
There's no theme, no composition, and no focus.
لا يوجد موضوع ، لا تكوين ، ولا تركيز.
That's just too harsh.
هذا قاسي للغاية.
What does it say?
ماذا يقول؟
It's hard to tell...
من الصعب معرفة ...
if the person on the right is an elephant or a human.
إذا كان الشخص الموجود على اليمين فيلًا أو إنسانًا.
And the kids at the bottom...
والأطفال في الأسفل ...
are more like...
أشبه ...
emotionless doodles with a few lines.
رسومات الشعار المبتكرة العاطفية مع بضعة خطوط.
But this is...
لكن هذا ...
(Harsh criticism)
(انتقادات قاسية)
- Why aren't you reading the rest? - This is really...
- لماذا لا تقرأ الباقي؟ - هذا حقا ...
"This is worth six dollars. To be honest,"
"هذا يستحق ستة دولارات. لكي نكون صادقين ،"
- Six dollars? - "it's not worth five dollars..."
- ستة دولارات؟ - "لا يستحق خمسة دولارات ..."
- Six dollars? - "it's not worth five dollars,"
- ستة دولارات؟ - "لا يستحق خمسة دولارات" ، "
"but I'm adding one dollar for labor costs..."
"لكنني أضيف دولارًا واحدًا لتكاليف العمالة ..."
"since there are many people in the drawing."
"نظرًا لوجود الكثير من الناس في الرسم."
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
Jae Seok's drawing is six dollars.
رسم جاي سوك هو ست دولارات.
For your team score, we will double his for the total.
لنتيجة فريقك ، سنضاعفه للمجموع.
That's higher than I thought.
هذا أعلى مما اعتقدت.
My goodness. Seriously...
يا إلهي. بجد...
- I got the lowest amount. - It's not even close.
- حصلت على أدنى كمية. - إنه ليس قريبًا.
- Are you in last place? - He is.
- هل أنت في المكان الأخير؟ - هو.
- I got six dollars. - Six dollars?
- حصلت على ستة دولارات. - ستة دولارات؟
- It will be doubled.
- سوف يتضاعف. - سوف يتضاعف.
But your price will be doubled.
ولكن سوف يتضاعف سعرك.
I'll announce the results...
سأعلن عن النتائج ...
of the Between Masterpiece and Failure Race.
من بين التحفة وسباق الفشل.
The total price of the Yu Family's drawings...
السعر الإجمالي لرسومات عائلة يو ...
is 67 dollars.
هو 67 دولار.
And the total price of the Kim Family's drawings...
والسعر الإجمالي لرسومات عائلة كيم ...
- is 102 dollars. - Yes!
- هو 102 دولار. - نعم!
Nice!
لطيف - جيد!
- The Kim Family wins the race. - We did it.
- عائلة كيم تفوز بالسباق. - فعلنا ذلك.
Kim Jong Kook, the head of the Kim Family,
كيم جونغ كوك ، رئيس عائلة كيم ،
the first-place winner, excluding Kim Jong Kook,
الفائز بالمركز الأول ، باستثناء كيم جونغ كوك ،
Shindong,
شيندونغ ،
and the second-place winner, Haha will receive the prize.
والفائز في المركز الثاني ، هاها سيحصل على الجائزة.
- Okay. - Yes!
- تمام. - نعم!
And,
و،
though his family won,
على الرغم من أن عائلته فازت ،
Seo Jang Hoon drew a total flop...
رسم سيو يانغ هون تقلبًا تامًا ...
and came in last...
وجاء في آخر ...
with the price of one dollar,
بسعر دولار واحد ،
- so he will get the penalty. - Penalty.
- لذلك سوف يحصل على العقوبة. - جزاء.
- I knew it.
- كنت أعرف. - جزاء.
I had no expectations in the first place.
لم يكن لدي أي توقعات في المقام الأول.
Yu Jae Seok, the head of the losing family,
يو جاي سوك ، رئيس العائلة الخاسرة ،
is getting the penalty.
هو الحصول على العقوبة.
- Oh, no. - I told you...
- أوه ، لا. - أخبرتك...
the 1st and 2nd place winners will be exempted.
سيتم إعفاء الفائزين بالمركز الأول والثاني.
The first place...
المقام الأول ...
is Ji Ye Eun with 25 dollars,
هل جي يون مع 25 دولار ،
and the second place...
والمركز الثاني ...
is Jee Seok Jin with 12 dollars.
هل جي سوك جين مع 12 دولار.
- It doesn't have the sides. - Milkshake
- ليس لديها الجوانب. - اللبن المخفوق
(Chungju Ji and Jee ranked high today.)
(Chungju Ji و Jee احتلوا المرتبة العالية اليوم.)
So, the members to get the penalty today...
لذلك ، الأعضاء للحصول على عقوبة اليوم ...
are Yang Se Chan, Shin Gi Ru, Yu Jae Seok,
هل يانغ سي تشان ، شين جي رو ، يو جاي سوك ،
and Seo Jang Hoon. Those four members.
و SEO Jang Hoon. هؤلاء الأعضاء الأربعة.
- What's that? - The prize is...
- ما هذا؟ - الجائزة ...
- It's dragon fruit. - a common object in paintings.
- إنها فاكهة التنين. - كائن مشترك في اللوحات.
It's the fruit set.
إنها مجموعة الفاكهة.
- Nice. - The penalty is...
- لطيف - جيد. - العقوبة ...
for those who failed to create a masterpiece.
لأولئك الذين فشلوا في إنشاء تحفة.
They will make another piece by taking a rubbing of their faces.
سوف يصنعون قطعة أخرى من خلال أخذ فرك وجوههم.
Why are we doing this all of a sudden?
لماذا نفعل هذا فجأة؟
What is this? My goodness.
ما هذا؟ يا إلهي.
This is what Jang Hoon hates the most.
هذا هو ما يكره Jang Hoon أكثر.
- Right. - The thing he hates most.
- يمين. - الشيء الذي يكرهه أكثر.
Show them how you do it.
أظهر لهم كيف تفعل ذلك.
You are handsome.
أنت وسيم.
It's decalcomania.
إنه ديالكوفيا.
All right.
حسنًا.
(The face-rubbing experts give a demonstration.)
(يقدم خبراء التمسك بالوجه مظاهرة.)
- Let's do this. - It looks good.
- دعونا نفعل هذا. - تبدو جيدة.
- Good. - It will come out well.
- جيد. - سوف يخرج بشكل جيد.
- It's perfect. - It looks good.
- إنه مثالي. - تبدو جيدة.
(Gi Ru, who left footprints, takes a rubbing of her face.)
(Gi Ru ، التي تركت آثار أقدام ، تأخذ فرك وجهها.)
- It's really big. - Hang on.
- إنه كبير حقًا. - انتظر.
It's huge.
إنه ضخم.
- Why is it so big? - By the way,
- لماذا هو كبير جدا؟ - بالمناسبة،
it's all over my face.
كل شيء على وجهي.
All right. Next.
حسنًا. التالي.
He is...
هو ...
He's the guy from Japan with a barrage of blows.
إنه الرجل من اليابان مع وابل من الضربات.
(Patting)
(باتنج)
It's him.
إنه هو.
- We can see him at a festival. - Right.
- يمكننا رؤيته في مهرجان. - يمين.
(Jang Hoon begins his face painting.)
(يانغ هون يبدأ لوحة وجهه.)
Oh, no.
أوه ، لا.
He really hates it.
انه حقا يكره ذلك.
(He really hates it.)
(إنه يكرهها حقًا.)
(Struggling)
(يكافح)
How did he end up like this?
كيف انتهى به الأمر مثل هذا؟
- He's being detailed. - He's meticulous.
- إنه مفصل. - إنه دقيق.
You are doing it with a lot of care.
أنت تفعل ذلك مع الكثير من الرعاية.
I want to make sure that his wrinkles are printed.
أريد أن أتأكد من طباعة تجاعيده.
He's so meticulous.
إنه دقيق للغاية.
Even his pores will be printed.
حتى مسامه سيتم طباعتها.
- Jae Seok is really... - Jae Seok,
- جاي سوك حقًا ... - جاي سوك ،
- put it on his face thoroughly. - He doesn't usually do that.
- ضعه على وجهه جيدًا. - لا يفعل ذلك عادة.
- You aren't usually like this. - Thoroughly.
- أنت لست مثل هذا عادة. - كاملاً.
Put some more on his cheeks.
ضع المزيد على خديه.
- That's enough, Jae Seok. - Stop it.
- هذا يكفي ، جاي سوك. - أوقفه.
- That's enough. - You're being playful again.
- هذا يكفي. - أنت مرحة مرة أخرى.
Stop it already!
توقف بالفعل!
(Stop it already!)
(أوقفها بالفعل!)
(Feeling great)
(شعور رائع)
You look so happy.
تبدين سعيدة جدا.
(You look so happy!)
(أنت تبدو سعيدا جدا!)
Print two sheets.
اطبع صفحتين.
(Sighing)
(تنهد)
- There you go. - You're doing well.
- هناك تذهب. - أنت بخير.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
Take it off gently.
خلعها بلطف.
- Gently. - We will get a masterpiece.
- بلطف. - سوف نحصل على تحفة.
"Baebully Hills."
"بيبلي هيلز."
- All right. - That's amazing.
- حسنًا. - هذا مذهل.
- It came out well. - It looks good.
- لقد خرج بشكل جيد. - تبدو جيدة.
- It's a good one. - It looks annoyed.
- إنه جيد. - يبدو منزعجًا.
His annoyed face is printed.
يطبع وجهه المزعج.
He looks very upset.
يبدو مستاء جدا.
- Thank you.
- شكرًا لك. - شكرًا لك.
(We thank the Baebullians, Jang Hoon, Gi Ru, and Shindong...)
(نشكر Baebullians و Jang Hoon و Gi Ru و Shindong ...)
(for filling up our day.)
(لملء يومنا.)
(The Returning Home in Glory Special)
(العودة إلى الوطن في Glory Special)
(Kim Min Jong, the national judo athlete who swept the world)
(كيم مين جونغ ، رياضي الجودو الوطني الذي اجتاح العالم)
(Kim Ha Yoon, the national
(كيم ها يون ، رياضي الجودو الوطني الذي اجتاح العالم)
(The nation's treasured athletes are welcomed...)
(رحب الرياضيون الذين يعتزون في البلاد ...)
(by the B-list PE students.)
(من قبل طلاب B-List PE.)
(The master of vault, Yang Ak Seon)
(سيد Vault ، Yang AK Seon)
(The fairy of Running University, Fake Yeon Jae)
(جنية الجامعة الجري ، يون جاي المزيفة)
(Confused)
(مشوش)
(The conference of the PE department at Running University starts.)
(يبدأ مؤتمر قسم PE في الجامعة.)
Except for these two, the rest...
باستثناء هذين ، الباقي ...
(They are at the community center level at most.)
(هم على مستوى مركز المجتمع على الأكثر.)
(What is this?)
(ما هذا؟)
(The fake athletes are blinded...)
(الرياضيون المزيفين أعمى ...)
(by the national treasure prizes.)
(بجوائز الكنز الوطني.)
(Endless fouls)
(أخطاء لا نهاية لها)
(The pride of the national athlete is completely hurt.)
(فخر الرياضي الوطني مؤلم تمامًا.)
Isn't he the Hulk?
أليس هو الهيكل؟
(Forget about the sense of fair play.)
(ننسى الشعور بالعب العادل.)
(How will the hurtful training of Running University end?)
(كيف سوف يتدرب التدريب المؤلم لجامعة الجامعة؟)
(Running Sports University Prize Battle)
(معركة جائزة جامعة الرياضة))